<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-02-28T10:03:34+00:00</updated><id>/en/feed.xml</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Guarding a Cup of Coffee in Dawushan</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%AE%88%E8%AD%B7%E5%A4%A7%E6%AD%A6%E5%B1%B1%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%80%E6%9D%AF%E5%92%96%E5%95%A1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Guarding a Cup of Coffee in Dawushan" /><published>2019-01-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%AE%88%E8%AD%B7%E5%A4%A7%E6%AD%A6%E5%B1%B1%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%80%E6%9D%AF%E5%92%96%E5%95%A1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%AE%88%E8%AD%B7%E5%A4%A7%E6%AD%A6%E5%B1%B1%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%80%E6%9D%AF%E5%92%96%E5%95%A1/">&lt;p&gt;Early this month, the National Development Council invited the new Executive Yuan Youth Advisory Committee for a &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2019-01-11-%E5%9C%B0%E6%96%B9%E5%89%B5%E7%94%9F%E6%94%BF%E7%AD%96%E5%BA%A7%E8%AB%87%E6%9C%83&quot;&gt;policy discussion&lt;/a&gt; on the “National Strategic Plan for Regional Revitalization.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://advisory.yda.gov.tw/02/userpost/27&quot;&gt;Fuyung Xiyi&lt;/a&gt;, a participant, shared his experience of running a computer information labor cooperative. He said when introducing science and technology to support local industrial reform, people should work together to cultivate indigenous talents to foster a sustainable culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;☕ It reminds me of a cup of coffee I tasted in Pingtung. This cup of coffee came from the Ulaljuc tribe, with a story about the creation of the original countryside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⛰ In 2009, the Morakot typhoon destroyed the old Taiwu tribe and the village changed its name to Ulaljuc after moving away. In order to rebuild, the people began to explore the mountains. They found the Japanese coffee garden and chose “organic boutique coffee” as their development goal. Today, there are 126 hectares of coffee grown in Taiwu Township, by 178 coffee farmers. The Coffee Industry Development Hall opened in 2016 is the only post-production factory in the country that can verify the back-end processing of organic coffee; students from all over the world can study here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 Now, Taiwu coffee has spread its aroma around the globe. The International Coffee Appraisal (Coffee Review) evaluated Taiwu Nature Typica at 93 points in 2016 and ranked it among the top three in the Asia-Pacific region, making it one of the most representative coffees of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏠 One of the keys to Ulaljuc’s success lies in the establishment of the Pingtung Native Taiwu Coffee Production Cooperative, which uses its own brand to integrate upstream and downstream industrial chains, supporting each other and marketing together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔗 According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://coop.moi.gov.tw/&quot;&gt;Ministry of the Interior website&lt;/a&gt;, there are currently more than 4,000 cooperatives of 10 categories in Taiwan, including production, distribution, labor, and consumption. In addition to selling goods, cooperatives can also operate insurance and provide services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📜 In the past, there were different interpretations of laws and regulations, and unclear demarcations between coop members and employees. Coops often ran into a wall when they approached government contracts because they could not provide “documents of employment.” Therefore, we are coordinating with the Ministry of the Interior, the Ministry of Labor, and the Public Construction Commission to add a clause on “protection of the rights and interests of cooperative members” in the contract template for the purchase of labor services. In that way, the authorities can better understand the nature of co-ownership and co-governance in cooperatives. We can also recognize the labor rights and interests of members and give full play to the strength of the cooperative economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍯 According to the Paiwan people, in ancient times, the sun laid eggs in a pottery kettle with a hundred-step snake guarding it. Finally, a man and a woman were hatched, that is, the ancestors of the tribe. As a result, the Ulaljuc Village Monument is surrounded by three symbols: the sun, a hundred-step snake, and a pottery kettle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌞 The Coffee Hall and the Cooperative, like hundred-step snakes and pottery kettles, guard the reborn Ulaljuc tribe. I sincerely hope that with the support of the regional revitalization strategy, the development of all parts of Taiwan will shine like the sun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">The Coffee Hall and the Cooperative, like hundred-step snakes and pottery kettles, guard the reborn Ulaljuc tribe.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/99b5176d6b7441531c1fb302aacc48f10481b2ca_2_1380x802.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Five pillars to keep the winter warm</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%95%E6%89%80%E5%86%AC%E6%9A%96-%E4%BA%94%E5%AE%B6%E7%82%BA%E9%84%B0/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Five pillars to keep the winter warm" /><published>2019-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%95%E6%89%80%E5%86%AC%E6%9A%96-%E4%BA%94%E5%AE%B6%E7%82%BA%E9%84%B0</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%95%E6%89%80%E5%86%AC%E6%9A%96-%E4%BA%94%E5%AE%B6%E7%82%BA%E9%84%B0/">&lt;p&gt;Towards the end of the year, I attended a special gathering at the Social Innovation Lab: “Taiwan GSG NAB warmup meetup.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇬🇧 Most people probably don’t know what “GSG” and “NAB” stand for. The full name of GSG is “Global Social Impact Investment Steering Group”. Launched by Britain’s Sir Ronald Cohen at the G8, the group is dedicated to connecting the financial, commercial, and public welfare communities. Since 2015, it has established National Advisory Boards in 21 countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 Why is it called “warmup meetup”? Ray Chen, general manager of the Living Water Enterprise Investment Development Company which helped facilitate this meeting, has exchanged with GSG several times to study the possibility of establishing NAB in Taiwan. In February 2018, NTU Professor Feng Yan, Corey Lien  of the B Corp Association, and Ray Chen were invited to Seoul to take part in the first “Asia-Pacific Impact Investment Workshop”, jointly organized by GSG, British Culture Council, and the United Nations Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific (UNESCAP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 The two-day workshop started off with the launch of the Korean NAP. With the assistance of Ray, I participated through telepresence in the discussion of NAB representatives from various countries, and have gained a better understanding of GSG. It turns out that GSG hopes to promote Impact Investing to drive the capital market and achieve the UN sustainable development goals, which will lead to more social innovation and social entrepreneurship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📈 GSG argues that social and environmental challenges often come from the adverse long-term consequences in the pursuit of short-term profits by investors. In addition to socially responsible practices corporations implement to avoid harm and promote public interests, Impact Investment hopes to go further and encourage innovative teams committed to proposing solutions to global problems, to scale mature solutions and build credibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👪 GSG emphasizes five pillars of the social innovation ecosystem: “demand, supply, intermediaries, ecosystem enablers, and government”. Many people in Taiwan have long been working in these five areas and there are sufficient conditions to establish NAB. Everybody’s enthusiasm is reflected in this small gathering — there were more than a dozen attending representatives from the financial industry and investment funds alone. If all goes well, Taiwan’s NAB will have the chance to become GSG’s fourth member in Asia at the end of this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙏 In the past year’s column, I have shared with you 12 stories — &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%82%BA%E6%9C%89%E6%84%9B%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%BA-%E8%A7%A3%E6%B1%BA%E5%9B%B0%E9%9B%A3/&quot;&gt;Social Enterprises&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%8D%E8%A6%81%E8%87%89%E5%85%AC%E5%9C%92-%E7%9A%84%E8%83%8C%E5%BE%8C/&quot;&gt;Regional Revitalization&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%BF%E5%91%BD%E7%84%A1%E5%83%B9-%E5%95%86%E6%A9%9F%E7%84%A1%E9%99%90/&quot;&gt;Land Rehabilitation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%B8%B6%E5%8B%95%E6%B3%95%E8%A6%8F%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0/&quot;&gt;Food Reuse&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/&quot;&gt;Circular Economy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA/&quot;&gt;Indigenous Culture&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85/&quot;&gt;Smart Pipelines&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E/&quot;&gt;Autonomous Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%BE%9E%E8%AA%B0%E5%BE%97%E6%8C%87%E5%8D%97/&quot;&gt;Civic Technology&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%99%82%E9%9B%A8%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%88-%E9%81%A9%E7%95%B6%E5%85%B6%E6%99%82/&quot;&gt;STEM Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%B4%E5%9C%8B%E7%84%A1%E9%82%8A%E9%9A%9B-%E5%90%8C%E8%81%B2%E5%92%8C%E8%80%85%E5%A4%9A/&quot;&gt;Human-computer Interaction&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C/&quot;&gt;Democratic Innovations&lt;/a&gt;. In the new year, I hope that more people can support Taiwan’s warm power and establish a closer partnership with the global sustainable community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">If all goes well, Taiwan's NAB will have the chance to become GSG's fourth member in Asia at the end of this year.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0eb95b1632fcac7b85a35f55c75fabbfa5a9f585_2_1332x1000.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week Column: Democratic Innovation, Open Source Sustainability</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week Column: Democratic Innovation, Open Source Sustainability" /><published>2018-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C/">&lt;p&gt;I have been “dressing the same” with more and more friends recently. This is not because we buy clothes at the same store, but the result of openness. My colleagues made a unique T-shirt with open-source materials. The T-shirt is printed with the Sustainable Development Goals’ “17 color wheel” logo and the words “Taiwan Can Help” on it. The design drawings are all open and everyone can print one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎 In early November, I visited Canada with my coworkers. Together with the local citizen technology community, we ran a workshop in Toronto to discuss the topic of “platform economy” with civil servants, people and NGOs at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍁 In the workshop, we shared vTaiwan’s experience in dealing with the platform economy issue. “vTaiwan” is a project conceived by the “gov zero” (g0v.tw) community in Taiwan. Through collaboration between the private sector and the government, it collected the ideas of stakeholders such as relevant ministries, service providers, platform operators and users, and finally concluded with consensus. The local citizen technology community in Toronto was amazed and immediately began to plan “g0v.ca”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍕 On the other side of the Atlantic, “g0v.it” has emerged in Europe. In June of this year, a minister who is responsible for “direct democracy” appeared in the joint cabinet of Italy for the first time. How civil society works with the government has become a top priority for the Italian community. The establishment of g0v.it was also inspired by the Taiwanese experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌍 When I was invited to the Vatican in March this year, I introduced g0v’s spirit, that is, “Don’t ask why no one is doing this; first admit that you are ‘no one’.” One of the audiences, Stefano Quintarelli, the Italian Congressman who invited me to the Holy See, immediately learned from Taiwan, and together with his like-minded friends, finally chose to introduce g0v’s first project “Budget Visualization”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄 Our Italian friends believe that this project is presented very intuitively, helps people understand the budget allocation and leaves room for discussion. Therefore, they used the original project’s open-source material to describe how Italian government uses the budget. Just click on the website “g0v.it” and you are free to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 The experience in Canada and Italy reminds me of a friend I met in the Vatican, Jeffrey Sachs, a Columbia University professor who was responsible for designing the Sustainable Development Goals. At g0v.it’s opening ceremony, he said: What g0v does makes the discussion of the matter become “interesting” again. This is the infrastructure that global democracy now needs most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 I agree with Sachs: The more people make contributions, the more opportunities there are to reimagine and build new democracy. The complete open source of g0v is not only social innovation but also democratic innovation. “Taiwan Can Help” is not just a slogan on a T-shirt.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">&quot;Taiwan can help&quot; is not just a slogan on a T-shirt.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c2fc370f07085dd84216a64f6fc6f7aa11d19dd5.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">There is a consensus on the steam fuel cost collaboration meeting, and it is more fair to collect with the mileage.</title><link href="/en/blog/%E6%B1%BD%E7%87%83%E8%B2%BB%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98-%E9%9A%A8%E9%87%8C%E7%A8%8B%E5%BE%B5%E6%94%B6%E6%9B%B4%E5%85%AC%E5%B9%B3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is a consensus on the steam fuel cost collaboration meeting, and it is more fair to collect with the mileage." /><published>2018-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E6%B1%BD%E7%87%83%E8%B2%BB%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98,%E9%9A%A8%E9%87%8C%E7%A8%8B%E5%BE%B5%E6%94%B6%E6%9B%B4%E5%85%AC%E5%B9%B3</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E6%B1%BD%E7%87%83%E8%B2%BB%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98-%E9%9A%A8%E9%87%8C%E7%A8%8B%E5%BE%B5%E6%94%B6%E6%9B%B4%E5%85%AC%E5%B9%B3/">&lt;p&gt;On November 30, 2018, PDIS held the 41st Collaborative Meeting in the Information Center of the Ministry of Finance to discuss &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail /c038fdae-0667-45b0-93cd-0ab761338758&quot;&gt;Automobile fuel tax changed with oil&lt;/a&gt; Proposal. On June 29th, the case was proposed by netizen billy on the Join platform. He pointed out that the fuel consumption fee for motor vehicles is to repair the road surface. It should be levied with oil according to the principle of user payment, using mass transportation vehicles. People do not have to be forced to pay extra fees, and drivers who use more roads have the power to save fuel and reduce carbon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Article 27 of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://law.moj.gov.tw/lawclass/lawall.aspx?pcode=k0040001&quot;&gt;Road Law&lt;/a&gt;: “the highway authority, for road maintenance, construction and for the safety management, it is necessary to levy a vehicle fuel use fee (hereinafter referred to as &quot;steam fuel charge&quot;…&quot;. from this, it can be seen that the fuel charge is collected for road maintenance, construction and safety management. the current collection method is based on the vehicle. the fixed fee is levied each year (season) for the type, purpose of use (self-use or business) and displacement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;there-are-three-similar-systems-in-the-gas-burning-fee-collection-schemes&quot;&gt;There are three similar systems in the gas burning fee collection schemes&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every country has a similar system to collect related expenses to maintain the road surface, but according to the calculation method, it can be divided into Collected by car, &quot;levied with oil&quot; and &quot;levied with mileage&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The levy on the vehicle is generally levied on the weight of the vehicle. In Taiwan, the displacement is calculated based on the displacement of the vehicle. Although the collection cost is relatively low, it is less in line with the principle of &quot;user pays&quot;. With oil, it is levied with fuel, but nowadays, with the continuous innovation of technology, it is necessary to consider the situation in which the roads such as electric vehicles and hybrid vehicles do not use oil, and the situation in which oil is not used, such as agricultural machinery and generators. In terms of oil and so on, it is more difficult to plan, and it is even necessary to create additional pipelines in response to the situation of electric vehicles. With regard to mileage collection, although it is more in line with the principle of user payment, I am afraid that it is necessary to install the corresponding interface on the vehicle to record, or to need to transmit and log in the pipeline, which is more complicated and may also violate privacy. Doubt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Research Report of the [Automotive Fuel Consumption Fee Collection System] made by the Transportation Research Institute of the Ministry of Communications in October 2017 (https://www.iot.gov.tw/file.ashx?id=9fc1e9c8 -a2f5-4e2a-a243-c8a2a8bc53cd)&quot;, as well as pre-interview interviews, the factors that people, government or industry care about are not the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the public, the elements they care about are fair, simple, and private. In terms of fairness, the public hopes to implement the principle of user payment, so that the payment can be more fair; the fee collection mechanism should be simple and convenient, if it is too unsocial, it may lead to public grievances; in the end, it is hoped to protect privacy and not excessively expose too many personal actions. Information to the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the government's focus is on administrative costs, law enforcement, impact on the transportation industry, and income from finance. In terms of administrative costs, the government does not want the administrative costs to be too high, resulting in a larger workload for civil servants. In law enforcement, the relevant fee collection mechanism cannot be illegal, beyond the authority of the government, and cannot be implemented and cannot be implemented; if the transportation industry costs increase due to charges It may affect prices and cause public grievances; in financial terms, the new fee collection mechanism cannot lead to insufficient fees. As for the relevant industry players, most of them do not want to change the fee mechanism to increase operating costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications believes that regardless of the method of collection of steam fuel costs, it should ensure that the financial resources are stable to meet the requirements for road maintenance and construction and safety management. Changes in the mode of expropriation should avoid a substantial increase in administrative costs, and minimize the level of socio-economic impact, and choose the right time to promote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;with-the-oil-collection-problem-with-the-mileage-collection-program-ministry-of-communications-research&quot;&gt;With the oil collection problem with the mileage collection program Ministry of Communications research&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the meeting, the Ministry of Communications explained that in order to avoid public misunderstanding, the Ministry of Communications recommended that the fuel burning fee be renamed Road maintenance fees, so as not to be confused with foreign fuel taxes. Regarding the content of the proposal, the Ministry of Communications said that according to the constitutional content of the Chief Justice, there is no problem with the collection of steam fuel charges. If it is levied with oil, such as the passenger transportation and taxis that were originally exempted, how to collect them in the future and how to refund them is a problem. At the same time, with the oil collection, prices may also rise, which may require more social communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Transportation shared the foreign case and pointed out that due to the fuel efficiency of many vehicles, the fuel tax revenue has also been continuously reduced, and because of the increasing number of electric vehicles, the US fuel tax has gradually evolved under fair consideration. Turn to &quot;road use fees.&quot; Currently in the US state of Oregon, it has been piloted. In 2015, the two-track system was implemented. About 700 vehicles are using the “road use fee”. Washington State and California are also actively testing the mileage-levied scheme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications also pointed out that according to the American AASHTO design guidelines, the damage degree of pavements of different vehicles is about 4 times of the axle load ratio. The damage caused by heavy trucks to the pavement and the maintenance cost in the future are much higher than the average. For self-use vehicles, in the future, it is possible to establish a fee collection mechanism with the weight of the vehicle plus the mileage of the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 13, 2017, the Legislative Yuan has decided to ask the Ministry of Communications to conduct relevant research on the mileage collection as soon as possible. The current study will be closed on May 29, 2019. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that the future discussion includes five levels, including feasible technologies, discussions on privacy, charging systems, and information security. The administrative level should consider how to save personnel costs. The most important part is the financial aspect. In order to take into account the stability and sustainability of finance, we need to know how much money we need to receive in the future. Since the gas burning fee collection system involves people's rights and interests, the Ministry of Communications will also develop plans and field test plans in the future, and then make policy decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8cbd75a50f2b806efa3881e7b4f71cd63e4c547d.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Touring Car Dealer believes that the current Ministry of Communications' exemption policy is only for mass transportation and taxis. It is not fair in the industrial circle. The tour bus is also a kind of mass transportation and should also be included in the exemption scope. The gas station trade union pointed out that the current air pollution charges were imposed, which led to an increase in the oil price of the gas station, which increased the turnover of the gas station, increased the business tax, and increased the handling fee of the bank card, thereby reducing the profit of the gas station. They are worried that if the fuel cost is levied with the oil, I am afraid that a similar situation will occur, which will lower the profit of the gas station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the charging plan, some people pointed out that the Ministry of Transportation’s charging standard now estimates the weight of the vehicle by the amount of exhaust, but now even large-scale transportation vehicles are lighter, and the large displacement may not necessarily represent the weight of the vehicle. . He believes that such a standard is probably the result of the Ministry of Communications's cheaper actions. It is recommended that the weight of the vehicle be used as the charging standard. As for the name changed to the road management fee, he thinks that there is no problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another participant pointed out that the government should maintain good accountability and use market mechanisms to make the system better. It has also been pointed out that they hope that the quality of the road surface can be better, not to build roads too frequently, resulting in poor road quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;us-oregon-province-builds-a-mileage-based-system-with-new-technology&quot;&gt;US Oregon Province builds a mileage-based system with new technology&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Transportation shares the technology of mileage collection. The Oregon State requires OBD2 to be installed on a new car. It will detect the speed and oil condition; OBD2 will transfer the mileage and GPS data to the management platform. The Ministry of Communications team said that their research team is currently studying several programs, such as car code tables, but they are worried that they will be tampered with; if OBD2 is used, the advantage is that it can be read, but there may be errors; if the returned data contains GPS, There may be issues that violate personal privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other is OBE, for example, OBU with many car networking technologies; Beacon can also be connected to the mobile phone using near-field communication, and then return the information. Using ETC detection may also be a method, but it may become that ETC is installed on every road, which may be troublesome. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that Beacon's new mobile phone and the possibility of using ETC tracking are relatively low, so the main evaluation of the first three options, namely the code table, OBD2 and OBE. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that a feasible plan is currently being developed, and the industry will come back to discuss it in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;create-a-new-form-to-help-the-group-focus-on-the-discussion&quot;&gt;Create a new form to help the group focus on the discussion&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to facilitate discussion, the afternoon discussion produced a different form to help you discuss. The table is divided into four quadrants, representing the status quo, with the oil collection, with mileage and mileage + vehicle weight and other four programs; in the current situation, the plan is also included in the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c194663d51670de3cc3035a9883849b784159e52.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; New form designed for discussion &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each program has its own fields of fairness, complexity, administrative costs, related industry costs, user costs, and “other” fields to classify the types of opinions of participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the group discussion, it is followed by the time of each group report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;discussion-in-each-group-believes-that-the-mileage-is-more-fair&quot;&gt;Discussion in each group believes that the mileage is more fair&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group pointed out that if &quot;maintaining the current situation&quot;, regardless of the actual road conditions, all the equal costs will be paid. More similar to the public welfare mentioned in other advanced conferences than fairness. They believe that the current classification of exhaust gas has nothing to do with the actual frequency of use and road damage, which is unfair. Perhaps this collection method is simple and simple, but now it seems to be a bit cheaper. This set of recommendations, the levy standard should be recalculated. Since the public has no way to identify how the 50 billion levy is distributed to the actual use and support of local governments, the fairness of the levy will be repeatedly verified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although there is no other technology in the current stage, the &quot;levy with oil&quot; program can best reflect the situation on the road, but the progress of science and technology makes the fuel consumption performance better and better, and the use of oil does not represent the road. The situation may be doubtful in fairness and justice. At the same time, the implementation of the gas station identification mechanism may be required. The administrative work is relatively complicated, and the increased operating expenses may also lead to loss at the gas station. For oil and electric vehicles, electric vehicles may also require additional matching methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3accdad2bd00872b2ccb00fbf55c715b25620b0b.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group report site &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the part of the mileage collection, according to the report of the Institute of Transportation, in the international trend, in order to stabilize the financial resources and truly reflect the status of the vehicles, the countries have changed their mileage in recent years. It is undeniable that this may be the final The fairest way. If you want to make the actual damage degree of the road can be measured, you can add the weight of the car as a consideration. However, the burden of government investment in construction costs and on-board installation costs is quite large. When technology is fully licensed and mature, it can be popularized with mileage. At the same time, the government may consider personal privacy in addition to collecting mileage. The part of protection should protect personal data in accordance with the individual law. In response to the increase in costs of related businesses, the government needs to consider supporting the use as a stable price. The first group also suggested that all fees should be divided into business and own use, and plan different payment plans. The second group believes that the cost of steam fuel charges is necessary, but in the method of collection, it can be considered to adjust the base fee plus the way of collecting according to different usage conditions. In the current situation, the second group pointed out that some business vehicles are for the public interest, so there is no need to levy steam fuel costs, but they still have damage and use on the road surface, which may be unfair. In terms of calculation standards, the second group believes that the standard calculated by the exhaust volume is outdated and can be calculated by using horsepower and vehicle weight. As part of the oil collection, the second group is concerned that the electric vehicle will not receive the cost; at the same time, the fuel consumption of the car may not be completely fair. If you want to consider the use of oil purchases, it will be more difficult to collect fees. The second group also believes that if the cost is charged by the gas station, it is necessary to be careful that the fee is included in the business tax, resulting in additional taxes on the gas station. It may be possible to give the fuel dispensers a modest fee and compensate for such losses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the participants in the second group believe that the mileage is more fair, and it is recommended to set the basic fee and then add the fee according to the different mileage. The second group also suggested that it is more fair to add the weight of the vehicle as a calculation factor. However, the second group pointed out that there may be ways to distinguish the rates of highways or other roads, and the reliability of mileage is also a problem. They suggested that the government can set standards so that the industry can compete fairly, as long as it can make standards-compliant ways to compete in this market and promote the development of the industry. In the system design, we must consider the old car that can not use the new technology, as well as the cost of installing the new car. The second group of discussions also mentioned the Japanese tax system, which can be taxed on the weight of the car, plus mileage fees, combined to become a new road use fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the second group also reminds that people who are in the middle of the country may need to have a corresponding package to give relief because they do not have public transportation means, otherwise it may be unfair. How to pass back the mileage of the local network environment is also a problem. In the early stage of the second group of proposals, the two-track parallel approach can be used to allow the public to choose the current method, or to add mileage pricing, and then consider the industry status to set a sufficient time limit so that the industry can have sufficient time to introduce it in stages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9b11cdbb2447313db77b4fad10714fa23a3ad77d.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Tang Feng’s live broadcast of the second session &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tang Feng concluded that the results of this meeting will be shared with the dean or other political council members at the government meeting next Monday after the team is fully organized. If there is a clear cut, it will make relevant The open government contact person knows; the hosted ministry will also share the discussion thread and the comprehensive comments of the meeting to the second person on the platform of the agreement, the future &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov. tw/2018-11-30-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba %e7%ac%ac%e5%9b%9b%e5%8d%81%e4%b8%80%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8 %ad%b0&quot;&gt;Verbatim Draft&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1r98q8vigmbtppljwzj68ey5-4hezzijt82uqaszie4w/edit&quot;&gt;issue manual&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kyje69o related information such as =/&quot;&gt;mind map&lt;/a&gt; will also be made public. However, since the fuel burning fee involves legal amendments, even if the name is changed, it is necessary to return to the Legislative Yuan for processing. But if other legislators are interested in this matter in the future, they can refer to the information of this meeting to discuss it, and they will not discuss the same issue again and again. Finally, Tang Feng sincerely thanked the friends who attended the meeting, &quot;Thank you for your advancement in legislation and administrative quality.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kyjE69o=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RJ9iL3GIRGw&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-director-of-the-table-led-the-discussion-to-be-well-received-the-appreciator-agreed-with-the-direction-of-the-ministry-of-communications&quot;&gt;The director of the table led the discussion to be well received. The appreciator agreed with the direction of the Ministry of Communications.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The civil servants who attended the meeting said that the meeting was as expected, but some tools were used, such as Mind map, they are hard to master. Trade union representatives are more concerned about the continuity of the policy. I hope that the government's policies will have consistent results and will not change at any time. Some people suggest that stakeholders can be more subdivided. For example, in this mileage-levied scheme, the garage is an important role in confirming the correctness of OBD, and their lack may be relatively important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second party believes that the government should not only hear the voice of the industry, but also the voice of the consumer group. Otherwise, it may end up with the consortium and manufacturers. They pointed out that the general public may think &quot;how to discuss for so long?&quot; They often feel that the official response is slow and half-time, and I hope to know when there will be changes. At the same time, they also pointed out that the people want the explanations that are easy to understand, and some of them are too literary and may not help communication. They hope that they will not want to find someone to come to the meeting and become a meeting, or that the government can be good for the country and listen to the voice of the people in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this meeting, the congressors at the meeting thought it would be helpful. When the discussion of the group was divergent, the table leader would pull back the discussion in due course. Some people in the public sector will come up with ideas that they have not heard before, and many union representatives share practical problems. The congressmen who help to discuss together understand the ideas of different stakeholders. The second person said that they would agree with the direction of the Ministry of Transportation to collect the mileage, and they will continue to care about this issue in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The participating scholars said that the team's ability to gather and information is very strong, so it can be effectively discussed; when the group discussion, everyone can further discuss specific suggestions from emotional or intuitive speech, the public department can let It is very useful and valuable for the public sector to provide opinions, participate in the process of policy planning, and make a list of the advantages and disadvantages of the program. However, he believes that the stakeholder is not diversified. Although there are many people in the industry, the voice of the second person is not enough. It is suggested that people with more different positions can be invited to participate. The scholar shared that in this meeting, he felt that there was a good chance of citizen participation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">On November 30th, PDIS held the 41st Collaborative Meeting with the Ministry of Communications in the Treasury Center. To assist in the discussion, the PDIS team designed a new form to facilitate discussion among participants. Participants felt that the Department of Transportation's mileage-based program was more equitable with oil.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8cbd75a50f2b806efa3881e7b4f71cd63e4c547d.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Common Voice across borderless waters</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%B4%E5%9C%8B%E7%84%A1%E9%82%8A%E9%9A%9B-%E5%90%8C%E8%81%B2%E5%92%8C%E8%80%85%E5%A4%9A/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Common Voice across borderless waters" /><published>2018-11-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%B4%E5%9C%8B%E7%84%A1%E9%82%8A%E9%9A%9B,%E5%90%8C%E8%81%B2%E5%92%8C%E8%80%85%E5%A4%9A</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%B4%E5%9C%8B%E7%84%A1%E9%82%8A%E9%9A%9B-%E5%90%8C%E8%81%B2%E5%92%8C%E8%80%85%E5%A4%9A/">&lt;p&gt;The dawn has just broken. Yet, the children are already seated in their classroom. They follow their teacher’s lead on screen and practice reading in their own native language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎪 This is a scene from the Council of the Indigenous Peoples’ &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/mismarteducation/&quot;&gt;“Live Broadcasting System Project”&lt;/a&gt;. When the time arrives for self-study each morning, the language teacher appears in front of a green studio screen and give lessons to the children on the other side of Taiwan. One of these studios is located in the national Social Innovation Lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 As an island located on the Pacific Ocean, Taiwan has 16 ethnic languages and 42 dialects among its indigenous peoples. However, these languages are facing the serious threat of extinction. Ten of these languages, including Puyuma, Saisiyat, Sakizaya, Kavalan, Tsou, Hla’alua, Kanakanavu, Mangesle, Mamangele and Donnarukai, have been listed as endangered languages by the United Nations and the Council of the Indigenous Peoples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏡 Teaching these languages to the next generation is the only way to ensure their revival. Therefore, when I saw that the studio of the Social Innovation Lab provides this function, I not only was overjoyed but also began thinking: what else can we contribute in addition to the live broadcast?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💬 The Common Voice project, developed by the social enterprise &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mozilla.org/foundation/&quot;&gt;Mozilla&lt;/a&gt;, has enabled me to see another possibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📲 This project uses crowd participation to improve on the existing AI speech recognition system. The mobile phone voice assistant currently available has made people’s lives much more convenient. However, voice recognition still requires a massive amount of voice data to enable deep learning by the machines. It is extremely expensive to build a computing system or a voice database. For this reason, the speech recognition technology currently available still focuses on mainstream languages, resulting in a decrease in the use of remote languages, which is not conducive to the rehabilitation of remote languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📖 So, Mozilla has come up with the Common Voice Project. From collecting, processing to archiving, it uses CC0 open authorization and completely forgoes the concept of copyright. Anyone can read the text on the website and record their own voice, thereby adding to the voice collection of different languages, accents, gender, age and contributing to the construction of the world’s largest open source voice database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏫 Our “Basic Law of the Indigenous Peoples”, “Basic Law of Hakka” or the “National Language Development Law” under review all have an emphasis on the rights of every person to enjoy an equal opportunity to learn the inherent ethnic languages. Therefore, in the future, we will be working with Common Voice to combine the existing government resources and build a collection of Taiwan’s remote languages, such as the aboriginal ethnic languages, or the tones and accents of each inherent ethnic language. As a result, we are committed to compiling complete textbooks of all related languages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎨 For many years, I have taken part in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://moedict.tw&quot;&gt;“MoeDict”&lt;/a&gt; project in the g0v community to build an online dictionary that integrates Taiwan’s multiple languages. I believe that the spirit of Common Voice and MoeDict is the spirit of an “inclusive cultural affirmation” through digital tools and open materials.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as everyone works together, every language in Taiwan can become the “common voice” of everyone in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">As long as everyone works together, every language in Taiwan can become the &quot;common voice&quot; of everyone in the future.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/ebf0c4a4e08f1c27cb0622ab416e3fbb77138b75.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Can Dongsha Island open up ecotourism? Participants suggested opening from the boat dive</title><link href="/en/blog/%E6%9D%B1%E6%B2%99%E5%B3%B6%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E7%94%9F%E6%85%8B%E6%97%85%E9%81%8A-%E8%88%87%E6%9C%83%E8%80%85%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E5%BE%9E%E8%88%B9%E5%AE%BF%E6%BD%9B%E6%B0%B4%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Can Dongsha Island open up ecotourism? Participants suggested opening from the boat dive" /><published>2018-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E6%9D%B1%E6%B2%99%E5%B3%B6%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E7%94%9F%E6%85%8B%E6%97%85%E9%81%8A%3F%E8%88%87%E6%9C%83%E8%80%85%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E5%BE%9E%E8%88%B9%E5%AE%BF%E6%BD%9B%E6%B0%B4%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E6%9D%B1%E6%B2%99%E5%B3%B6%E8%83%BD%E5%90%A6%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E7%94%9F%E6%85%8B%E6%97%85%E9%81%8A-%E8%88%87%E6%9C%83%E8%80%85%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E5%BE%9E%E8%88%B9%E5%AE%BF%E6%BD%9B%E6%B0%B4%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE/">&lt;p&gt;On August 6, 2018, the Ocean Commission opened a government liaison to promote the proposal &quot;Do Dongsha Island should open sightseeing?&quot;, through the collaborative meeting to understand the current situation of Dongsha Island and evaluate the open eco-tourism Feasibility. After the monthly meeting voted, the case became the topic of the collaborative meeting. On October 26, PDIS held a collaborative meeting with the IOC and the Ministry of the Interior in the Kaohsiung Sea Committee Office to discuss issues related to open tourism in Dongsha Island and further discuss possible ecology. Travel plan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;re-education-the-marine-department-has-assessed-the-dongsha-island-eco-tourism-plan&quot;&gt;Re-education, the Marine Department has assessed the Dongsha Island eco-tourism plan&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the Executive Yuan approved the &quot;Dongsha Atoll National Park Project&quot; in 2004 &lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /www.ndc.gov.tw/news_content.aspx?n=b750418c4dc9c700&amp;amp;sms=d7712d76e0354f54&amp;amp;s=cb0243579bebfbce&quot;&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt;, in the future, priority should be given to resource rehabilitation, monitoring and ecological research. After the re-education reaches certain results, consider promoting the follow-up ecology. Tourism and environmental education work; Dongsha Atoll National Park project book also established five years before the establishment of the conservation and re-cultivation period, temporarily not open the general public sightseeing, for resource investigation and research, environmental rehabilitation and related facilities planning and other management work After five years, based on the results of its management, it will assess whether to implement small-scale ecotourism and environmental education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017, the results of relevant surveys and monitoring show that the average atoll reef coverage in Dongsha is over 50%, the highest coverage rate has reached 80%, and the re-education has achieved certain results. Therefore, the Marine National Park Management Office began to evaluate the development of eco-tourism. The program was issued in 2009 and 2017 respectively. Professor Ou Shengrong presided over &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marine.gov.tw/filesys/dlarea/29/file2.pdf&quot;&gt;The Dongsha Atoll National Park Ecotourism Development Plan&lt;/a&gt; In the future, we will implement a total amount of control and develop a small and beautiful exquisite ecological journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motives for opening up eco-tourism include local re-education and development of eco-tourism, so that more people can understand the importance of local ecological conservation; after the opening of sightseeing, the increase of local tourists and eco-tourists can help to scare The problem of overfishing of local cross-border fishing vessels. At the same time, increasing domestic and foreign tourists through eco-tourism can increase China's influence in the South China Sea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the inventory of the issues, we found that many of the work including local facilities enhancement, eco-tourism, etc. are already in the planning of the Marine Department. How do you deal with these issues in this collaborative meeting? Through internal discussions, we have re-assured HMW Challange from the double-diamond image. &quot;How do we make domestic and foreign tourists understand the importance of ecological conservation in Dongsha under the goal of conserving local ecology or increasing the influence of the South China Sea? It is also assumed that &quot;open eco-tourism&quot; is a solution to focus on &quot;whether the current planned eco-tourism can meet ecological conservation or increase the influence of China's South China Sea&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a1ed0902e980d88dc03684de69c147752092ddec.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Moderator report meeting topic &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;to-develop-eco-tourism-it-is-necessary-to-improve-the-construction-of-the-island-and-improve-relevant-regulations&quot;&gt;To develop eco-tourism, it is necessary to improve the construction of the island and improve relevant regulations.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the meeting, IOC pointed out that Huang Huanghui, the chairman of the IOC, was asked by an interview with the Central News Agency. The ocean is as public money as the sun, the air and the water. Everyone should abandon their selfishness and let the public money work the most. I hope that we can plan to let the relatives of the East and Nansha garrisons go to the island to visit relatives and open short-term leisure sightseeing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Marine Park Management Office of the Ministry of the Interior of the Ministry of the Interior pointed out that the distance between Dongsha Island and Hong Kong and Shantou is closer than that of Taiwan. In the past, there were often mainland iron-shell vessels crossing the border to catch fish. Hong Kong yachts also dive to this place. . There are many special species in Dongsha Island, such as coral reef ecology, F. striata, sharp-toothed lemon shark, and ferocious round crab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3d22d6830c4b8360ccb4e9bff7e623dd05552d4c.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Sea Management Office indicates the location of Dongsha Island &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At present, there is a civil aircraft in Dongsha Island that can carry 70 people every week. The military aircraft only has one shift per month. The main purpose is to let the officers and staff on the island use the upper and lower islands; the materials needed by the officers and staff on the island , necessities and related facilities, equipment parts, all by the ship to be replenished, although the ship can travel to the periphery of the atoll, but because the water depth in the atoll is relatively shallow, it is still necessary to rely on the platform ship to connect to Dongsha Island Pier. The maximum amount of energy that can be replenished now is 17 tanks per voyage, including some low-temperature refrigerated containers. In order to strengthen the local transportation, the maritime patrol office hopes to dredge a channel, but it may have some impact on local species, and the patrol station is further evaluating it. Under the premise of functional compatibility and ecological load capacity, the Marine Management Department hopes to make Dongsha a sustainable ecological island with high quality recreational service quality. The whole development strategy hopes to improve the existing island on the principle of low impact development. Facilities, improve the living functions of the island. In the short-term, a professional agency will be entrusted with the task of eco-tourism. Participants can participate in activities such as planting corals, alien species removal, clean beaches, environmental education experiences, stargazing, etc., and hope to use ecological experience and work holiday mode. To expand the number of service people and the number of people to prepare for the development of medium and long-term; the short-term part is set to the trial period, which is about three years; the medium-range is to expand from the land to the waters, providing more recreational experience. It includes various experiences such as diving, underwater photography and boat diving. In the long-term part, we hope to promote the entire Dongsha Island to quality recreation and service quality, innovative island landscape and sustainable island development. The projects that can be developed include international sailing and boarding. Diving, glass boat experience, semi-submarine and beach activities can be used to plan offshore floating islands, develop underwater bicycles, water walks and more. However, the development of eco-tourism may face some problems. In order to develop eco-tourism, it is necessary to set control of carrying capacity, assessment indicators of eco-tourism, and set up permanent monitoring areas. At the same time, it is also necessary to properly separate the scope of ecological protection and provide a range of recreation. After the relevant regulations are finalized, a professional manufacturer is required to handle it, and the facilities on the island need to be continuously improved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taiwan Yacht Industry Association shares the way of yacht eco-tourism. They point out that the yacht itself is a self-sufficient vehicle and tool. It is recommended that the Dongsha eco-tourism can be operated by yachting and diving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the issue is clarified, ecologists hope that the relevant public sector information of the conference will be made publicly known to the public. After discussion, it is suggested that the Marine Department can raise the &quot;draft&quot; and then disclose the relevant information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-issue-is-clarified-focusing-on-the-supporting-measures-of-eco-tourism-in-dongsha-island&quot;&gt;The issue is clarified, focusing on the supporting measures of eco-tourism in Dongsha Island&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many reefs near Dongsha Island. If there is no light map of the relevant waters, it is likely to hit the rocks. Unfortunately, this information is a business secret. He hopes to make effective use of this information to make the local boat safer. He also shares that the local area is affected by the northeast monsoon and may be more suitable for sightseeing from May to September.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another teacher shared that before Boracay was over-loaded due to excessive cruising, it caused the island to reopen after half a year and restricted the activities of many related activities. It is suggested that Dongsha Island should be targeted at climate change changes. The assessment of the detailed areas and seasons will be better for the future sustainable management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/83e76428f878c3e03eb6bfdf719eaf1d1da9dd80.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The host confirms the facts and clarifies the dispute &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the boat dive, some participants suggested that five to ten boat dive boats can be opened and operated at the same time. You can go to Kaohsiung Port to pick up dive tourists, board the ship and go to Dongsha for recreation. The Kaohsiung City Government also expressed its support for the view of the Yacht Association. You can test it out to Dongsha for boating and diving. The Kaohsiung City Government pointed out that Dongsha Island is a good diving spot. In addition, Taiwan's yacht manufacturing quality is very high. If it is used for boat diving, it will also help Taiwan's yacht industry. The Kaohsiung City Government suggested that Dongsha Island could be used to set up a project to pilot a dive in Dongsha Island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kaohsiung City Government also shared that there are currently two private yacht marinas in Kaohsiung City. Currently, the operation is already on track. The equipment at the terminal is sufficient for use, and it is hoped that the test of boarding and diving will be carried out as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some participants are worried about the opening of eco-tourism. Some people reminded that if the planning and management personnel do not know how to do eco-tourism, there will be great risks. For example, due to improper wastewater treatment, the waste village of Sipadan Island in Malaysia. It has also been shared that many foreign open diving places have charges in addition to the total amount of control. For example, some national parks collect ecological taxes, and the funds are earmarked for local ecological conservation. When ships enter, they will see the number of tons of restrictions. The ecologists attending the meeting pointed out that in some places, the strength of citizen scientists will be introduced to conduct regular physical examinations of coral reefs, and it will be closed when coral reefs are in poor condition. Some participants also said that they should refer to the concept of &quot;no trace of mountains and forests&quot;, let professional guides do eco-guided, commentary, and guide tourists to bring back their own garbage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/ea4e0e29ac2d182c8bd922402fcc6717433d2e1a.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Meeting discussion site &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the status of the Dongsha Island Lagoon, it is also the focus of discussion at the venue. The participating teachers shared that about 3 meters of lemon sharks return to the lagoon every year to produce small sharks, and there are also a large number of squids. The local area is a habitat where small sharks and squid can feed. This is an important highlight. . He mentioned that the circulation of the small lagoon is not very good. If there is a ship staying, or even a motorcycle on the water, there will be maintenance oil or related heavy oil, which will inevitably have a great impact. I hope to carefully evaluate the dredging. Action to avoid serious impact on the local area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Marine Department pointed out that in Dongsha, not only the lemon scorpion was seen around Dongsha Island, but also a lot of lemon mites were found in the outer atoll. However, the warships of the sea management department are that the iron-shell vessels in China, Vietnam and other places weigh 200, 300 tons, and use the bottom trawl in the local area to cause comminuted damage to the local coral reefs; Ships can't deal with these iron-hull ships, and it is difficult to board the ship, which is dangerous. Therefore, it may be necessary to make a certain degree of sacrifice to dredge the Dongsha waterway so that large ships can come in and park to prevent Chinese and Vietnamese fishing vessels from invading the border to protect the local ecological resources. The Marine Department said that the maritime patrol department has tried its best not to affect the ecological environment of the area. It hopes that the minimum space will be exchanged for future law enforcement energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the strengthening of local hardware facilities, the Marine Management Office said that only the new tourist center, sewage treatment plant and waste disposal site are planned, which is necessary for the development of eco-tourism and the maintenance of the ecological environment of Dongsha Island. .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tourism industry suggests that in the future, it is possible to tie a public anchor ball in a place with high stability and suitable for diving, so as to avoid damage to the coral reef when the ship is docked for diving. They also mentioned that when they traveled to the local area in the future. If we see that Chinese fishing boats cross the border, they will be reflected to the patrol agency to assist the maritime patrol department in law enforcement and reduce the burden on the patrol station. However, they believe that the Ministry of Defence's current 45-day review period for personnel going to Dongsha may be too long, which may be a big limitation and needs to be adjusted. The Ministry of National Defense responded that the matter needs to be reported to the chief to see if there is a chance to adjust in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-discussion-suggesting-to-increase-marine-conservation-energy&quot;&gt;Group discussion, suggesting to increase marine conservation energy&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the morning discussion, the afternoon will be divided into two groups for group discussion on the topic of whether the current planned ecotourism can meet ecological conservation. . In order to train the official colleagues to learn the hosting skills, this group discussion was chaired by the CDD colleagues and assisted by the PDIS members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After discussion, the first group believes that the management regulations can be made more sound in the future unified issuance of the sea management office, and eco-tourism can take into account the needs of ecological conservation; in addition, it can also benefit from some indigenous people. How to get along with nature. Although participants strongly recommended planning ecotourism from the area of ​​boat dive, it is difficult to manage the boat diving at the sea management office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/5/508e98724d451ff4cbb7619580698debd7d29885.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second group talks about the problem of diving insurance, because there is currently no insurance for diving activities in the country. Although there is insurance to bring to the diving, it is handled in the post-delivery, not for diving. Insurance. In the aspect of overfishing, the second group believes that after 2000, with the assistance of sea patrols and sea pipes, there are still many fishing boats crossing the border, but the situation of overfishing has been reduced a lot. He felt that the problem of overfishing should be removed. The second group also mentioned the problem of local garbage and conservation. If it is to clean up the floating garbage on the sea, it needs to take a boat. The cost is much higher than the removal of garbage on land. However, the allocation of funds may be averaged, resulting in insufficient funds. It is difficult to achieve marine conservation. The second group also specifically discussed the issue of local 4G signal enhancements, suggesting that it can be enhanced using satellite mobile phones. The IOC finally shared that in 2000, after the establishment of the Sea Guard, the deployment of maritime energy in Dongsha was carried out. The situation of over-fishing has been greatly improved. At present, it has already had a deterrent effect under long-term law enforcement. The patrol agency believes that the ship lodgers can assist in photographing, searching for evidence and assisting the maritime patrol department in carrying out relevant enforcement. However, there are still insufficient funds. The sea patrol agency pointed out that the plastic waste in the ocean can only be cracked and cannot be decomposed. After the shellfish or fish are eaten by eating, they will enter the food chain and may be eaten by high-end fish or humans, which has a great impact. &quot;Although the fish does not have Voting rights, but we must pay attention to it.&quot; In the future, the IOC will build a marine fund to maintain and conserve the marine environment through the establishment of the Ocean Sustainability Management Fund in accordance with the Basic Law of the Sea. After a full day of discussion, Tang Feng’s political committee reported the results of today’s discussion at the government meeting next week, allowing the president and relevant heads of the ministry to serve as a reference for future governance and policy planning. [Question Manual] related to the issue (https://docs.google.com/document/d/1S2SWMqjaiz2rmMj83t2P0eRLPcwOIo1dWRv456_SbL0/edit), &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kzr-i_u=/&quot;&gt;Mind Map&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-10-26-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba% 9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac%e5%9b%9b%e5%8d%81%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94% e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;verbatem record&lt;/a&gt; will also be made available on the Internet for the public to understand the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kzR-I_U=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/40fe786bcfb4703d03b698e1fd89659c189ceba6.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Tang Feng political commissar summary &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-small-table-is-performing-well-and-the-interested-people-can-have-more-yuan&quot;&gt;The small table is performing well, and the interested people can have more yuan&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is mentioned that some important figures of the ministry today did not attend, such as the relevant contractors of the Ministry of National Defense, resulting in Some of the issues were put on hold; some participants pointed out that some participants still stayed on land planning and could not understand the thinking of ocean recreation. They should let other participants experience the boat diving and discuss it in order to discuss the specific situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some participants felt that the CDC colleagues who served as the table chief performed well. Sometimes the discussion was divergent. The table leader would still assist in pulling back and clarifying the opinions to be expressed. The relevant plans would also be included to assist in the discussion. Focus. The form of the mind map can also help you to think comprehensively, but unfortunately there is no Action Item, it is difficult to draw conclusions in a short time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The official colleagues pointed out that in fact, some discussions have been predicted before the meeting, and all the things that these different stakeholders have considered need to be included in the discussion. However, it is now in the feasibility assessment, and the opinions of this collaborative meeting can be incorporated into some subsequent adjustments, and some psychological preparations for the future can be done. However, he also reminded that the yacht operators themselves are very concerned about safety. However, in the position of the public authorities, not everyone is concerned about safety. Some operators are not high enough to enter the threshold and may not be responsible for safety. This may be appropriate when discussing. Clarify the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was pointed out that only the ship-seekers were found this time. As a result, the discussion direction will be easy to focus on the eco-tourism plan for boat dive; perhaps it is also possible to think about whether there are more interested parties, such as eco-operators. Wait, let more opinions come together for discussion.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">On October 26th, PDIS held a collaborative meeting with the IOC and the Ministry of the Interior in the Kaohsiung Seas Committee Office to discuss issues related to the opening of Dongsha Island and further discuss possible ecotourism programs. Participants suggested that ecotourism could be opened from boat dive.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/5/508e98724d451ff4cbb7619580698debd7d29885.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: When the rain is not first, the appropriate time</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%99%82%E9%9B%A8%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%88-%E9%81%A9%E7%95%B6%E5%85%B6%E6%99%82/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: When the rain is not first, the appropriate time" /><published>2018-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%99%82%E9%9B%A8%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%88,%E9%81%A9%E7%95%B6%E5%85%B6%E6%99%82</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%99%82%E9%9B%A8%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%88-%E9%81%A9%E7%95%B6%E5%85%B6%E6%99%82/">&lt;p&gt;During the UN General Assembly in New York in September this year, I met a friend who could almost be described as “legendary”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👩 Her name is Mariéme Jamme. She is founder of the British iamtheCODE organization, a social enterprise that supports young women to study programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⛈ Why did Mariéme set up this organization? She was born in the countryside of Senegal. When she was 13 years old, she was smuggled into Paris by a trafficker and was sexually exploited. When she was 15 years old, she was arrested by the police. Because she did not have an opportunity to receive an education, she could hardly read or write until she was 16 years old, and could only do low-level manual labor to survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📖 Not wishing to surrender to her fate, she ensconced herself in the public library, memorized dictionaries, read encyclopaedias, and even self-studied spreadsheets and programming language. Step by step, she has become the person she is today, and has received the affirmation by the Gates Foundation and the UNICEF Annual Innovation Award.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💻 In 2016, she founded iamtheCODE to help other girls and young women like herself regain the control of their lives away from the hands of misfortune.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👓 Mariéme has told me a little story. This year, when she was holding a hackathon in Liverpool, England, among the attendees was a young girl who never took off her glasses and did not say a word. When Mariéme spoke to her, she found out that the girl had been bullied because of her gender identity. Eventually, this shy girl succeeded in developing a community-assisted platform for anti-bullying in 2 days and 24 hours of hackathon and established self-affirmation and resistance to bullying in collaboration with other children who did not appear “mainstream.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏡 This little story reminds me of the “Social Enterprise World Forum” conference in Edinburgh in early September. There are also two similar scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👂 Howard Weinstein, founder of Solar Ear, started in Africa and developed a solar-powered hearing aids. He hired hearing impaired people to lead the production process and produce equipment that suits their needs; the MIT Laboratory and Baan Dek Foundation launched the “Digital Super Hero Academy” (DSHA) because they saw that vulnerable children in South Asia lacked critical thinking and social stimulation about their living environment. Therefore, they worked with the local social workers to develop an interactive teaching kit so that these children can pick up practical life skills quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌱 I think these stories all reflect the implicit meaning of “appropriate technology”: it is not so much about using “advanced and innovative technology” to “rescue” people in need of help; rather, it is about enabling the other party to “master” the tools, starting from their own needs and enabling them to improve their lives, just as Mariéme was able to transform her life by learning spreadsheet and programming language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌍 “Our goal is to train one million female programmers in developing countries such as Africa, the Middle East and South America by 2030”, Mariéme told me resolutely. I think that the shy girl must have been one of them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">During the UN General Assembly in September this year, I met a friend in New York who could almost describe it as a &quot;legend&quot;.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dd5164b6b018cbb27d2782ab6542d501c8f7788f.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Who gets the guide from democracy?</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%BE%9E%E8%AA%B0%E5%BE%97%E6%8C%87%E5%8D%97/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Who gets the guide from democracy?" /><published>2018-09-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-09-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%BE%9E%E8%AA%B0%E5%BE%97%E6%8C%87%E5%8D%97%3F</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%BE%9E%E8%AA%B0%E5%BE%97%E6%8C%87%E5%8D%97/">&lt;p&gt;As the election approaches, more and more related discussions are taking place. They remind me of my experience as a first time voter at the age of 21.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗳 In that year, a young man near our home staunchly emerged to challenge the long-serving incumbent village chief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our young friend was unafraid of the incumbent and offered some refreshing political views. He convinced me decide to use my very first vote to support his courage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 Unexpectedly, this young man won the election by one vote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opponent refused to accept the vote. However, this did not alter the outcome of the election. Thus, for the first time in Chih Nan Village, there was a new village chief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏁 When I saw the data after the deadline of the election registration, I think that had my friend been running for election now, he might be shocked by the intensity of the election. According to the statistics of the Central Committee, there are nearly 30,000 candidates vying for more than 10,000 elected places, including municipal mayors, municipal councilors, urban village chiefs, mountain aboriginal district chiefs and district resident representatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔍 How do we find the right person in this vast sea of people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This question is exactly what gnv “Vote Taiwan Voting Guide” project sponsor, Johnny (Luo Jincheng), has been pondering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎲 Johnny said that when he was young, he had no idea how to figure out the difference between legislators and members. He voted in accordance with his mother’s opinion, which “seems like a waste of our hard-won democracy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stemming from this doubt, Johnny began to categorize the relevant public information and used data and source code for free open access, allowing everyone to work together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔢 When you click on the voting guide website, you can see, in addition to the candidate’s political views, information about the candidate’s personal property declarations, political contributions, and even their voting and proposal records during their past tenure. Everything is available at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In both the 2014 and 2016 elections for the legislature and legislators’ elections, Johnny had launched the “Voting Guide”. This year is the third time that he has launched the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📈 After integrating and structuring, these precious materials are shared by Internet users. In the last two elections, up to 400,000 people had used them in the month prior to the election day. This demonstrates that the demand for such materials in Taiwan’s society is extremely high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is gratifying to see that this year the project has received the support of the g0v Citizenship Science and Technology Innovation Award and the Kindle Citizen Platform. They have strengthened the design and publicity of the existing foundation. Even people who are not familiar with citizen technology can use it beneficially. Their cooperative experience is undoubtedly another example of social innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙋 Johnny said on the website, “Even if a democratic system is a good system, it must still have some shortcoming somewhere.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think what the voting guide has supplemented is a “political resume”. It is like a compass that helps us find a reliable candidate, similar to the way I voted for the youthful chief candidate all those years ago.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">The voting guide may be supplemented by the &quot;political resume&quot;. It is like a compass, helping us find a trustworthy candidate, just as I voted for the young chief candidate.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6da4e52684f8769ebca1b18ddfe725b918a9dd4c.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Dancing with Autonomous Vehicles</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Dancing with Autonomous Vehicles" /><published>2018-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E/">&lt;p&gt;On weekends, I like to visit Jian Guo Weekend Flower Market near my home. When I saw people struggling to go to the parking lot with a flowerpot, or when they were standing under the burning sun trying to wave down a ride, I was always thinking: Is there a more convenient way?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚦 This is not news; there are many cars and motorcycles in Taiwan. According to Environmental Protection Administration’s statistics, there are more than 13 million motorcycles in Taiwan, with an average of 380 per square kilometer, ranking number one in Asia. There are nearly 8 million cars as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Taiwan is crowded with cars, which has a significant impact on the air quality and road traffic safety in the city. How can we improve the situation? Autonomous vehicles are a possible solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚲 Before I joined the cabinet in 2016, I discussed the development of unmanned vehicles with friends from MIT Media Lab in Paris. After joining the cabinet, I also suggested that they use the Social Innovation Lab as a venue for hackathon, so that the “Smart Tricycle” could interact with the general public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 What is special about the “Smart Tricycle”? Through open source and open data, it enables Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Collective Intelligence (CI) to strengthen each other and explore new ways of interaction together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🛣 At present, many people still have doubts about unmanned vehicles. In my opinion, they are just like new species. Now when we are on the road, we estimate other vehicles’ intentions based on their signals and the way they drive. Autonomous vehicles can receive nearby signals through the Internet of Vehicles, allowing them to use the road more intelligently. Vehicle sensors can also collect nearby traffic information. Not only can you learn the traffic information on your own, it can also help the city understand you better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🐎 Human beings will inevitably encounter challenges when learning to coexist with such new species. The most important thing at this stage is to set up an experiment site, allowing unmanned vehicles to simulate the actual situation freely inside the site. I used to visit the GoMentum experiment site in California. When I was looking at the unmanned vehicles in the venue, it felt like I was surrounded by animals, and they could interact with people to find out the possibility of future operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏙 Therefore, I look forward to the completion of the construction of Tainan Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City, which has already started. In the 2.2-hectare Tainan Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City, in addition to a special test field, there would be a control center from which the action of the vehicles could be observed. Imagine: When you entered Shalun Smart Green Energy Science City, the cars that were passing by you, or even the car you got on at the entrance were all unmanned vehicles, and the entire Science City could become an experiment site for vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From carriages to cars, every evolution of transportation has reshaped our society. By the time that Artificial Intelligence became a part of the city, our daily life would change. For example, after visiting Jian Guo Weekend Flower Market, when you pressed a button, the “Smart Tricycle” would help take the flowerpot home. I look forward to this day.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">When I saw people struggling to go to the parking lot with a pot, or when they were parked with a big sun, I was always thinking: Is there any more convenient possibility?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f6d7a369567dd01fa82c40d4de1b219b8d0b0c43.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How does TV join the earthquake bulletin? Collaborative meeting spelling out possible solutions</title><link href="/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E8%A6%96%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%9C%B0%E9%9C%87%E9%80%9F%E5%A0%B1-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%8B%BC%E5%87%BA%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How does TV join the earthquake bulletin? Collaborative meeting spelling out possible solutions" /><published>2018-07-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E8%A6%96%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%9C%B0%E9%9C%87%E9%80%9F%E5%A0%B1%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%8B%BC%E5%87%BA%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E8%A6%96%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%9C%B0%E9%9C%87%E9%80%9F%E5%A0%B1-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%8B%BC%E5%87%BA%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95/">&lt;p&gt;On July 27, 2018, the PDIS team and the relevant ministry held a &quot;compulsory full TV channel to join the &quot;Earthquake Express&quot; message for instant broadcast broadcast function] at the NCC venue (https://join.gov Collaborative meeting in the case of .tw/idea/detail/1909a9d2-7e4e-4e3a-9380-d35c5d1ba2de).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case was filed on February 8, 2018 by the friend Dynasty. In the proposal copy, he pointed out that although there are mobile phones that immediately broadcast the function of earthquake warnings, there are still problems such as unsupported mobile phones and signals, which may cause mobile phones to receive earthquake information; TV is the second largest contact for Taiwanese people. The media needs to add the &quot;Earth Shock&quot; feature to all TV channels. He also cites the example. At present, some news channel media in Taiwan have cooperated with the Central Meteorological Bureau to cooperate with the &quot;Earthquake Express&quot; message to broadcast the function. It is hoped that the media will be added to the &quot;Earthquake Express&quot; to broadcast the broadcast function through the regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although this proposal did not reach the threshold of 5,000 people, because of the important issues, after the recommendation of the China Development Association, the vote at the monthly meeting became the topic of the collaborative meeting. In order to understand this topic, the PDIS team conducted pre-existing data collection and interviews with various ministries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0501dceb4bbb80b9ff3daba8233d81dfd37c9b6e.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Collaborative meeting site &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;unlike-the-japanese-environment-the-earthquake-quick-report-is-difficult&quot;&gt;Unlike the Japanese environment, the earthquake quick report is difficult&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The earthquake quick report is not a way to predict the imminent earthquake, but the &quot;shock wave&quot; information transmitted through the earthquake, through the Internet or Radio waves, etc., the speed of transmission is faster than the &quot;shock wave&quot;, and the earthquake in the area where &quot;Shenbo&quot; has not arrived is notified. However, when the seismograph detects a relatively fast P-wave to the time the alarm is emitted, the range of S-wave movement with a large destructive force and a slow moving speed is called a dead zone. If there is a large truck passing near the seismograph, and explosives are required for construction, the seismograph may be mistaken for an earthquake. Therefore, the current standard for sending quick reports is usually that multiple seismographs detect the earthquake at the same time. Alerts, in terms of accuracy and immediacy, the blind zone will be expanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, Taiwan's environment is also a major obstacle to earthquake prediction. The earthquake in Japan will occur in the trench next to it. The earthquake is relatively large and there is a distance from Japan. However, in Taiwan, many seismic belts are at the foot, and at the same time, Taiwan has a small area, so the earthquake quick report is worse than Japan. However, there are many TV stations that have contacted the Central Meteorological Bureau to provide a quick earthquake report to the Central Meteorological Bureau in order to provide services for people to listen to earthquakes, and to broadcast an instant earthquake report on the news station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fire Department of the Ministry of the Interior has planned another way to broadcast disaster warning videos: in the event of a major disaster, each platform vendor will send a signal from the central government to request the on-board box to turn to public view; at the same time, public view can broadcast disaster prevention announcements. The information is displayed so that people in front of the TV can see it. On September 21, 2017, the Fire Department of the Ministry of the Interior has asked the operators to cooperate with the test in a manual manner. On September 21, 2018, the message service platform (MSP) will be sent to the platform and the public. View, automate the test of how this message is published. However, the current fire department's information service platform has not been connected to the Meteorological Bureau's earthquake report, and it is unable to automatically forward the earthquake report. The public TV is still in contact with the weather bureau to discuss the possibility of the earthquake report. At present, further discussion may be needed. Problems with other solutions. Therefore, this collaborative meeting will focus on how to use the TV media to make more channels for receiving quick reports, making it easier for the news to be transmitted to the public. Before the meeting, the PDIS team also worked with various ministries to write &lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /docs.google.com/document/d/10_sim536djo6eno1pswvozvuu5ce2casiztuxqyiacu/edit&quot;&gt;issue manual&lt;/a&gt; to allow participants to refer to it before the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vTq_1kt9FJTTFJdYnDNxhEmR1Y3aupImaUXAPnMEgIKi2ki1JuET-1yRZnCQ9dgDyQQeCe0E9nz79F0/pub?embedded=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/2/24de24c38c44910d3e605bb31e2dcb07eb83c4eb.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Interested people and related relationships &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;proposer-and-ministry-report-spelling-out-the-views-of-different-stakeholders&quot;&gt;Proposer and Ministry report, spelling out the views of different stakeholders&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the July 27th collaborative meeting, the sponsor stated that his proposal was motive in February 2018 On the 4th earthquake, after the earthquake, the sponsor saw an alarm on TV and found a pipeline with a TV bulletin. The proponent pointed out that there are currently six news media in Taiwan, but the form and sound specifications are not uniform. It is recommended to be unified so that everyone can reflect on &quot;this is an earthquake.&quot; The proposer also suggested that the background of the card could be transparent to avoid interfering with the picture or to reduce the picture to avoid interfering with the message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/91f449Ro3kM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of the Interior pointed out that there are currently six TV stations broadcast by the station, such as Dongsen, Sanli, TVBS, Zhongshi, Zhongtian, and Daai. The format of the six TV stations is not consistent. Although the conditions, requirements, and materials of the wave are all provided by the Meteorological Bureau, the presentation methods cannot be unified. The Ministry of the Interior said that the relevant laws and regulations involved in this case include the TV broadcasting law, the cable radio and television law, the cable radio and television system operators disasters and emergency response measures, but the relevant mechanisms, expropriation and operation mechanisms need to be further clarified. The Ministry of the Interior pointed out that the entire government's disaster prevention and control system is quite complex. It is necessary to divide into three levels: front-level mitigation, post-settlement and post-surgical recovery: central level, county level, and township level. Therefore, the meeting will be co-sponsored by the Ministry of the Interior, NCC and the Ministry of Communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NCC, the current TV channels are divided into satellite broadcasters and wireless TV. Satellite broadcasters can transmit signals to satellites or MOD operators via satellite to transmit channel content to users. Wireless TVs are divided into several types. One is to transmit signals through wireless TV relay stations, and the viewers buy a set- The top box can be viewed by connecting to the TV; another wireless station that must be loaded or contracted with cable TV can also be seen on the cable TV; the other is that the mobile communication network of CBS is received by the mobile phone. NCC said that the current disaster prevention laws and related laws and regulations do not mandate that the passers-by must be connected to the network of disaster prevention and control units, mainly because the industry has spontaneously signed a letter of intent for cooperation with the Elephant Bureau. At present, there is only one TV in the TV, and others. There are five Weiguang companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, NCC pointed out that there is a regulatory suspicion that forces all TV channels to automatically broadcast disaster prevention messages. The radio and television three laws authorize the main points of the natural disaster emergency requisition channel. This part is the propaganda of post-disaster disasters. Like SARS and dengue fever, the channels levied should broadcast the content of the disaster prevention unit. In the procedure, the disaster prevention and defense unit first sends an application for requisition to the general meeting, and then the communication will review and requisition the channel, and the designated television and broadcasting operators will stop broadcasting the program and broadcast the disaster prevention information. Articles 27 and 31 of the Disaster Prevention Law respectively transmit disaster warning messages or set up a response center before the disaster, and use the media to collect and transmit disaster information during and after the disaster. According to the regulations, it is a pre-, post-, and post-event. Dissemination of disaster prevention information. However, in the earthquake quick report, due to the emergency response center when the earthquake rapid report occurred, the relevant regulations may have doubts and need to be dealt with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Meteorological Bureau pointed out that after the disaster prevention and alerting cell broadcasting system was launched in 2016, people's mobile phones could receive messages. In the same year, Dongsen TV station actively visited the Meteorological Bureau, hoping that when the earthquake occurred, I hoped that the picture could be covered. In this way, people can simultaneously get the news of the earthquake bulletin. After discussion, after the TV station made equipment purchase and system construction, in August 2016, the Meteorological Bureau signed a cooperation contract with Dongsen TV, and the Meteorological Bureau began to provide the information of the Dongsen TV Express. Followed by other TV stations to discuss cooperation with the Meteorological Bureau.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Meteorological Bureau said that the content of the entire screen is provided by the Meteorological Bureau, and the way of the screen overlay, the sound of the reminder or the duration of the time. The Meteorological Bureau respects the ideas and ideas of the design of each TV station. It does not force a certain amount of time or how the entire screen is displayed. However, some meteorological bureaus in the text hope that everyone is consistent, so the text is provided by the Meteorological Administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-issue-is-clarified-and-the-current-known-issues-are-discussed-in-depth&quot;&gt;The issue is clarified, and the current known issues are discussed in depth.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the issue is clarified, the National Earthquake Center shares that the National Earthquake Center has cooperated with the Ministry of Education to establish a compound earthquake in the small and medium-sized countries. Quick report system. The compound seismic quick report system combines the Earthquake Administration's earthquake report and the local earthquake detection mechanism to detect nearby earthquakes through self-built seismometers. Guozheng Center said that the case is also included in the forward-looking plan and hopes to have opportunities to promote it to other fields in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Channel operators are worried that if they use the TV to publish earthquake news, I am afraid that the audience will stay in front of the TV and miss the opportunity to escape. The Disaster Prevention Office explained that the current direction of the government is to promote a multi-dimensional earthquake notification notification mechanism, which is the mechanism of &quot;multi-modal notification&quot;, which is also adopted by many countries. Not only TV, but also through various channels to let everyone know that &quot;the earthquake wave is about to arrive&quot;, so that everyone can act quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dongsen TV shared that Dongsen News has set up a complete set of SOPs after receiving the earthquake report. How to deal with the anchor, how to do the pilot control, and what actions the editor has, have established a fixed process. . After the news station was built, the top management also wanted to expand, so it may be launched at Dongsen Finance. However, an assessment found that Dongsen Finance Station will do live broadcast of Taiwan lottery lottery from 8:30 to 9:00 every night. If the earthquake is being reported when the ball is ran out, will it be questioned by the fans? Sex? At the same time, each time you build such a system, it costs about 6.7 million. If each one is built, it will cost tens of millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a midday break, the afternoon group discussion focused on &quot;How to make a TV earthquake report&quot;, including what happens when a false positive occurs? How to improve the speed of the quick report? Is there any other way to provide earthquake quick news services other than TV stations?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cefe13fe0a8de71c30fdc0732003b78e51073d83.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-discussion-looking-for-possible-solutions&quot;&gt;Group discussion, looking for possible solutions&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After discussion, the earthquake quick report on TV is divided into two parts, one is the channel industry push, and the other is the system industry forced transfer. In terms of channel operators, small TV stations may not be able to afford the relevant costs, need to increase equipment, or provide incentives to encourage TV station interface. If the system operators force the transfer, they will also face the problem that the small platform is difficult to interface. After the transfer, they may also be protested by the channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The system industry has forced the turntable part of the exercise, but there is no automation between the MSP and the meteorological bureau. There is no private network between the MSP operators. The fire department is worried that it may take too much time and need to do more tests. Confirm that it takes time. The second group suggests that the information reception of the set-top box can refer to the cell broadcast mechanism on the mobile phone, and the NCDR directly throws the earthquake report to the platform operator. The second group also proposes another way. You can refer to the method of primary and secondary schools. The Meteorological Bureau only sends the epicenter, then sends the epicenter and scale, saves the calculation time, and calculates the shock wave scale and arrival time by the set-top box. This will speed up the transfer. In the information transmission, the application of the Central Meteorological Administration is installed at the head end of each platform. The information is directly transmitted from the head end to the set-top box, and then the on-board box performs operations on its own location. However, Cathy clarified that the current set-top box may be difficult to provide such a computer system, and if other instructions are in progress, it may affect the calculation process. However, in the future, technology will change with each passing day, and there may be such a computer system in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the aspect of false positives, the anchor can be corrected in a verbal manner, and a marquee can be added. The time for clarification should be as fast as possible, and mechanisms should be established to coordinate the mechanisms for finding problems afterwards. In addition, let the public know that false positives are normal, and internal parties should also exercise clarification mechanisms for false positives and respond as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you let the people know how to take refuge after the TV message? First of all, the voice should be unified, and it should not cause panic among the people. It is also necessary to know how to take refuge through the education and training of primary and secondary schools. Since some disabled people may not see it, the sound transmission needs to be discussed to allow the visually impaired to respond quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/46b206867e6926d0f1f63f45a1d6273be38a5668.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other aspects of the rapid earthquake reporting pipeline, in addition to broadcasting in primary and secondary schools, towns and villages, you can also consider using air raid warnings or the police department's broadcasts; in addition, the disaster prevention industry can also be encouraged to do related activities. Pick up. At the end of the meeting, Tang Feng’s political commissar summed up, “Today is really like a jigsaw puzzle. Everyone brainstorms.” She explained, “Now is the stage of feasibility assessment, so don’t worry about getting it right now.” The future It will be assessed by the Ministry of the Interior which programs are feasible and which are not feasible, and openly respond to netizens on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the gathering of the conference, these opinions will be reported to the Dean and relevant heads by the Tang Feng political commissar at the next week's government meeting as a reference for follow-up decision-making; [The Agenda Handbook] at the meeting (https:/ /docs.google.com/document/d/10_sIM536djO6EnO1PsWvozvuu5CE2caSizTUXQYIacU/edit), &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kz_sp_s=/&quot;&gt;Mind Map&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit. pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-07-27-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1 %e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac%e4%b8%89%e5%8d%81%e4%ba%94%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6 relevant information such as %9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;verbatim&lt;/a&gt; will also be published on the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz_SP_s=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f7e1ae9d668e42696f487af03aaf865adf156a47.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Meeting summary report status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;collaborative-meeting-to-build-consensus-from-the-bottom-up-civil-servants-are-expected-to-learn-new-methods&quot;&gt;Collaborative meeting to build consensus from the bottom up, civil servants are expected to learn new methods&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposer said that the topic is a professional issue, many things are not understood by the general public, relevant units Will know. According to his observation, today's meeting preparation is very sufficient. The issue manual integrates the regulations and helps a lot. However, when discussing, it will add new things, and it will take time to understand. The threshold is higher, although he listens. Understand, but it is recommended that people who do not understand can ask questions. In terms of venues, the proponents suggested that the logo could be strengthened in the future to facilitate participants to find the venue. The civil servants attending the meeting thought that many people had received public proposals from different channels. In the past, there was no such face-to-face, and many ministers participated in the discussion of the proposal. The Meteorological Bureau considered this a good model. It is not implemented as decided in the past. It has the opportunity to build consensus from the bottom up and know what can be done and what can't. Civil servants also believe that a neutral host is a necessary presence, which can reduce the feeling of confrontation, and also guide the collaborative meeting in a timely manner; the host team can also relieve the pressure of many public departments, such as the need to spend the issue manual A lot of time and energy, the public sector is difficult to do; but with this issue manual, you can have a more comprehensive view and help the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The civil servant pointed out that it is quite difficult to find a concrete and feasible solution, but through this discussion, it can be clarified which is not feasible and which can be tried. Some participants said that this meeting uses mental maps to present, which can help you understand the overall issue. There are also topic manuals to help you understand the topic and help you do your homework before the meeting. He laughed and said that the topic manual is &quot;the specification of the paper grade.&quot; However, there are also civil servants who believe that the mind map is unfamiliar. He has not learned to use the mind map during his growth, so he will be confused when using it. Although the mind map can quickly see the face of the issue, the traditional topic book help is still relatively large. But the civil servant also said that if there is an opportunity in the future, I hope that there will be more opportunities for the public sector to learn new ways of analyzing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f5db8caeef82c510a1b1c183d6a98c118a0f4e37.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Through the process of clarifying the collaborative meeting, participants suggested that the voices used in the TV earthquake report could be unified and that other ways of notifying the people to escape as soon as possible could be made.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f5db8caeef82c510a1b1c183d6a98c118a0f4e37.JPG" /></entry></feed>