<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2018-09-02T08:05:15+00:00</updated><id>/en/</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Dancing with unmanned vehicles</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Dancing with unmanned vehicles" /><published>2018-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E/">&lt;p&gt;At the weekend, I really like to visit Jianguo Flower Market near the residence. When I saw people struggling to go to the parking lot with a pot, or when they were parked with a big sun, I was always thinking: Is there any more convenient possibility?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚦 The large number of steam locomotives in Taiwan is no longer news. According to the statistics of the Environmental Protection Agency, there are more than 13 million locomotives in Taiwan, with an average of 380 vehicles per square kilometer, ranking the highest in Asia. Even cars have nearly 8 million vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Such a high-density vehicle has a significant impact on the air quality and traffic safety of the Taiwanese region. How can such problems be improved? Unmanned vehicles are a possible direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I entered the cabinet in 2016, I discussed the development of unmanned vehicles in Paris and friends at the MIT Media Lab. After entering the cabinet, I also suggested that they use the Air China Social Innovation Center as a venue for hackathon, so that the “Smart Tricycle” has the opportunity to interact with the general public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is special about the smart tricycle? Through open source and open materials, it enables Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Collective Intelligence (CI) to strengthen each other and explore new ways of interaction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, many people still have doubts about unmanned vehicles. In my opinion, they are actually like new species. Now we drive, by lighting the number and driving, to observe the intention of the next car. Unmanned vehicles can receive nearby signals through the Internet of Vehicles, allowing them to use the road more intelligently. The sensors on the vehicle can also collect traffic conditions in the vicinity. In addition to self-study, it can help the whole city to understand itself better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans are inevitably challenged by such new species in the process of learning to coexist. Being able to have an experimental site, let the unmanned vehicles test and simulate the actual situation inside, is the most important thing at this stage. I once went to the GoMentum test site in California to see the unmanned car in the venue. It felt like I was surrounded by animals and could interact with people to find out the possibility of future operations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, I have been looking forward to the Tainan Shalun Science City, which has already started. In the 2.2-hectare Tainan Sharon Science City, in addition to the special test field, the vehicle’s actions can also be observed from the control center. Imagine: After entering Sharon Science City, the passing cars, even from the entrance of the park, are all unmanned vehicles, and the entire Science City can become a vehicle experience field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the carriage to the car, every evolution of the vehicle has reshaped our society. By the time that artificial intelligence becomes a part of the city, our daily lives will change. For example, after visiting the Jianguo Flower Market, press a button, “Smart Tricycle” can help bring the pot home, I look forward to this day.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會創新" /><summary type="html">When I saw people struggling to go to the parking lot with a pot, or when they were parked with a big sun, I was always thinking: Is there any more convenient possibility?</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f6d7a369567dd01fa82c40d4de1b219b8d0b0c43.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How does TV join the earthquake bulletin? Collaborative meeting spelling out possible solutions</title><link href="/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E8%A6%96%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%9C%B0%E9%9C%87%E9%80%9F%E5%A0%B1-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%8B%BC%E5%87%BA%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How does TV join the earthquake bulletin? Collaborative meeting spelling out possible solutions" /><published>2018-07-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E8%A6%96%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%9C%B0%E9%9C%87%E9%80%9F%E5%A0%B1%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%8B%BC%E5%87%BA%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E8%A6%96%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E5%8A%A0%E5%85%A5%E5%9C%B0%E9%9C%87%E9%80%9F%E5%A0%B1-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%8B%BC%E5%87%BA%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95/">&lt;p&gt;On July 27, 2018, the PDIS team and the relevant ministry held a &quot;compulsory full TV channel to join the &quot;Earthquake Express&quot; message for instant broadcast broadcast function] at the NCC venue (https://join.gov Collaborative meeting in the case of .tw/idea/detail/1909a9d2-7e4e-4e3a-9380-d35c5d1ba2de).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case was filed on February 8, 2018 by the friend Dynasty. In the proposal copy, he pointed out that although there are mobile phones that immediately broadcast the function of earthquake warnings, there are still problems such as unsupported mobile phones and signals, which may cause mobile phones to receive earthquake information; TV is the second largest contact for Taiwanese people. The media needs to add the &quot;Earth Shock&quot; feature to all TV channels. He also cites the example. At present, some news channel media in Taiwan have cooperated with the Central Meteorological Bureau to cooperate with the &quot;Earthquake Express&quot; message to broadcast the function. It is hoped that the media will be added to the &quot;Earthquake Express&quot; to broadcast the broadcast function through the regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although this proposal did not reach the threshold of 5,000 people, because of the important issues, after the recommendation of the China Development Association, the vote at the monthly meeting became the topic of the collaborative meeting. In order to understand this topic, the PDIS team conducted pre-existing data collection and interviews with various ministries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0501dceb4bbb80b9ff3daba8233d81dfd37c9b6e.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Collaborative meeting site &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;unlike-the-japanese-environment-the-earthquake-quick-report-is-difficult&quot;&gt;Unlike the Japanese environment, the earthquake quick report is difficult&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The earthquake quick report is not a way to predict the imminent earthquake, but the &quot;shock wave&quot; information transmitted through the earthquake, through the Internet or Radio waves, etc., the speed of transmission is faster than the &quot;shock wave&quot;, and the earthquake in the area where &quot;Shenbo&quot; has not arrived is notified. However, when the seismograph detects a relatively fast P-wave to the time the alarm is emitted, the range of S-wave movement with a large destructive force and a slow moving speed is called a dead zone. If there is a large truck passing near the seismograph, and explosives are required for construction, the seismograph may be mistaken for an earthquake. Therefore, the current standard for sending quick reports is usually that multiple seismographs detect the earthquake at the same time. Alerts, in terms of accuracy and immediacy, the blind zone will be expanded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, Taiwan's environment is also a major obstacle to earthquake prediction. The earthquake in Japan will occur in the trench next to it. The earthquake is relatively large and there is a distance from Japan. However, in Taiwan, many seismic belts are at the foot, and at the same time, Taiwan has a small area, so the earthquake quick report is worse than Japan. However, there are many TV stations that have contacted the Central Meteorological Bureau to provide a quick earthquake report to the Central Meteorological Bureau in order to provide services for people to listen to earthquakes, and to broadcast an instant earthquake report on the news station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fire Department of the Ministry of the Interior has planned another way to broadcast disaster warning videos: in the event of a major disaster, each platform vendor will send a signal from the central government to request the on-board box to turn to public view; at the same time, public view can broadcast disaster prevention announcements. The information is displayed so that people in front of the TV can see it. On September 21, 2017, the Fire Department of the Ministry of the Interior has asked the operators to cooperate with the test in a manual manner. On September 21, 2018, the message service platform (MSP) will be sent to the platform and the public. View, automate the test of how this message is published. However, the current fire department's information service platform has not been connected to the Meteorological Bureau's earthquake report, and it is unable to automatically forward the earthquake report. The public TV is still in contact with the weather bureau to discuss the possibility of the earthquake report. At present, further discussion may be needed. Problems with other solutions. Therefore, this collaborative meeting will focus on how to use the TV media to make more channels for receiving quick reports, making it easier for the news to be transmitted to the public. Before the meeting, the PDIS team also worked with various ministries to write &lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /docs.google.com/document/d/10_sim536djo6eno1pswvozvuu5ce2casiztuxqyiacu/edit&quot;&gt;issue manual&lt;/a&gt; to allow participants to refer to it before the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vTq_1kt9FJTTFJdYnDNxhEmR1Y3aupImaUXAPnMEgIKi2ki1JuET-1yRZnCQ9dgDyQQeCe0E9nz79F0/pub?embedded=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/2/24de24c38c44910d3e605bb31e2dcb07eb83c4eb.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Interested people and related relationships &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;proposer-and-ministry-report-spelling-out-the-views-of-different-stakeholders&quot;&gt;Proposer and Ministry report, spelling out the views of different stakeholders&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the July 27th collaborative meeting, the sponsor stated that his proposal was motive in February 2018 On the 4th earthquake, after the earthquake, the sponsor saw an alarm on TV and found a pipeline with a TV bulletin. The proponent pointed out that there are currently six news media in Taiwan, but the form and sound specifications are not uniform. It is recommended to be unified so that everyone can reflect on &quot;this is an earthquake.&quot; The proposer also suggested that the background of the card could be transparent to avoid interfering with the picture or to reduce the picture to avoid interfering with the message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/91f449Ro3kM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of the Interior pointed out that there are currently six TV stations broadcast by the station, such as Dongsen, Sanli, TVBS, Zhongshi, Zhongtian, and Daai. The format of the six TV stations is not consistent. Although the conditions, requirements, and materials of the wave are all provided by the Meteorological Bureau, the presentation methods cannot be unified. The Ministry of the Interior said that the relevant laws and regulations involved in this case include the TV broadcasting law, the cable radio and television law, the cable radio and television system operators disasters and emergency response measures, but the relevant mechanisms, expropriation and operation mechanisms need to be further clarified. The Ministry of the Interior pointed out that the entire government's disaster prevention and control system is quite complex. It is necessary to divide into three levels: front-level mitigation, post-settlement and post-surgical recovery: central level, county level, and township level. Therefore, the meeting will be co-sponsored by the Ministry of the Interior, NCC and the Ministry of Communications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NCC, the current TV channels are divided into satellite broadcasters and wireless TV. Satellite broadcasters can transmit signals to satellites or MOD operators via satellite to transmit channel content to users. Wireless TVs are divided into several types. One is to transmit signals through wireless TV relay stations, and the viewers buy a set- The top box can be viewed by connecting to the TV; another wireless station that must be loaded or contracted with cable TV can also be seen on the cable TV; the other is that the mobile communication network of CBS is received by the mobile phone. NCC said that the current disaster prevention laws and related laws and regulations do not mandate that the passers-by must be connected to the network of disaster prevention and control units, mainly because the industry has spontaneously signed a letter of intent for cooperation with the Elephant Bureau. At present, there is only one TV in the TV, and others. There are five Weiguang companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, NCC pointed out that there is a regulatory suspicion that forces all TV channels to automatically broadcast disaster prevention messages. The radio and television three laws authorize the main points of the natural disaster emergency requisition channel. This part is the propaganda of post-disaster disasters. Like SARS and dengue fever, the channels levied should broadcast the content of the disaster prevention unit. In the procedure, the disaster prevention and defense unit first sends an application for requisition to the general meeting, and then the communication will review and requisition the channel, and the designated television and broadcasting operators will stop broadcasting the program and broadcast the disaster prevention information. Articles 27 and 31 of the Disaster Prevention Law respectively transmit disaster warning messages or set up a response center before the disaster, and use the media to collect and transmit disaster information during and after the disaster. According to the regulations, it is a pre-, post-, and post-event. Dissemination of disaster prevention information. However, in the earthquake quick report, due to the emergency response center when the earthquake rapid report occurred, the relevant regulations may have doubts and need to be dealt with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Meteorological Bureau pointed out that after the disaster prevention and alerting cell broadcasting system was launched in 2016, people's mobile phones could receive messages. In the same year, Dongsen TV station actively visited the Meteorological Bureau, hoping that when the earthquake occurred, I hoped that the picture could be covered. In this way, people can simultaneously get the news of the earthquake bulletin. After discussion, after the TV station made equipment purchase and system construction, in August 2016, the Meteorological Bureau signed a cooperation contract with Dongsen TV, and the Meteorological Bureau began to provide the information of the Dongsen TV Express. Followed by other TV stations to discuss cooperation with the Meteorological Bureau.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Meteorological Bureau said that the content of the entire screen is provided by the Meteorological Bureau, and the way of the screen overlay, the sound of the reminder or the duration of the time. The Meteorological Bureau respects the ideas and ideas of the design of each TV station. It does not force a certain amount of time or how the entire screen is displayed. However, some meteorological bureaus in the text hope that everyone is consistent, so the text is provided by the Meteorological Administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-issue-is-clarified-and-the-current-known-issues-are-discussed-in-depth&quot;&gt;The issue is clarified, and the current known issues are discussed in depth.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the issue is clarified, the National Earthquake Center shares that the National Earthquake Center has cooperated with the Ministry of Education to establish a compound earthquake in the small and medium-sized countries. Quick report system. The compound seismic quick report system combines the Earthquake Administration's earthquake report and the local earthquake detection mechanism to detect nearby earthquakes through self-built seismometers. Guozheng Center said that the case is also included in the forward-looking plan and hopes to have opportunities to promote it to other fields in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Channel operators are worried that if they use the TV to publish earthquake news, I am afraid that the audience will stay in front of the TV and miss the opportunity to escape. The Disaster Prevention Office explained that the current direction of the government is to promote a multi-dimensional earthquake notification notification mechanism, which is the mechanism of &quot;multi-modal notification&quot;, which is also adopted by many countries. Not only TV, but also through various channels to let everyone know that &quot;the earthquake wave is about to arrive&quot;, so that everyone can act quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dongsen TV shared that Dongsen News has set up a complete set of SOPs after receiving the earthquake report. How to deal with the anchor, how to do the pilot control, and what actions the editor has, have established a fixed process. . After the news station was built, the top management also wanted to expand, so it may be launched at Dongsen Finance. However, an assessment found that Dongsen Finance Station will do live broadcast of Taiwan lottery lottery from 8:30 to 9:00 every night. If the earthquake is being reported when the ball is ran out, will it be questioned by the fans? Sex? At the same time, each time you build such a system, it costs about 6.7 million. If each one is built, it will cost tens of millions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a midday break, the afternoon group discussion focused on &quot;How to make a TV earthquake report&quot;, including what happens when a false positive occurs? How to improve the speed of the quick report? Is there any other way to provide earthquake quick news services other than TV stations?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/cefe13fe0a8de71c30fdc0732003b78e51073d83.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-discussion-looking-for-possible-solutions&quot;&gt;Group discussion, looking for possible solutions&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After discussion, the earthquake quick report on TV is divided into two parts, one is the channel industry push, and the other is the system industry forced transfer. In terms of channel operators, small TV stations may not be able to afford the relevant costs, need to increase equipment, or provide incentives to encourage TV station interface. If the system operators force the transfer, they will also face the problem that the small platform is difficult to interface. After the transfer, they may also be protested by the channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The system industry has forced the turntable part of the exercise, but there is no automation between the MSP and the meteorological bureau. There is no private network between the MSP operators. The fire department is worried that it may take too much time and need to do more tests. Confirm that it takes time. The second group suggests that the information reception of the set-top box can refer to the cell broadcast mechanism on the mobile phone, and the NCDR directly throws the earthquake report to the platform operator. The second group also proposes another way. You can refer to the method of primary and secondary schools. The Meteorological Bureau only sends the epicenter, then sends the epicenter and scale, saves the calculation time, and calculates the shock wave scale and arrival time by the set-top box. This will speed up the transfer. In the information transmission, the application of the Central Meteorological Administration is installed at the head end of each platform. The information is directly transmitted from the head end to the set-top box, and then the on-board box performs operations on its own location. However, Cathy clarified that the current set-top box may be difficult to provide such a computer system, and if other instructions are in progress, it may affect the calculation process. However, in the future, technology will change with each passing day, and there may be such a computer system in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the aspect of false positives, the anchor can be corrected in a verbal manner, and a marquee can be added. The time for clarification should be as fast as possible, and mechanisms should be established to coordinate the mechanisms for finding problems afterwards. In addition, let the public know that false positives are normal, and internal parties should also exercise clarification mechanisms for false positives and respond as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you let the people know how to take refuge after the TV message? First of all, the voice should be unified, and it should not cause panic among the people. It is also necessary to know how to take refuge through the education and training of primary and secondary schools. Since some disabled people may not see it, the sound transmission needs to be discussed to allow the visually impaired to respond quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/46b206867e6926d0f1f63f45a1d6273be38a5668.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other aspects of the rapid earthquake reporting pipeline, in addition to broadcasting in primary and secondary schools, towns and villages, you can also consider using air raid warnings or the police department's broadcasts; in addition, the disaster prevention industry can also be encouraged to do related activities. Pick up. At the end of the meeting, Tang Feng’s political commissar summed up, “Today is really like a jigsaw puzzle. Everyone brainstorms.” She explained, “Now is the stage of feasibility assessment, so don’t worry about getting it right now.” The future It will be assessed by the Ministry of the Interior which programs are feasible and which are not feasible, and openly respond to netizens on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the gathering of the conference, these opinions will be reported to the Dean and relevant heads by the Tang Feng political commissar at the next week's government meeting as a reference for follow-up decision-making; [The Agenda Handbook] at the meeting (https:/ /docs.google.com/document/d/10_sIM536djO6EnO1PsWvozvuu5CE2caSizTUXQYIacU/edit), &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kz_sp_s=/&quot;&gt;Mind Map&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit. pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-07-27-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1 %e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac%e4%b8%89%e5%8d%81%e4%ba%94%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6 relevant information such as %9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;verbatim&lt;/a&gt; will also be published on the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz_SP_s=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f7e1ae9d668e42696f487af03aaf865adf156a47.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Meeting summary report status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;collaborative-meeting-to-build-consensus-from-the-bottom-up-civil-servants-are-expected-to-learn-new-methods&quot;&gt;Collaborative meeting to build consensus from the bottom up, civil servants are expected to learn new methods&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposer said that the topic is a professional issue, many things are not understood by the general public, relevant units Will know. According to his observation, today's meeting preparation is very sufficient. The issue manual integrates the regulations and helps a lot. However, when discussing, it will add new things, and it will take time to understand. The threshold is higher, although he listens. Understand, but it is recommended that people who do not understand can ask questions. In terms of venues, the proponents suggested that the logo could be strengthened in the future to facilitate participants to find the venue. The civil servants attending the meeting thought that many people had received public proposals from different channels. In the past, there was no such face-to-face, and many ministers participated in the discussion of the proposal. The Meteorological Bureau considered this a good model. It is not implemented as decided in the past. It has the opportunity to build consensus from the bottom up and know what can be done and what can't. Civil servants also believe that a neutral host is a necessary presence, which can reduce the feeling of confrontation, and also guide the collaborative meeting in a timely manner; the host team can also relieve the pressure of many public departments, such as the need to spend the issue manual A lot of time and energy, the public sector is difficult to do; but with this issue manual, you can have a more comprehensive view and help the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The civil servant pointed out that it is quite difficult to find a concrete and feasible solution, but through this discussion, it can be clarified which is not feasible and which can be tried. Some participants said that this meeting uses mental maps to present, which can help you understand the overall issue. There are also topic manuals to help you understand the topic and help you do your homework before the meeting. He laughed and said that the topic manual is &quot;the specification of the paper grade.&quot; However, there are also civil servants who believe that the mind map is unfamiliar. He has not learned to use the mind map during his growth, so he will be confused when using it. Although the mind map can quickly see the face of the issue, the traditional topic book help is still relatively large. But the civil servant also said that if there is an opportunity in the future, I hope that there will be more opportunities for the public sector to learn new ways of analyzing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f5db8caeef82c510a1b1c183d6a98c118a0f4e37.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Through the process of clarifying the collaborative meeting, participants suggested that the voices used in the TV earthquake report could be unified and that other ways of notifying the people to escape as soon as possible could be made.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f5db8caeef82c510a1b1c183d6a98c118a0f4e37.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: AI and master</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: AI and master" /><published>2018-07-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85/">&lt;p&gt;The typhoon has just passed, bringing abundant rainfall. This is the blessing of Taiwan, and there is no shortage of water in summer; however, in recent years, stable water supply has always been a challenge for Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚰 You may not know that more than half of the water pipes in Taiwan are still plastic water pipes used to popularize tap water 30 years ago. These plastic pipes are limited to funds and cannot be completely replaced. As a result, the water leakage rate of the entire pipe is as high as 15%, and the water lost by the pipeline is nearly 1 billion tons per year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a big question, is there a solution? There are indeed experts who are doing “grab the leak”. Taishui’s existing 80 masters carry a “leak detector” that can amplify 900 times of sound, and “listen” back and forth in the sewer. The seniors have 30 years of experience. However, 80 of them go down one by one, and they can circle around Taiwan in three years. Even if they are not sleepy, it is difficult to find new leaks in real time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This hot problem, I didn’t expect to see the dawn of an AI technology recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning, I was in the President’s Cup hackathon. For the first time, I saw the proposal of the “Rescue Water Baby” team and found that they used the technology of “supervised learning”, which means that the trapped masters told the machine. What kind of data is heard indicates that there is a leak, and then the “deep learning” algorithm is used to predict whether the field check is correct. By the time the “machine apprentice” gradually builds the model, it can save the masters a lot of time and effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🕚 Such a system is not the first invention in Taiwan, but also a solution for Israeli company developers, but it is costly. In Taiwan, the system written in open source has reached 70% accuracy, and the time it takes to find a leak source has dropped to one-tenth of the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;自主 Self-developed technology has one advantage: it can be used in other fields, such as smart meters or natural gas pipelines. Because of the pressure and flow rate, this concept can also be used. The “Rescue Water Baby” team will also represent Taiwan in the next month to participate in the acceleration plan organized by the New Zealand government to provide solutions to local water leakage problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the interesting thing about this case is that there is always a voice in the workshop: AI is coming, and human work opportunities will be replaced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👴 For example, the 80 masters who caught the leak, are they unemployed when AI comes? completely opposite! The process of machine learning will continue to require the wisdom of human beings to “fill in” and constantly let people learn from each other in order to solve the problem one by one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 “Rescue Water Baby” incorporates the wisdom of the master, solves the problem in collaboration, and finds new value for people. This is what we expect.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會創新" /><summary type="html">&quot;Rescue the baby&quot; incorporates the wisdom of the master, solves the problem in collaboration, and finds new value in the value of people. This is what we expect.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bf74b4534e016990033a3a484b8cd79f12eb4fab.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Is it feasible to take a vacation off? Collaborative meeting to think about related packages</title><link href="/en/blog/%E8%AD%A6%E6%B6%88%E4%BC%91%E5%81%87%E5%8F%AF%E8%A1%8C%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%99%BC%E6%83%B3%E7%9B%B8%E9%97%9C%E9%85%8D%E5%A5%97/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is it feasible to take a vacation off? Collaborative meeting to think about related packages" /><published>2018-07-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-07-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E8%AD%A6%E6%B6%88%E4%BC%91%E5%81%87%E5%8F%AF%E8%A1%8C%E5%97%8E%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%99%BC%E6%83%B3%E7%9B%B8%E9%97%9C%E9%85%8D%E5%A5%97</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E8%AD%A6%E6%B6%88%E4%BC%91%E5%81%87%E5%8F%AF%E8%A1%8C%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%99%BC%E6%83%B3%E7%9B%B8%E9%97%9C%E9%85%8D%E5%A5%97/">&lt;p&gt;On May 28, 2018, netizen Zhang Law Enforced Proposal on the Join Platform &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/adf22df8-b405-4594-b637-10b5dc341c88&quot;&gt;Revising the Anniversary and Festival Implementation Measures in Article 5, Paragraph 4, Paragraph 5, Adding the Fifth Section to Add Police and Fire Fighters On the day of the police festival and the firefighting holiday&lt;/a&gt;, it is considered that the work of the police and firefighters is highly dangerous and laborious. Uncertainty and overworked work, I hope to increase the day of the holiday and boost morale. In order to clarify the proponents' claims and to think about possible solutions, the PDIS team held a collaborative meeting on July 17th at the Ministry of Finance Information Center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;regression-problem-starting-from-the-cause-of-overworked&quot;&gt;Regression problem, starting from the cause of overworked&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposer believes that police duty is dangerous and widespread, and it also gives a lot of overworked conditions. One-day approach to improve the morale of the police, after internal discussions with the relevant authorities, decided to follow the spirit of the collaborative meeting, in addition to the feasibility of a day off, but also explore the reasons for the general overwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After several discussions and collaborations before the meeting, we found that the reason for the overwork of the police is the lack of manpower, and the business is too heavy and other related issues. Due to the special work, the police need to work on duty 24 hours a day, so they take the shift. However, because the police are on duty 24 hours a day, many of the ministry's related businesses will ask the police for assistance, but these services have become one of the police's excessive workload. The reform of the country is a related issue in which the police have dealt with the police overwork. It is believed that the police's performance system should be amended to improve the police's overwork. Although the manpower of firefighters is currently not subject to the control of the total number of posts, the local government has a total number of posts, and the increase in firefighting manpower may crowd out the manpower of other bureaus. The business of many units requires the assistance of the fire department to become a heavy business burden for firefighters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist participants in clarifying the context of relevant issues, the PDIS team worked with the Home Office to write the [Question Brochure] for this meeting (https://docs.google.com/document/d/18HfXduTs23Czn7UPtsgSyQ7X-71gnjtkoMt6HBq_JnI/edit) And send it to the participants before the meeting so that the participants can read it in advance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vQ9PiictQFo1JD1yErJbBeK_CtCuMkc0Ar1Gdn5p7WHBtsR-0owos5Ww1bYZcX_kAZOqiyqbv5-JKad/pub?embedded=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e26f20dd3734e11fd11395f8947886a7a6b6d245.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Meeting situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-sponsors-are-expecting-a-vacation-to-make-the-police-feel-valued&quot;&gt;The sponsors are expecting a vacation to make the police feel valued.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the meeting, the sponsor proposed a &quot;comparison table for soldiers and police officers&quot;, arguing that the police work regardless of storm or snow Uninterrupted, &quot;the complexity is undoubtedly the most arduous among all public servants.&quot; But in the face of protests, the police are always a pawn that the public is jealous of, and they can't help themselves. In terms of working conditions, the Police Service Regulations stipulates that it is 8 hours, but each unit has exceptional overtime work every day, and there is no overtime payable. The proponents believe that the military is on holiday according to the regulations of the Ministry of National Defense. The police do not have a holiday at present. They hope that they can have a day off, reduce the number of grassroots troubles and unnecessary performances, and let the police feel that they are valued by the state. In this regard, the Civil Affairs Department responded that if it is to eliminate the holiday, it is necessary to consider other occupations to request the possibility of holiday, which requires overall consideration; the police department believes that if the policy decides to take a day off on June 15th, the police festival If the police department can cooperate with it, there will be no related problems, the related business has been reduced, and the administrative assistance has been reduced from 187 to 167. In 105 years, there was also a letter explaining that the police could subdue the purchase of food. The Police Department said that the police's welfare measures can be obtained from Facebook [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/npa4u/&quot;&gt;NPA Director's Office&lt;/a&gt;&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Fire Department said that if the policy determines the firefighting holiday, the fire department can cooperate. In terms of manpower shortage, as long as the local government can pull up the organs and firefighters, the subsidy will be more. I hope that the firefighting manpower can be increased year by year through this mechanism. In terms of business, the related businesses such as beekeeping and snake hunting have gradually shifted. Go to the agricultural administrative unit or entrust the private sector to handle it. In terms of the welfare of firefighters, there are the maximum amount of time and amount to be paid for overtime pay. Regarding the part of the Fire Fighting Festival that is not required to be prepared for the celebration, the Fire Department's position is in fact consistent with that of the Police Department. It is still necessary to commend some of the best-performing firefighters and charity colleagues in the year. In the future, we will focus on commendation activities and reduce the nature of performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-facts-clarify-the-cause-of-the-problem-and-clarify-the-current-situation&quot;&gt;The facts clarify the cause of the problem and clarify the current situation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the facts are clarified, the police force’s participants pointed out that the local government is not aware of the manpower application of the Central Police Department. Unclear about the manpower needs of the localities, the Department and the local government seem to have some gaps in communication. As a result, the local government and the self-governing autonomous projects of the parliament have caused the overhaul of the local police officers and police. It is recommended that the department control the autonomous projects proposed by the local governments. The Police Department responded that in May 2015, the police officers were appointed to assist in the implementation of the principle. It is hoped that the local police station can convince the heads of the local jurisdictions of the local jurisdictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a police officer's proposal, I hope that in the performance part, do not arrange short-term projects, so that colleagues can be prevented from making illegal forms, such as raising a case or breaking a law. One of the second-party advocates suggested that in addition to the leave, there are always some police officers and firefighters who must be on duty that day. I hope that there will be some benefits on the day of the police festival and the firefighting festival, such as not taking any courses, not waiting for services. Something, only perform urgent tasks, or arrange some other meals, massages and other enjoyment. In fact, this is actually a problem that will be encountered in the performance of the whole world. The same working time, rather than investing in serious work, may sometimes choose to invest in the indicators to meet this performance first. The process of satisfaction may not always be possible. Get the job well done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Police Department responded that there were meetings in the department to discuss police projects, appraisals and related projects, and some suggestions. It is hoped that these projects can be considered by local police stations. For example, there are 23 items in the normal part of the evaluation project. However, the Police Department also reminded that some projects are sometimes based on performance, but on the consideration of style and discipline. In terms of &quot;project evaluation&quot;, the Police Department is already gradually reducing. I believe that colleagues in the field can feel it slowly. In terms of mitigating performance, the Police Department has invited the teachers of the National Police to set up courses to let more than 400 people who are currently planning performance-related assessments in local police stations to understand how performance is better. After that, relevant scholars and experts will be invited to regularly review the performance of the merger. Among them, an online platform will be planned to allow grassroots police officers to provide advice or to express their opinions on projects and evaluations. In the selection of representatives at the grassroots level, they will also inform all units to understand the opinions of the police and let the grassroots members The police can participate. The sponsors would like to know whether the Civil Affairs Department will use the exclusive anniversary of the police officers as the direction of the law. After the adoption of the anniversary and the draft holiday, it is difficult for the police officers to have a chance to take a day off. The Secretary for Home Affairs has responded that there are many drafts, mostly based on commemorative days and festivals. At present, the Legislative Yuan has great disagreement on whether or not different industries should be on holiday. At present, these drafts are not targeted at specific occupations, and the controversy is mostly in political holidays. The fire department has clarified that guarding the lives and property of the people is the responsibility of the firefighters. As long as the people dial 119, the firefighters will perform the tasks of disaster relief and ambulance, but it can simplify other duties. The Taipei City Fire Department added that the welfare part and the dangerous plus part have been tried twice for the Personnel Administration of the Executive Yuan. The Taipei City Fire Department is trying to double the risk. The manpower segment has increased from 300 to 1,800 people from 2014 to this year. It is very helpful for the firefighters in Taipei City. In the past, they worked overtime and could not ask for overtime pay. Obvious reduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f49f20aa0cffc19ee1bce85505deb3cdb254cd28.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-discussion-about-holiday-related-packages-and-thought-about-the-solution-method&quot;&gt;Group discussion about holiday related packages, and thought about the solution method&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a morning clarification, the afternoon meeting focused on whether the day of the holiday is feasible and related, and whether the overwork is resolved Possibly, it is divided into a group of police officers and a group of firefighters, which are discussed separately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The police team believes that if there is a day off on holidays, there should be no major problems in the service. However, if there is a holiday, the relevant progress activities will have to be adjusted. After all, the election of the former police officer in the police festival is a great honour and seems to need to be held. It has been suggested that it is possible to allow vigilance to take part in a day off to participate in activities. It may also be a direction to think about. In addition, it is also suggested that the celebration of the police festival should reduce performance activities or eliminate performance activities and reduce the burden on the police; At the same time, the grassroots colleagues can decide what activities they should hold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The part of the police that is busy in work, according to the resolution of the reform of the country, the police department has follow-up measures. Previously, after each business unit completed the project itself, it will do a project evaluation report, but it only ends there. Now the Police Department will adopt a new approach. Every year, we will conduct an inventory and review of the project. We will also invite scholars and experts and invite representatives at the grassroots level to come up and express their opinions on the project. Although the reform of the country was the original resolution of the meeting, the committee was established. However, after the four board members were invited to the police station to participate in the discussion, these members did not oppose the new practice. Luo Bingcheng’s political commissar also supported this direction. The follow-up meeting of the Police Department will be promoted in this direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the appraisal part, some appraisals are based on the position of the central business unit, such as the policy direction of the president, the dean or the minister, but the heads of the county and the city themselves have the responsibility for success or failure in the local public order, and these directions will become the grassroots appraisal. project. If there are too many appraisal projects, it may lead to overworked police. The first group of discussions found that the police department does not want the improperly increased appraisal to cause the police to overwork, and also opposes the grassroots supervisors improperly requesting their colleagues to extend their service hours, or stop the rotation. . At present, the Police Department has a pipeline to respond, such as the existing Director's mailbox or the NPA Director's Office. Some people worry that because the grassroots chiefs need to be promoted, they will ask the following people to improve their performance, which will lead to overwork. However, after discussion, it is found that if the promotion cannot be combined with work performance, it may have problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the improper supervision of public opinion representatives, the members of the police force urged the officers of the police department to support the grassroots colleagues and insist on living according to their positions. However, within the legal scope of the law, some methods may be provided for the representatives of the public. Can respond to the needs of public opinion. These requests for related matters should be handled by the Independent Commission Against Corruption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c5b211b4bc59f1c3c9b7250fd5837ff28148ee31.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The firefighter team first shared that the day of the holiday can be divided into &quot;substantial holiday&quot;, that is, everyone does not work for a day, and &quot;type holiday&quot;, although the day is a holiday, but the person doing the work and the things to do are Do as usual. However, the Fire Festival is a representative festival. In addition to the praise of firefighters, the same day, the colleagues of Yixiao need a grand ceremony. However, in fact, the Fire Festival is not only active on the day, it may be active in the previous week or before, especially the promotion activities. These publicity activities are because the firefighting festival is very close to the Chinese New Year, and it is often prone to fire and carbon monoxide poisoning. Therefore, people need to be cautious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If firefighters are on vacation, can other public departments or related occupations be compared? After discussion, the staff of the Highway Festival and the Railway Festival are subject to the Labor Law. In terms of public servants, it is possible to dismiss the police on duty and the work is heavy and dangerous. Therefore, there is a legitimate reason for the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of the shortage of firefighters, if you want to replenish manpower, you must pass exams and training. Training takes a year and a half to be appointed, so if there is a related manpower requirement, it will take two years or even three years to complete. At present, the Fire Department has enriched the fire manpower plan. It is expected to increase by 3,000 people every five years. It is hoped that the firefighters will have time to rest by manpower. In terms of service schedules, ideally, I hope that I can take a break from work. However, in fact, according to the current system, there will be overtime work and still need to make up the manpower. However, each person who fills a person will have more than one million dollars a year, and the burden on local finance is relatively heavy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The part of overtime pay, the current central subsidy is set at 12,000 yuan, and the overtime pay limit is 17,000 yuan. The difference between 12,000 yuan and 17,000 yuan is paid by the local government. Whether the finance can be loaded can reach the upper limit. In terms of compensatory time off, the current working hours of firefighters are very long, so the cumulative speed of compensatory time off cannot keep up with the speed of vacation. It may be one year, and the rest will not be completed. The discussion mentioned that if the firefighters were originally on vacation, but were recalled, these increased days of vacation due to suspension may not limit the time limit so that they can always find opportunities to catch them back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the meeting, the sponsor added that if the government pays attention to the police, the cost of a day off is small, but the police can feel the support of the government. I hope the government can support the proposal and let the police have a chance. Take a day off. He said: &quot;Police and consumerism can only get rid of the formal slogan. It is not the sergeant who says &quot;hard work&quot;. The police and the special holiday or a day off can really highlight the significance of this festival.&quot;
 The above solutions, as well as the conference process, will be reported by the Tang Feng political commissar to the heads of the relevant ministries and the dean at the government meeting next Monday, as a follow-up policy to promote reference. Related &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kzheamw=/&quot;&gt;Mind Map&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-07- 17-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac %e4%b8%89%e5%8d%81%e5%85%ab%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;verbatim record&lt;/a&gt; Also It will be open to facilitate the public to understand the relevant process of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kzHeaMw=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dfd725fe67420876c0650bb16a169bcb9935f800.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Tang Feng thanked the participants for their contributions &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-sponsor-is-dissatisfied-and-thinks-that-the-meeting-should-focus-on-the-day-of-the-holiday&quot;&gt;The sponsor is dissatisfied and thinks that the meeting should focus on the day of the holiday.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participants pointed out that the content of today’s discussion is actually similar to the previous one. However, this collaborative meeting is an opportunity for The Police Department and the Fire Department can face the problem and answer it once and it works well. However, are there any basis for these answers? The disappearing service will not reappear in another way, and may still need to be verified. Participants pointed out that in the future, if government agencies can be asked to disclose more information for private verification, it can be confirmed that these commitments have been implemented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a teacher who observed that there seemed to be a relationship between the top and the bottom of the meeting, which led to the lack of willingness to speak at the grassroots level. The presence of the legislator may also affect the speeches of the participants, but this may also be difficult to resolve. The proponents thought that these overwork issues were mentioned before, but the government always responded in this way, so they did not want to entangle them on these issues. He believes that the meeting should not discuss the issue of overwork, and should focus on the feasibility of a day off, so that the grassroots staff can feel the police.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/486f73a497f894cef6184f8bca49e2ef3ce1685e.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group collaboration status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Netizens believe that because the police and firefighters work with high risks, labor, uncertainty, and work overwork, I hope to increase the day of the holiday and boost morale. After clarifying the appeal, the collaborative meeting focused on the possibility of a holiday and a solution to the police overwork.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dfd725fe67420876c0650bb16a169bcb9935f800.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How to prevent child care centers and kindergarten child abuse problems? Collaborative meeting recommended to improve teachers’ working conditions</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E9%98%B2%E7%AF%84%E6%89%98%E5%AC%B0%E4%B8%AD%E5%BF%83-%E5%B9%BC%E5%85%92%E5%9C%92%E5%85%92%E8%99%90%E5%95%8F%E9%A1%8C-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E6%8F%90%E6%98%87%E6%95%99%E5%B8%AB%E5%8B%9E%E5%8B%95%E6%A2%9D%E4%BB%B6/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to prevent child care centers and kindergarten child abuse problems? Collaborative meeting recommended to improve teachers' working conditions" /><published>2018-06-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-06-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E9%98%B2%E7%AF%84%E6%89%98%E5%AC%B0%E4%B8%AD%E5%BF%83%E3%80%81%E5%B9%BC%E5%85%92%E5%9C%92%E5%85%92%E8%99%90%E5%95%8F%E9%A1%8C%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E6%8F%90%E6%98%87%E6%95%99%E5%B8%AB%E5%8B%9E%E5%8B%95%E6%A2%9D%E4%BB%B6</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E9%98%B2%E7%AF%84%E6%89%98%E5%AC%B0%E4%B8%AD%E5%BF%83-%E5%B9%BC%E5%85%92%E5%9C%92%E5%85%92%E8%99%90%E5%95%8F%E9%A1%8C-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E6%8F%90%E6%98%87%E6%95%99%E5%B8%AB%E5%8B%9E%E5%8B%95%E6%A2%9D%E4%BB%B6/">&lt;p&gt;On June 29, 2018, PDIS held the 36th Collaborative Meeting of Open Government Liaisons at the Yukong Headquarters Center to discuss the possibility of nursery centers, kindergarten installation monitors, and the reduction of teacher-student ratio. .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This collaborative meeting was a merger of two cases. On March 15, 2018, netizen Jia He proposed on the Join platform &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/d4834778-78aa -4328-b2a0-bcf517880e1c&quot;&gt;Please support legislation to force custody centers and kindergartens to set up an online surveillance system&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, i hope to legislate to force the nursery center and kindergarten to set up an online online surveillance system so that parents can immediately watch the child's actions. then on march 24th, netizen coral lin proposed &quot;[reducing the teacher-student ratio] in the kindergarten (https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/c42ad297-84b9-4ccd-8326-dda69e0e76f9)&quot; on the Join platform. It is required to reduce the teacher-student ratio in kindergartens and improve the quality of early childhood education. After the open government liaison voted in May, the two cases were handled together; therefore, we held this collaborative meeting on June 29.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pre-study-to-clarify-the-reasons-behind-the-appeal&quot;&gt;Pre-study to clarify the reasons behind the appeal&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the analysis of the issue, the proponent hopes to install the online surveillance system. It is hoped that through the surveillance system, children can be seen at the nursery center or kindergarten. I was ill-treated. However, according to the spirit of the collaborative meeting, we will first explore the key reasons for the sponsor's proposal, and then explore whether this method can really solve the problem. After interviews and understanding, we found that the abuse problem in the nursery center or kindergarten often comes from the out-of-control nurse and the education service staff. Improving labor conditions is probably the solution to reducing child abuse. If the monitoring system goes online so that parents can watch it directly (referred to as &quot;online monitor&quot; in this meeting), parents may be too concerned about their children, so they are constantly involved in the service process of the nursery center and kindergarten, resulting in the first line. A heavier burden on personnel. If the monitor is only a video recording (called &quot;video monitor&quot; in this conference), it is not possible to install it without a dead end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the area of ​​improving working conditions, the most common initiative is to reduce the teacher-student ratio. At present, the teacher-student ratio of the nursery center is 1 to 5. For kindergartens, 1 to 8 for two and a half to three years old, and 1 to 15 for children over three years old. According to the research, reducing the teacher-student ratio can greatly reduce the labor burden of the nursery staff and the education service personnel, and it is also very helpful for the education of young children. However, in terms of teachers' working conditions, there are other possibilities such as raising salary and improving the relationship between teachers and teachers. The sponsors hope to install online monitors because of the poor mutual trust between parents and teachers. Therefore, how to improve mutual trust between teachers and teachers is also a problem that needs to be solved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist participants in clarifying issues, the PDIS team worked in advance with the Department of Health and Welfare and the Ministry of Education to write the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1_x1gw5sdlekcvtcnu1eatnjigbjs14c7zntw-ba0fnq/edit&quot;&gt;Question Manual&lt;/a&gt;, and Send it to the participants in advance to help you understand the topic before you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vRHs5vCqm0EJwHsbW6run-fLku-5YJATXJqWu567WQfzy-w-nKO85AN-ln7XX0KGMuBpnS5FmsAcFop/pub?embedded=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;considering-the-cost-of-child-care-and-child-care-the-researcher-has-reduced-the-number-of-teachers-and-students-more-than-many-times-without-consensus&quot;&gt;Considering the cost of child care and child care, the researcher has reduced the number of teachers and students more than many times without consensus&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the collaboration meeting, Weifu explained that in order to reduce the teacher-student ratio, Weifu Department From October 13, 2015 to December 28, 2016, a total of 7 research conferences were held. On April 16 this year, a conference on “prospecting issues related to education and care services” was held. The case was also included in the discussion. However, there is still no way to reach a consensus on the discussion at the meeting. Wei Fu's colleagues pointed out that although reducing the care ratio can reduce the care pressure of the nurses and improve the quality of the nursery, the operating costs of the nursery center will increase, which will also be reflected in the fees, so it is difficult to form a consensus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ministry of Education pointed out that the current surveillance system is not a necessary equipment for kindergartens, but public kindergartens can apply for setup with the Ministry of Education's State Education Department if they have needs; but online surveillance systems may involve issues related to human rights and privacy. . The Ministry of Education pointed out that at present, in the prevention of child abuse, the Ministry of Education has notified and managed the unsuitable personnel, and there are also penalties for improper discipline. The professional knowledge of teachers also has a way to improve, and the Ministry of Education will also actively provide a friendly working environment for the staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of teacher-student ratio, the Ministry of Education pointed out that the claim of the sponsors is somewhat different from the current situation. Once the teacher-student ratio is lowered, public kindergartens will reduce the amount of collections of more than 40,000 people. To maintain the current collection capacity, it is necessary to increase the number of education service personnel of more than 3,000 people. It is estimated that it will spend an additional 1.95 billion. . In the case of private kindergartens, lowering the teacher-student ratio may also increase operating costs and increase the burden on parents. The Ministry of Education said that at present, 50 kindergartens must be built in the forward-looking infrastructure, and the plan for the publicization of early childhood education should be expanded. The principle of non-profit kindergartens and public kindergartens should be promoted. The Legislative Yuan also has resolutions. After the publicization ratio reaches a certain level, based on the promotion of pre-school education service quality, it should be considered to reduce the number of classes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-first-line-nursery-and-education-service-staff-are-under-great-pressure-and-the-parents-are-the-biggest-challenge&quot;&gt;The first-line nursery and education service staff are under great pressure, and the parents are the biggest challenge&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the clarification of the issue, many participants also shared their views. One teacher shared that at the teaching site, because the school is a place for group activities, the children occasionally push, fight, and noisy, but the teachers at the scene can handle it very well, but if you add an instant monitor, many times Different. She pointed out that the workload of kindergarten teachers is increasing year by year. In addition to preparation for each item, there are various administrative workloads such as updating ingredients, prevention and treatment of infectious diseases, and fire prevention training. She said that the biggest challenge for teachers is the parents behind them: &quot;Every parent has different requirements for children. Even the father, mother, grandfather and grandmother of the same family have different educational methods.&quot;
| The Education Industry Council pointed out that these practical aspects are the reason why the industry can't find talents, because installing monitors leads to a worse working environment, so they leave and cross other industries. The colleagues of the Chiayi Education Bureau also pointed out that the situation they encountered was often that the parents confessed to the school, the excellent teaching and maintenance service personnel left the job, and the algorithm institute also gave him innocence, and these people no longer returned to the education service industry. He also reminded that the situation of the local township is very different from that of the metropolitan area. The aunts of the locals often go to work three or four times to wait for the children to get off work. It is also difficult to find the staff of the education service in the local township: &quot;The city and the city cannot be integrated. .&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;is-the-child-care-market-mechanism-participants-have-different-tune&quot;&gt;Is the child care market mechanism? Participants have different tune&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the on-site issues of the monitor, there is also a discussion on the market mechanism. Parent associations and a professor believe that the installation of monitors should return to the market mechanism. Some parents like to install. In order to meet such needs, there are naturally schools installed, and everyone should be free to choose. But another professor believes that the mechanism of early childhood education is not a market economy, nor a free economy. She pointed out that if it is the route of the market economy, what should people in low- and middle-income households generally do? She believes that the government should take the middle route. This is the question of how much the government has to enter and how much it will invest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another issue that sparked the discussion was the issue of self-editing textbooks. Private and child traders pointed out that private and young people often use workshop materials to reduce the workload of first-line teachers. But one professor believes that this is the reason for the consequences. She pointed out that the workshop set teaching materials are too far away from the children and there is no spirit of actual experience. She shared that President Tsai Ing-sung had just gone to Nanhai Kindergarten. Nanhai Kindergarten explored the playground of his own park with his children, thinking about how to improve and making a book together. &quot;We don't want to go to the past textbook-style education system,&quot; she stressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d469032fab7d43b08d02dc95ea7e57e6192ff92d.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;afternoon-discussion-focused-on-improving-the-quality-of-teachers-work-and-strengthening-mutual-trust-between-teachers-and-teachers&quot;&gt;Afternoon discussion focused on improving the quality of teachers' work and strengthening mutual trust between teachers and teachers&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, the discussion focused on how to prevent child abuse, improve the quality of teachers' work, and how to strengthen mutual trust between teachers and teachers. .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group of discussions pointed out that the development of the floor of the teacher's salary is a feasible direction, suggesting that even the government can pay part of the teacher's salary in the future. In addition, the first-line teachers need to unite to form a trade union, so they can compete for better working conditions. However, the education staff are less labor-conscious. It is recommended that training should be included in the training of labor rights awareness; the government also needs to implement labor inspection and strengthen Irregular visits by the Education Bureau or the Social Affairs Bureau. The staff of the Education Bureau pointed out that they hope that there will be an opportunity for the auditors to wear the secret recorder, which will be more convenient and can be used as evidence for the penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of the cost of the operators, the operators and the staff of the Education Bureau agree that the industry should report the financial status as much as possible, and attach the tax certificate, salary transfer documents and other certificates to the government. If the information is detailed enough, it will prove the company. The price increase should be returned to the teacher as much as possible, and the government should also approve a reasonable price increase based on the documents checked by these accountants. However, the industry believes that there are cases where the transfer documents are attached, but the review committee does not agree with the situation. The Education Bureau also believes that some operators may not be honest when they declare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The director pointed out that some parents are reluctant to let their children accept development assessments, causing some hidden special education students to enter the campus, causing additional burden on teachers. It may be necessary to integrate special education and general education on the premise of considering individual capitalization laws. System, or development assessment before entering the park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the establishment of mutual trust, increasing the interaction between parents and the school is the most important factor. Parents can be invited to participate in the study results discussion, or the appraisal committee members can join the parent representatives, train together, and understand the good teaching site. What is the way. In the handling of disputes, on the one hand, it is necessary to establish a complaint channel for healthy third parties (for example, through the public sector). If there is a video monitor on the campus, it is necessary to establish a good method of referral, and to apply to the public sector, for example, to go to the police first. The bureau will file the case or read it through the Education Bureau or the Social Affairs Bureau.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fbd2c5679b0e3ab104b78c11e3454fa78103a561.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second group of reports pointed out that lowering the teacher-student ratio may increase operating costs, causing parents to pay more tuition; if they are subsidized by the government budget, they may also crowd out other budgets. In strengthening parent-teacher mutual trust, parents may be given appropriate expectations for management. Officials can also encourage the media to provide positive preschool education reports to avoid negative news only; however, traditional media may lack interest in positive reporting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The topics discussed by the participants will be reported to the Dean at the government meeting next Monday after the PDIS team has compiled the information. The head of the relevant ministry will also get the same information. Will &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-06-29-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba %9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac%e4%b8%89%e5%8d%81%e5%85%ad%e6%ac%a1 %e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;Verbatem Record&lt;/a&gt;[heart map] with the issue clarified (https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kz66l4a=/) Open for reference by all walks of life, but also for future reference policies can be based on reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz66l4A=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;although-the-meeting-is-long-it-can-effectively-clarify-the-issue-participants-appreciate&quot;&gt;Although the meeting is long, it can effectively clarify the issue. Participants appreciate&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The government colleagues pointed out that there are too many information on this topic, including baby care, kindergarten, public, private, non-profit, and the content of the issue. Need to digest well, the words need to be more precise, to avoid misunderstanding. One of the teachers pointed out that the issue manual clearly clarified the context, but she thought that the early childhood education scene may be less clear to everyone, so she spoke more to share the practical situation of the early childhood education scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people believe that the differences between public and private have long been misunderstood. He pointed out that in the past few years, there have been great changes in the quality of private and child. The status of today's meeting gives everyone the opportunity to resolve many misunderstandings. He shared that many public sector meetings that had been involved before could only speak once, and there was no opportunity to refute. Today's meeting is a long time, and there are more opportunities for dialogue and clarification. Some participants also thought that some of the speeches in the middle caused a rebound, but the organizers quickly confirmed whether they felt uncomfortable. She felt that it was very good to take care of the participants' feelings. She suggested that this meeting should invite more young parents to talk about the issue of children being taken care of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the mind map, a professor who attended the meeting felt very much appreciated. The mind map can help you quickly clarify the context of the issue and see the relevant issues. Unlike the traditional public service system, it is often seen later. Forgot what I wrote before.&quot; He hopes that this form of meeting can be extended to more areas to help you clarify the issue.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">After the discussion, the topic discussed how to improve teachers' working conditions, improve mutual trust between teachers and teachers, and reduce the pressure on frontline service personnel.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d469032fab7d43b08d02dc95ea7e57e6192ff92d.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week Column: Revelation of Hibiscus</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week Column: Revelation of Hibiscus" /><published>2018-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-06-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/%e9%a6%ac%e5%a4%aa%e9%9e%8d%e9%83%a8%e8%90%bd&quot;&gt;马太鞍&lt;/a&gt; is the largest tribe of the ami and one of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://youthtravel.tw/sub/travelspot/eastern/index.php?id=33&quot;&gt;youth travel points&lt;/a&gt; planned by the youth department in hualien. in the past, the mountains and valleys were all &lt;a href=&quot;https://amis.moedict.tw/#fata'an&quot;&gt;fata’an&lt;/a&gt;, and the “Matai Saddle” was transliterated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of last month, I went to the Mata Ang tribe to meet and met &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mapulong.com/&quot;&gt;Mablon Farm&lt;/a&gt;. master ulang (kechunyu) tells us about the farm when it is always a whisper, so that everyone laughs. Four years ago, she started her own business from the land of her home. Today, the Mabulon Farm is open to popularity by relying on a large number of quality organic wild vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to crops, Mablon Farm has also gained community friendship. Ulang invites the tribes to work together, become mutual farming partners, and more often care for their neighbors: “When I see people who need help, I will drive them and often help me see the medicines and read the official documents,” she said. &lt;a href=&quot;https://amis.moedict.tw/#:mapolong&quot;&gt;Mapulong&lt;/a&gt; In the language, it means “together”. Ulang does make the farm a bridge in the tribe through action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌱 How do tribal youths find links to tribes? Lamen (CaiYijing), chairman of the Mata Sang Tribe Eco-Cultural Industry Development Association, is very impressed. More than a decade ago, Lamen, who graduated from the sect, returned to the tribe. From the study of the Taiwan Science and Technology Program at the time, he helped to plan a series of experiences. Mablon Farm is one of the agricultural experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💪 Lamen believes that although this series of projects is small, the benefits are beyond imagination - in addition to making more people aware of the tribal culture, the various ethnic groups in the eastern region are also promoting the way through promotion. , to establish a closer relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💯 [太巴塱] with Matthew Saddle (https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E5%A4%AA%E5%B7%B4%E5%A1%B1%E9%83%A8%E8%90%BD)(Tafalong) tribe, also started from more than ten years ago &lt;a href=&quot;https://youthtravel.tw/sub/travelspot/eastern/services.php?pid=57&amp;amp;id=225&quot;&gt;participation plan&lt;/a&gt;. how to get young friends to come to the tribe to gain in-depth experience is the subject of katai (xiaomingshan), the chief executive of the taiba village community building association, and the brainstorming of the tribes. for this reason, they even have only the annual sacrifices that the tribes participated in &lt;a href=&quot;https://youthtravel.tw/eventscontent.php?id=498&amp;amp;securechk=8cca1365ab64f567b55bc04a26c84c14&quot;&gt;open to the public&lt;/a&gt;. These efforts have enabled the Taipa tribe to carry out the grand travel plan to date, with an average satisfaction rate of 99.8 points.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌿 This reminds me of the bitterness of the greens in the soup when I ate. It didn’t take long for me to taste the sweetness. The tribe’s friend said that this is a common local wild vegetable &lt;a href=&quot;https://amis.moedict.tw/#sokoy&quot;&gt;sokoy&lt;/a&gt; (hibiscus,xiuguamilanguagepinyin). The same is true of the stories of Ulang, Lamen, and Kanew: the hard work ahead will eventually return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have time, you may wish to take a trip and taste the taste of hibiscus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會企業" /><summary type="html">The same is true of the stories of Ulang, Lamen, and Kanew: the hard work ahead will eventually return.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/b3847c96045edae82bc127c07d93ade99863b151.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How is the new tax filing website made?</title><link href="/en/blog/%E6%96%B0%E7%89%88%E5%A0%B1%E7%A8%85%E7%B6%B2%E7%AB%99%E6%98%AF%E6%80%8E%E9%BA%BC%E7%85%89%E6%88%90%E7%9A%84/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How is the new tax filing website made?" /><published>2018-06-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-06-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E6%96%B0%E7%89%88%E5%A0%B1%E7%A8%85%E7%B6%B2%E7%AB%99%E6%98%AF%E6%80%8E%E9%BA%BC%E7%85%89%E6%88%90%E7%9A%84%3F</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E6%96%B0%E7%89%88%E5%A0%B1%E7%A8%85%E7%B6%B2%E7%AB%99%E6%98%AF%E6%80%8E%E9%BA%BC%E7%85%89%E6%88%90%E7%9A%84/">&lt;p&gt;On May 1, 2017, designer Zhuo Zhiyuan put forward on the Join platform &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/750df7c4-550f-47ae- &amp;quot;84ee-39eba6dabb23/discuss&quot;&gt;Tax filing software is difficult to use&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, I think that the tax filing software &quot;unclear instructions, difficult interfaces, unintelligible processes, do not know how much time is wasting people in understanding this difficult system, how many customer service personnel Answer the same questions every year.&quot; He wrote in the proposal, &quot;It is easier to understand the tax filing software, more people use it, less people ask questions to trouble tax officials, or simply let the tax payment mood be more pleasant, a little more user experience. Design, isn't it?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On May 8 &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2017-05-08-%e9 %96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c-po-%e7%ac%ac%e4%b8%89%e6%ac%a1%e6%9c%88% e6%9c%83&quot;&gt;the third open government contact monthly meeting&lt;/a&gt;, the ministry of finance opened the government liaison to raise the case. the ministry of finance opened the government contact officer (po), saying that the chief of the Ministry of Finance attaches great importance to the case and understands relevant proposals. Therefore, he is willing to adopt an open attitude, listen to the opinions of the people, and hope that the people of the country will The tax filing software used can be changed as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;initial-collaborative-meeting-initial-collection-of-possible-issues&quot;&gt;Initial Collaborative Meeting Initial Collection of Possible Issues&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On May 19th, PDIS opened the [First Collaborative Conference] for the case of &quot;reporting software is difficult to use&quot; https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2017-05-19-%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E8%81%AF %E7%B5%A1%E4%BA%BA%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%83%E6%AC%A1%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8 %AD%B0). At the meeting, Liang Ruifen, chief of the Comprehensive Income Tax Section of the Internal Revenue Service of the Financial Information Center, pointed out that the Ministry of Finance will help improve the friendly interface and improve the operational procedures, and will also carefully evaluate the possibility of developing cross-platform tax filing software. Some people suggest that the interface should be open to the public to design the front end. The Ministry of Finance believes that taxation is more complicated and professional. It must be adjusted in accordance with the tax law, so that the private sector may have tax disputes, and the responsibility will be difficult to clarify. As far as the private tax filing system is concerned, it is necessary for each voucher to develop offline components for exclusive Mac users. Liang Ruifen said that the main reason for the poor experience of Mac taxing software is that it is cumbersome to install components and it takes a lot of time. It may be necessary to improve the experience by recording teaching videos, improving documentation or creating environmental testing tools. As for future planning improvement programs, consider developing a cross-platform reporting system for the Web. Finally, Liang Ruifen shared that according to the satisfaction survey at the time of reporting the tax filing system, it can be known that &quot;satisfaction and great satisfaction&quot; is as high as 94%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moderator Zhang Fangrui said that through this collaborative meeting, I hope to bring the broad-based users, such as end users, professionals and service providers, to the forefront, to clarify your problems and demands, and then imagine What kind of services are provided; further, we will consider what relative policies, regulations, and methods of transportation are available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposer Zhuo Zhiyuan believes that with the advancement of the times, more and more apps have been used, and the standard of use has been raised very much. The Mac operation mode is relatively streamlined, so users are cumbersome to install and lengthy manuals. The content lost patience. Prior to the collaborative meeting, Zhuo Zhiyuan had collected a number of questions in advance. He classified the problems as short-range, medium-range and remote, and could start from the need to improve. Zhuo Zhiyuan explained that in order to understand these problems, you can first test the ease of use, see what is good, what is not easy to do, and gradually improve every year, so that the public can feel the gradual update, and can also prepare for changes in a year or two. , &quot;Let the user never know you, to understand you.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the group discussion, the first group of friends found that the current tax filing software problem contains too many words, plus the text is more difficult, difficult to understand, may find ways to add instructions; process is not clear, ease of use Aspects should also be tested. However, in terms of satisfaction, the satisfaction questionnaire should not be used in the use, so the investigation is not complete satisfaction, only the experience of use. Zhuo Zhiyuan said that the director of the Ministry of Finance Information Center said that a team is needed and he can help set up one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second group of friends pointed out that when planning the design at the beginning, we must find ways to be included in the user. The satisfaction or usability survey may have to entrust another team to do it; the interface can also be moderately reminded. A few steps let people know how many more steps can be completed. Chen Quanxi, director of the Finance Center, added that in the future, the principles of UX and UI will be listed in the procurement case, and experts will be asked to help verify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tang Feng said that the content of this meeting will be reported to the president and the heads of relevant ministries at the government meeting. If they have any opinions, they will share with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-details-of-the-problem-will-continue-to-be-clarified-and-classified-after-the-clarification-meeting&quot;&gt;The details of the problem will continue to be clarified and classified after the clarification meeting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the first collaborative meeting, it is simply a collection of different opinions, but these opinions are collected after the event. I'm afraid it may not be consistent with the problems encountered during use; the pages mentioned are not clear on which page. Since this information is not complete enough, you need to find further steps to solve the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to confirm the status of the tax filing problem, after the collaborative meeting, the ease of use test will soon be started, hoping to understand the feelings of the current taxpayer users. The Financial Information Center and the IRS are divided to find out the different types of taxpayers, so that they can use the tax filing software they have never used before, and use them to quickly explain their problems. Through these ten usability tests, I quickly found a lot of problems in use. At the same time, we also conduct research on the details of the process before and after tax filing to understand and inventory possible problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the confirmation of these materials, the first tax filing system workshop was held very quickly on August 15th. This workshop further categorizes all the problems seen and combines them with different processes to understand each of the different steps, stages, and possible problems. In addition to sorting out the problems I saw before, I also asked the participants to help supplement the questions, and to make a preliminary convergence of the questions and to think about the initial solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;three-workshops-from-the-gathering-problem-to-the-implementation-interface&quot;&gt;Three workshops from the gathering problem to the implementation interface&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the first workshop, Zhuo Zhiyuan observed that the government colleagues were very confused. &quot;So how do I report to the supervisor tomorrow?&quot; The convenience of the people is very happy, but how do civil servants report to the superiors? How much did it cost for a day's activities? The result is a bunch of sticky stickers on the wall? The new method does not allow for the old structure, so there is a need to assist government officials to understand and integrate them. There is information to report to the superior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second workshop was held on August 23rd to solve the problem clarified in the first workshop and try to make the meeting people draw a wireframe together. The solution to the day's solution is divided into two groups, one group wants to guide the taxation pre-position, and the other group is the guidance method needed in the tax return. Zhuo Zhiyuan observed that the people attending the meeting were very happy to have the opportunity to contribute to the government, so they were very happy to start doing it. On the contrary, the government participants did not dare to do it. However, after the people finished, they were more likely to change. It is better to enter the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third workshop was held on September 6th, and the wireframe drawn by the second workshop was electronically produced and an interactive framework was created. Zhang Fangrui explained that if the paper's low fidelity prototype is directly provided to senior executives and vendors to execute, I am afraid that the space will be too large and there will be errors in implementation. Therefore, to create an interactive prototype, the imagination space is relatively small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d42bf895ff75a92d08b92dd002ab9ef794957197.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Entrance page suggested by participants in the third workshop &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-the-workshop-continue-to-work-hard-to-assist-the-manufacturer-to-modify-the-interface&quot;&gt;After the workshop, continue to work hard to assist the manufacturer to modify the interface&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After these three workshops, the follow-up meeting has been held several times to discuss how to implement the concept of tax filing software to the manufacturer. In the development. Zhuo Zhiyuan said that at the first meeting after the meeting, Guanmao was actually very opposed to such development, because this is the fourth year of the tender, and the Ministry of Finance suddenly has to re-do it. Such problems require Tang Feng to help explain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zhu Zhiyuan also found that for the manufacturers to participate in the workshop to provide advice at the beginning, in the end is to do it themselves, so the participation workshop will be lack of interest, if the manufacturer enters early, in fact, the more Finding some problems early can also make this process smoother. In order to let Guanmao enter the situation earlier, Zhuo Zhiyuan also sorted out the materials collected by the previous workshops. He divided the difficulties encountered by the people into red that would be stuck, and a yellow that would be slightly paused, listed on the table for each step. He explained, &quot;If you go online, the red must be solved, so that you know where there is a problem. Instead of talking about it for a long time, you don't know where the problem is.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also a meeting called Marathon, from early to late. That discussion began with the discussion of the prototype, from the pre-tax filing, the tax return, to the recommendations of each screen, and so on, the entire process was completed in one day. The four screens of the tax return that everyone sees now are the result of the discussion at the time. Many people don't know that the health insurance card is ready, they still need to prepare the card reader, and they also need the health insurance card password. So through this portal, let everyone know what materials need to be prepared at the beginning, and test the equipment in advance. The follow-up process will be much smoother, and it will not be found in half of the tax return. That meeting is to get all the processes one by one, so that the trade knows how to develop. Even if the team is still idle, the officials of the Ministry of Finance will monitor the tax filing status at any time. If they find that there are problems with tax filings on the online community, they will immediately follow up and report to the Ministry of Finance for revision. Zhuo Zhiyuan said that because the entrance to the new tax filing system is too beautiful, many friends who use Windows will also click on this page to apply for tax returns, but this page is for Mac and Linux users, so they will not be able to file tax returns after they enter. After Zhuo Zhiyuan discovered this problem, he immediately returned to the Ministry of Finance. The Ministry of Finance also added the words &quot;Windows users please use offline version&quot; at the top of the tax return page in a short period of time to avoid people's mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-design-process-is-more-important-than-the-results&quot;&gt;The design process is more important than the results&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zhu Zhiyuan shares, this time, four stages are organized to distinguish the design process: what is the problem, how to create the solution, the execution of the production, and the adjustment on the line. He said that in the process he was like a scout, assisting the government in exploring the whole process and clarifying the difficulties the government encountered in the project. He said that design has methods and principles from beginning to end, not just a principle. The whole process should understand the current situation, advance the goal, clarify the problem environment and the world in which it is located, so that the website can go online without being embarrassed. &quot;Everyone will tell me that he is very difficult to use. This is the conclusion, but we need to find out what happens in the process. What happens before and after? I want to see the process, not the conclusion.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2a3ca5df6c3bb079db4f0edf1aff8262d6334481.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Zhuo Zhiyuan shares the division of labor between different roles at each stage &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After understanding your situation, you will often find that many times the other party does not change, but these opinions are unreasonable requirements for the other party. How can we help everyone reach the middle balance? Is there a way for everyone to move forward? Zhuo Zhiyuan suggested: &quot;After understanding the world in which the problem lies, then propose the way to change.&quot; Design is not about making products, but about how many roles and how many contact points in the process of solving problems can improve the process together.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Tax filing software is difficult to use. Zhuo Zhiyuan, the proponent of the explosion proposal, first understands the world in which the problem lies and then proposes a change. Design is not about making a product, but about how many roles and how many touch points are needed to solve the problem.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d42bf895ff75a92d08b92dd002ab9ef794957197.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Electronic invoices are more environmentally friendly! Collaborative meeting suggestions to clarify information</title><link href="/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E5%AD%90%E7%99%BC%E7%A5%A8%E6%AF%94%E8%BC%83%E7%92%B0%E4%BF%9D-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E6%BE%84%E6%B8%85%E8%B3%87%E8%A8%8A/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Electronic invoices are more environmentally friendly! Collaborative meeting suggestions to clarify information" /><published>2018-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E5%AD%90%E7%99%BC%E7%A5%A8%E6%AF%94%E8%BC%83%E7%92%B0%E4%BF%9D!%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E6%BE%84%E6%B8%85%E8%B3%87%E8%A8%8A</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E9%9B%BB%E5%AD%90%E7%99%BC%E7%A5%A8%E6%AF%94%E8%BC%83%E7%92%B0%E4%BF%9D-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E5%BB%BA%E8%AD%B0%E6%BE%84%E6%B8%85%E8%B3%87%E8%A8%8A/">&lt;p&gt;On May 25, 2018, the PDIS team held a thirty-fourth collaborative meeting at the Treasury Information Center to discuss whether legislation could prohibit companies from printing additional coupons when invoicing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;coupons-cannot-be-recycled-and-the-sponsors-are-worried-about-adding-garbage&quot;&gt;Coupons cannot be recycled, and the sponsors are worried about adding garbage&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people have experience in getting coupons after spending in the store, and even some netizens posted dozens of centimeters on the Internet. The coupons triggered a discussion among netizens. There is a Youtuber &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_vtekdqpfxk&quot;&gt;production video&lt;/a&gt;, indicating that the current coupons cannot be recycled, and many netizens are worried that these coupons may create more garbage because they cannot be recycled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On February 20, 2018, Netizen Shuntsung Chang proposed on the Join platform &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join .gov.tw/idea/detail/22f9d6ad-0d48-4c19-99f7-1f0f4dba8830&quot;&gt;In the &quot;Electronic Invoice Implementation Work Points&quot; to add specifications, prohibiting it from using or optionally printing product offers&lt;/a&gt;), I hope that I can ban or choose to print merchandise coupons in the &quot;Electronic Invoice Implementation Tips&quot; to avoid some unscrupulous The merchandise offer is printed along with the invoice, which makes the electronic invoice greatly compromised in the expected environmental protection effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At present, the government has vigorously promoted electronic unified invoices. In the process of promoting electronic invoicing, the business people's stubs have been paperless, saving half of paper. In view of the different consumer information capabilities, if no type of vehicle is used or there is a need for paperwork, the electronic invoice will be printed on paper, and the flexible electronic printing &quot;electronic invoice certificate&quot; will replace the traditional cash register unified invoice. The method of printing the period and the track number to avoid wasting paper and taking into account the convenience of both buyers and sellers. The Ministry of Finance does not regulate the use of thermal papers for electronic invoices. However, if merchants print on sensitive paper, they must comply with the specifications in Annex 2 of Point 2 of the “Electronic Invoice Implementation Operations”, and the bisphenol A content must comply with the Ministry of Economic Affairs. Standards Inspection Bureau CNS15447 standard to ensure people's redemption and health rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the electronic invoice is printed, the shopping details or coupons and balance coupons will also be printed. In terms of shopping details, because most of the super-commercial consumers do not need details, the default is not to print the details. However, large supermarket operators usually set the system as a preset print order, because people generally buy more goods in the supermarket, and there is a need to count the goods. At this time, the details are indispensable. Coupons are usually accompanied by promotional activities. The balance vouchers are the balance records generated by the use of coupons issued by various industry players. These are important means for consumers to guide consumers and encourage consumers to return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These conference materials are written in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mqjn76eiojo68kr7epq--0qx0vjnilxlxzjxuoh3fv0/edit&quot;&gt;Issue Manual&lt;/a&gt; and sent to the participants before the meeting so that everyone can Read beforehand and clarify the context of relevant issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vTyiwejDIYO2wiaXA2lQu_4NoIOhhvOw1hER8s9c-nyuVbqLw9aO8OFaIstQYWhX98OtMWe4mkbFj7K/pub?embedded=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/ec6e667c8b9f90ab3cbe568c2b1b99a5e6141ce6.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;traditional-invoices-require-hot-carbon-ribbon-to-cause-more-pollution&quot;&gt;Traditional invoices require hot carbon ribbon to cause more pollution&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the meeting, the Ministry of Finance stated that in addition to providing mobile phone barcodes as common vehicles and regulatory vehicles, the Ministry of Finance also Vehicles that actively promote credit card payment, in order to comply with the trend and trend of mobile payment, also promote the combination of mobile payment and electronic vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many netizens wondered why the purpose of promoting electronic invoices at the time was? According to the Ministry of Finance, electronic invoices can actually save the operating costs of physical invoices, including manpower, warehousing, shipping or shipping, etc. For consumers, because these electronic invoices contain electronic information, the government can automatically The award can save the manpower for redemption and awards, and can improve the performance. For the part of the collection authority, the manpower for sales operations and data can be saved, and the Ministry of Finance can control the invoice information to reduce the risk of fraud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Finance pointed out that the current situation of the promotion of electronic invoices from 106 years, the annual invoice volume is 6.8 billion, accounting for 70% of the unified invoice, that is to say, in the business part, at least 6.8 billion savings Sheets of paper; in the consumer segment, there were 1.08 billion invoices in the same year that were not printed, accounting for 16.42% of all invoices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One participant pointed out that the old-style cashier invoice will have one original and one copy, one is reserved by the store owner, and the original is taken by the consumer, so in fact, the previous year’s usage It is 9 billion sets, and the so-called &quot;9 billion sets&quot; is the invoice size of 18 billion. He said that if the paper used to convert the past 18 billion sheets of paper into paper, it would be nearly 6,000 tons. The paper used in the 7 billion electronic invoices now has a pulp consumption of only 1,500 tons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This participant added that the hot paper will be hot and shiny, but in general, the paper must have a hot carbon ribbon to present the text, and how long the invoice is, how long the hot ribbon will be. These hot carbon ribbons are all plastic and have a more serious environmental pollution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/be9743760f56f73632bb5646e47045df1d557b79.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The EPA added that the current heat recovery paper recovery may be technically feasible, but it still depends on the cost considerations of the industry. If the recycling cost is too high, it may still be difficult to recycle, and the reduction at the source should be more effective. The EPA added that although everyone is not so ideal for incineration, the heat after incineration will be used for power generation, so the last way to recycle is not to recover from material, but to recycle energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;in-the-afternoon-i-thought-about-the-consumption-surface-and-the-environmental-protection-solution&quot;&gt;In the afternoon, I thought about the consumption surface and the environmental protection solution&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some discussion, after lunch, the afternoon grouped into the consumer and environmental aspects to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group of reports pointed out that the details should be able to try to preset not to print, print out if necessary, and reduce the printed thermal paper. In terms of coupons, the first group also suggested that consumers should be able to choose not to print out. However, you may encounter POS replacement issues, and the built-in programs need to be modified. Maybe big businesses can adopt, but small businesses may be more difficult to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the consumer side, the first group of recommendations should be targeted at consumers. The industry can also actively push eDM, recommend consumers to use eDM to request coupons, or use eDM to collect points, but may need to pay attention to The problem of capital law. At the same time, consumers themselves must work hard to promote each other and change consumer behavior to reduce waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Environmental protection, the first group of recommendations, thermal paper can be recycled, but Taiwan does not have a complete economic scale, valuable scale, overall recycling economy. In this regard, the EPA needs to communicate with paper mills and recycling companies and provide appropriate evaluation programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bdaa29304fe0caa143d5fcb8dfc8cdc0c2958b0e.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second group believes that if consumers are asked to choose whether or not to print, they will still complain when they return home and will incur more costs. If you use the app as a coupon carrier, there may be a problem with the number of gaps. Some convenience stores that attend the meeting believe that although everyone wants to be paperless, many people still need paper. Sometimes, discounts are like a wide variety, and consumers are not allowed to choose which ones to print. In particular, the store staff is very busy. &quot;It is already a busy method of the Octopus Octopus.&quot; If you forget to ask, you may be sued. Convenience stores worry that if this process is added, SOPs and training will be added, which may make the consumer experience worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the printing coupon section, the second group believes that if you do not use hot paper printing coupons, the industry may use other means to print, but not environmentally friendly. The second group suggested that the EPA should clarify that there would be no toxic substances in the incineration of the heat-sensitive paper, and the content of bisphenol A is also qualified. As for the recovery of thermal paper, it is recommended that the EPA should do research to understand the status of thermal paper recycling and publish it on the Internet for public reference. At present, the implementation of electronic invoices is more environmentally friendly than the traditional invoices, and there will be no problems with hot carbon ribbons. It is necessary for the EPA, paper mills and operators to continue to clarify, so that everyone has a clearer understanding and consensus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These opinions will be brought to the government meeting by the political commissar Tang Feng, and will be reported to the dean and the heads of relevant ministries for reference for future policy planning; the [mental map] of the meeting (https://realtimeboard.com) /app/board/o9J_kz0WAU0=/) with &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2018-05-25-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6 %94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba%e7%ac%ac%e4%b8%89%e5%8d%81%e5%9b %9b%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8%ad%b0&quot;&gt;Verbatim Record&lt;/a&gt; will also be released on the network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz0WAU0=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-problem-is-clearly-defined-and-there-is-a-good-solution-collaborative-meetings-help-clarify-issues&quot;&gt;The problem is clearly defined and there is a good solution! Collaborative meetings help clarify issues&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The civil servants who assist in organizing collaborative meetings say that they have participated in collaborative meetings before they know how to do it. A live conference needs to evaluate people, equipment, technology, software, and many details to deal with. The work of handing the microphone needs to be dealt with on the spot, and the briefing time is up. It is also a problem to remind me if the camera is not blocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The super-commercials who participated in the meeting believed that the discussion format of the collaborative meeting was different from that of the past public offices, and invited different people to participate. However, they also reminded that there are young people and old people in convenience stores. They need to consider the perception of different customers. More research is needed to clarify the issue of heat recovery. The sponsor suggested that if the site could not give a conclusion, it should be given a timetable for everyone to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A participant said that I didn't know what to do at first, but because the host had brought the topic to the issue of reduction and environmental protection, he could speak to answer everyone's doubts, so how can the host put it? It is important to bring the topic to the key person to have a chance to speak. He believes that the problem is clearly defined to know what to do, and tools and models such as collaborative meetings can find out the logic and clarify the problem, which is very good. However, this collaborative meeting did not invite more third-party payment vendors to attend, which may be a pity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The industry suggested that the government should deal with public opinion. For example, &quot;There is more people in the next door than in the past, why is it environmentally friendly?&quot; But in fact, after using the thermal paper, the total amount has decreased, but the consumption I think it is more than before because &quot;the definition of recyclability is different.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trying to use the issue card discussion, some people think that the card seems to be used less, he doesn't feel it; but some people think that it is good to discuss with paper, no need to think again, save to rewrite it. time. How to strengthen the discussion at the collaborative meeting site remains to be tested in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">After discussions at the collaborative meeting, participants found that the current electronic invoices were more environmentally friendly than before. It is suggested that the government can clarify relevant information in the future to avoid misunderstandings.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bdaa29304fe0caa143d5fcb8dfc8cdc0c2958b0e.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Local partners to create an Asian future</title><link href="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Local partners to create an Asian future" /><published>2018-05-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-05-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/">&lt;p&gt;🌏 At the beginning of May, I went to Taichung to participate in the Asia-Pacific Social Enterprise Summit of Tomorrow Asia with more than 30 international speakers from 15 countries. This event, which was hosted by the Social Enterprise, the Magpie Foundation, and the Eli International, attracted thousands of people, let me see the connection between Taiwan and the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🐟 Inside and outside the venue, more than 30 sessions and more than 60 booths have made me different and amazing. One of the most impressive is the conversation with Gavin Armstrong, founder of Lucky Little Ironfish. Before the meeting, when I asked Gavin for a personal profile, he did not talk about himself, and completely focused on the seriousness of the iron deficiency problem in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This attitude is also reflected in the operation of Lucky Little Ironfish, which is to brainstorm with the people and find local solutions – such as the “fish” they built in Cambodia, and the majority of vegetarians. India has changed to the shape of &quot;leaves&quot;. With such meticulous care, we have implemented the social innovation spirit of &quot;focusing on social issues, inspiring innovation through innovation, and leading innovation through innovation&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same feelings come from the team of &quot;Pears want to live&quot; in Taichung. They combine design, small farmers and other social enterprise partners to transform the pear stems of high pears into unique ones. Think of the pen, solve the problem of air pollution caused by burning pear stems. The social enterprise market has stringped up the local agriculture, crafts, cultural and creative ecosystems, so that friends from all over the world can see the thickness of life and social connections in Taiwan. In addition, this summit successfully enabled the speakers from all walks of life to come up with social issues such as silver hair, food and agriculture, environmental green energy, and weak employment. They not only shared how social innovation can change their lives, but also participate. The examples are presented from a complementary perspective. This kind of discussion makes the issue more stereoscopic, and it also encourages those who participate to understand how to combine multiple forces and respond to the concept of “cross-sector partnership” (SDG 17.17) in the sustainable development goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in a cross-departmental discussion, I proposed the analogy: government agencies are like NPOs (non-profit organizations). One of our missions is to recognize friends who solve social problems together and help solve problems for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌄 As Vice President Chen Jianren said in his speech, the government is working with the community to plan a &quot;social innovation action plan&quot; for the next few years. It is expected that through &quot;value cultivation, capital acquisition, innovation, regulation, and regulation, Strategies such as promoting expansion and international links, continue to integrate resources across ministries, assist friends who are interested in innovation, and find common solutions to social problems. And I am very happy to be one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/QtykZeZRe88&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/center&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷、魏守斌、薛雅婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會企業" /><summary type="html">One of our missions is to recognize friends who solve social problems together and help solve problems for everyone.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/08b38a4651ca9cf8163529894a98ad0627de97f5.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Is the Suhua Reformation the safe way for locomotives to go home? Collaborative meeting site observation</title><link href="/en/blog/%E8%98%87%E8%8A%B1%E6%94%B9%E6%9C%83%E6%98%AF%E6%A9%9F%E8%BB%8A%E5%AE%89%E5%85%A8%E5%9B%9E%E5%AE%B6%E7%9A%84%E8%B7%AF%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%8F%BE%E5%A0%B4%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Is the Suhua Reformation the safe way for locomotives to go home? Collaborative meeting site observation" /><published>2018-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-04-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/en/blog/%E8%98%87%E8%8A%B1%E6%94%B9%E6%9C%83%E6%98%AF%E6%A9%9F%E8%BB%8A%E5%AE%89%E5%85%A8%E5%9B%9E%E5%AE%B6%E7%9A%84%E8%B7%AF%E5%97%8E%3F%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%8F%BE%E5%A0%B4%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F</id><content type="html" xml:base="/en/blog/%E8%98%87%E8%8A%B1%E6%94%B9%E6%9C%83%E6%98%AF%E6%A9%9F%E8%BB%8A%E5%AE%89%E5%85%A8%E5%9B%9E%E5%AE%B6%E7%9A%84%E8%B7%AF%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%8F%BE%E5%A0%B4%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F/">&lt;p&gt;On April 27, 2018, the PDIS Group's Total Social Innovation Center held a thirty-second collaborative meeting to discuss the issue of multi-vehicle traffic passing through the Suhua reform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;suhua-changed-unplanned-traffic-locomotive-controversy&quot;&gt;Suhua changed unplanned traffic locomotive controversy&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suhua changed its name to the 9th line Suhua Highway mountain road improvement plan, started planning in 2009, started construction in 2011, On February 5, 2018, the Suao-East Australia section was completed and opened to traffic, and small cars were opened. Since Suhua Reform did not open locomotives or heavy locomotives, many locomotives protested when they opened up. They believed that the ban on locomotive traffic in Suhua was a discrimination against locomotives and caused controversy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/3/350438d6348a63737e45c0bee581b542f5cad01a_1_580x500.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Suhua change road section overview, the picture is taken from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://thbu4.thb.gov.tw/page?node=6861c85c-e12e-468e-b885-f3e9d29d40ed&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;understanding of Suhua&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This case was proposed by the user Xiu Ming on the public policy participation platform on February 5th [&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/4afaf924-a334-4d90-b580-a2183a87993c&quot;&gt;Open Suhua changed to multiple vehicles&lt;/a&gt;&quot;, after the completion of the case on february 9, the threshold of 5,000 people was crossed on march 15. after the discussion of the open government liaison meeting, it became the subject of discussion in the collaborative meeting. the core issue of the case is that taiwanese locomotives are not the same as foreigners. the ministry of communications has long planned the policy of diversion of steam locomotives. taiwan's engineering environment design targets locomotives, and the locomotive driving space has not been properly allocated, resulting in the lack of lane concept for locomotives for a long time. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iot.gov.tw/modules/publication/publication-details?node=3598166a-c839-4f0d-8beb-33c093e49de0&amp;amp;id=40b33382-06bb-4c86-9c38-2affa9c17e12&quot;&gt;motorcycle policy white paper&lt;/a&gt; By strengthening the locomotive driving education and training mechanism, or the elderly people to continue or give up the safety mechanism of using the vehicle, to strengthen the habits of the locomotive family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e24c0a6c493a601dad9bcf5a69161b898741dc37.png&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The vision and plan presented in the locomotive policy white paper &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;locomotive-rights-promotion-association-suhua-highway-is-more-dangerous-than-suhua&quot;&gt;Locomotive Rights Promotion Association: Suhua Highway is more dangerous than Suhua.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A second person from Hualien said that he would take 20 Suhua Highways a year, on this road. The impression is the word &quot;fear.&quot; The Locomotive Rights Promotion Association also believes that for the locomotive family, Suhua Highway has a more dangerous environment, high illegal sections, narrow roads, poor night vision, and longer driving time. In contrast, the Suhua-changed tunnel is much larger and the interior space is more spacious. It should be a safer road. The Gaogong Bureau had previously pointed out that the air and noise in the tunnel affected the body and mind of the locomotive knight, as well as the danger of mixed traffic between the locomotive and the car. Therefore, the Suhua was not allowed to change to the locomotive. The proponent believes that the current air in the tunnel does not affect the body, not to mention the 18-kilometer mountain tunnel in Japan. It is also open to locomotives. It is questioned that the Ministry of Communications has enlarged the small risks and ignored the Suhua Highway. high risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/91e7f22df03a7a0290dc1d350f79671540af15a3_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The second person explains the danger of Suhua Highway &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;department-of-transportation-vehicles-are-diverted-and-there-is-a-safe-road&quot;&gt;Department of Transportation: Vehicles are diverted, and there is a safe road&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications reports that the Suhua Highway has been used for more than 80 years. In the past, the design was actually not so much, so the road section The design is not very good. At present, the Suhua reform plan has improved the situation of the Suhua Highway. As for the Suhua Reform, it was hoped that the impact on the nearby ecological and settlements would be reduced when planning. Therefore, the two-way two-lane road was configured, and the vehicle type was also implemented in stages and diversions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications explained that in the future, Suhua will be replaced by large trucks, passing buses and small buses, and the Suhua Highway will be planned as a rest road, prohibiting the passage of large trucks, only sightseeing buses. , minibuses, locomotives and bicycles. In this way, the big trucks and locomotives that are most likely to be in a car accident will be diverted. These two roads will be safe roads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the opening of the locomotive into the Suhua, due to the speed limit of the Suhua, the locomotive is more likely to cause casualties after the collision, so it is not desirable to open the tunnel where the locomotive passes through the Suhua.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications also added that if the typhoon comes and the Suhua Highway is unable to pass, it will plan an emergency response plan for the locomotive to pass the Suhua reform. At that time, the Suhua Reform Association will ban the passage of vehicles above the car. After the locomotive knights gather at a certain place, they will pass through the front and rear guides to pass the Suhua reform. In the follow-up discussion, the host team clarified the arguments agreed by both parties. Everyone hopes to reduce the chance of accidents in the tunnel. It also hopes to strengthen the habits of the locomotives and reduce the casualties of the locomotives on the road.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the two sides still have some controversy about some figures. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that the national highway observation of the trial of heavy-duty vehicles found that the probability of violation of locomotives is higher than that of ordinary vehicles; however, the Locomotive Rights Promotion Association believes that the rate of casualties on the national highway is lower than that of ordinary roads. It is a safer choice. The Gaogong Bureau also pointed out that in the past, these roads were rarely discussed with the use of ethnic groups. However, the planning of the Suhua landscape road has already communicated with the local residents in advance, and the needs of the people will be investigated in advance in the future. planning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the heavy machine can have different positions on both sides of the national road, regardless of the Ministry of Communications or the Locomotive Rights Promotion Association, it agrees that the driving concept of the locomotive lane should be promoted as much as possible to reduce the danger of locomotive driving. The discussion in the afternoon discussed how to safely pass the Suhua Highway and the Suhua Reform. After the discussion, the two groups reported the results of their respective discussions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-collaboration-preliminary-research-trial-locomotive-has-a-consensus&quot;&gt;Group collaboration, preliminary research, trial locomotive has a consensus&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group began to focus on the reasons why Suhua changed to the locomotive. The Locomotive Rights Promotion Association believes that the temperature and air quality values ​​can be placed at the entrance of the Suhuahuan Tunnel to allow the locomotive riders to choose whether or not to enter. In terms of locomotive roads, more stringent regulations can be formulated to force the locomotives to Drive in a lane-like way and strictly enforce the law through the monitor. If you are concerned that the air quality is too bad, you can also plan traffic control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/d/d47f87becdf8b00993ceb9a41dd5000b81db8074_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The first group discusses the situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The General Administration of Highways believes that these packages are not enough. According to the General Administration of Highways, the Suhuahuan Tunnel has been planned to exclude locomotives from the beginning, so only one fast lane plus one emergency lane is designed. If the locomotive is to be opened, the design of the tunnel needs to be greatly adjusted, including section, lane, electromechanical, traffic control, and emergency contingency plans. The General Administration of Highways pointed out that the Yamate Tunnel in Japan has specially improved the ventilation of the tunnel in order to allow the locomotive to pass, and added water mist equipment to control the temperature inside the tunnel. In contrast, the Suhuachang tunnel is not planned to allow locomotives to pass, so air quality, temperature control, and even lanes are not suitable for locomotive traffic, because the plan does not cover the results of the locomotive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the General Administration of Highways promised that in the future, it would be possible to issue a package for the research report of the long tunnel of the locomotive, and to evaluate the feasibility of the locomotive passing the Suhua reform. These research reports can be used as reference for Taiwan's long tunnel planning in the future. As for the improvement of Suhua Highway, the discussion in the first group suggests that some sections of the road should be built with tunnels or planned for locomotive lanes. If it is really forbidden to pass large trucks in the future, it should be strictly enforced, and even buses must enter. It should also be reviewed for application. Some sections of the road should be cut and straightened, and the lighting conditions should be paid attention to, and some street lights should be added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The discussion in the second group has a clear consensus on the trial locomotive traffic. It may be possible to do a trial after all the buses have been opened, so that there will be follow-up information as an assessment of whether the locomotive is open or not. In terms of the tunnel environment, it is also necessary to pre-collect relevant standards such as temperature and air quality of tunnels passing through the international locomotive. The second group of discussions also found that the Locomotive Rights Promotion Association and the Ministry of Communications were inconsistent in the “safety” standards. It is recommended that the follow-up be evaluated together for a focused discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/1/1bd8d1a6b2dd9e99a0bb43faa3af0e5a26a2be0b_1_690x388.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The second group discusses the situation &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the future, I hope that such roads will be evaluated by scholars and organizations related to organic vehicles before planning. I hope that this opportunity will be used to set common standards for the open conditions of locomotives that everyone can accept. Not everyone's standards are different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After these comments have been completed, the political commissar Tang Feng will bring the &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kz3fwa0=/&quot;&gt;conference conclusion&lt;/a&gt; to the government conference to report to the Executive Dean and The heads of relevant ministries can get the results of these discussions as a follow-up policy study.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kz3FWa0=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VbwKBK24T_g&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;participants-are-looking-forward-to-the-establishment-of-an-early-consultation-mechanism&quot;&gt;Participants are looking forward to the establishment of an early consultation mechanism&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The congressional assistants attending the meeting said that it is very difficult to see that the executive can adopt such a form of meeting and hope that the meeting can have some concrete results. References can also be made to relevant materials. He is also very appreciative of the form of the mind map, thinking that this can see the whole picture of the issue. The official colleagues also said that the issue mental map is clearly organized, more systematic, and the context is clearer. Participants said that only the experience of public hearings had been held before. Today's collaborative meetings are somewhat different from the public hearings. The hosts are relatively neutral and hope to be used in other topics. They think that it is very good to improve the discussion environment. The public hearing will only send a letter, and I don't know if there is any positive action. Participants believe that the government should establish various consultation meetings in the spirit of collaborative meetings in the future. Listen to the voices and ideas of different people before policy planning, and also investigate different evidences. &quot;The previous consultation process should be established. Get up, otherwise this kind of controversy will be more and more.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Since Suhua Reform did not open locomotives or heavy locomotives, many locomotives protested when they opened up. They believed that the ban on locomotive traffic in Suhua was a discrimination against locomotives and caused controversy. After the discussion at the meeting, the General Administration of Highways promised to send out relevant research on the locomotive long tunnel for reference for subsequent policies. In the future, before planning, such roads also hope that scholars and organizations related to organic vehicles will join the assessment to make the planning more perfect.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b47fb29c6be0f07c367fff2529cad68e7d0e377e_1_690x286.jpg" /></entry></feed>