<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-06-29T19:05:28+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">National Champions and National Day</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%9C%8B%E6%89%8B%E8%88%87%E5%9C%8B%E6%85%B6/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="National Champions and National Day" /><published>2019-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%9C%8B%E6%89%8B%E8%88%87%E5%9C%8B%E6%85%B6</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%9C%8B%E6%89%8B%E8%88%87%E5%9C%8B%E6%85%B6/">&lt;p&gt;💯 A piece of good news for everyone — National champions of the WorldSkills Competitions (WSC) will be part of this year’s National Day Parade to receive everyone’s applause! National skill champions and vocational education of all trades will be the highlight of the National Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👷 These are not my words, but those of Executive Yuan Youth Advisory Committee member and Skills for U CEO Huang Wei-xiang. They come from the first paragraph of a post on Facebook page Craftsmanship Insights, posted on June 11.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 Most readers would know Taiwan is an “invisible champion” in many fields, serving as the mainstay of various industries. Taiwan’s famous cuisine, in particular, has received worldwide praise these two years as Taiwanese restaurants gain a presence in the Michelin Guides. However, we should all acknowledge the soul behind Taiwan’s excellent products and services in multiple fields —  the veterans cultivated by vocational education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎉 In fact, Taiwan’s skill veterans have long been shining on the international stage. WorldSkills Competitions is a biennial event hosted by the 81 member states of WorldSkills International, and the competition is so fierce it is considered to be an Olympics of skills. In the 44th WSC of 2017, Taiwan won four gold medals, one silver medal, and 27 bronze medals, with a winning rate of 88%; in 2015, Taiwan won five gold medals, seven silver medals, and 19 bronze medals, ranking 3rd place overall. These results are no doubt first class in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🥇 Regrettably, such excellent results were not well known in Taiwan. This has caused the disproportional resources allocation on the part of the government, as well as a misunderstanding of the Taiwanese on the strength of the country. Fortunately, Huang Wei-xiang’s proposal alongside with Executive Yuan President Su Tseng-chang’s prompt instructions, and Legislative Yuan President Su Jia-chyuan’s full support have allowed these veteran’s skills to come into light in the National Day celebrations this year, so that they can receive their deserved acknowledgment and acclaim from both nationals and foreign guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Today’s results are made possible by the Yuan-level Youth Advisory Committee, programmed and founded by Executive Yuan’s former Premier, Lin Chuan. They are also concrete proof to Lin’s original intention fulfilled: the members’ deep insights into public policies, active participation and suggestions have brought overall innovation to policy execution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Youth Engagement" /><summary type="html">The national team of the World Skills Competitions (WSC) will be part of this year's National Day Parade to receive everyone’s applause!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c9a67a08ad4ef90821636f4c30fea558d2880ada.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">“Quadratic Voting” and “Common Ownership Self-Assessed Tax”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%B9%B3%E6%96%B9%E6%8A%95%E7%A5%A8%E6%B3%95-%E8%88%87-%E5%85%B1%E6%9C%89%E8%87%AA%E8%A9%95%E7%A8%85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="“Quadratic Voting” and “Common Ownership Self-Assessed Tax”" /><published>2019-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E3%80%8C%E5%B9%B3%E6%96%B9%E6%8A%95%E7%A5%A8%E6%B3%95%E3%80%8D%E8%88%87%E3%80%8C%E5%85%B1%E6%9C%89%E8%87%AA%E8%A9%95%E7%A8%85%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%B9%B3%E6%96%B9%E6%8A%95%E7%A5%A8%E6%B3%95-%E8%88%87-%E5%85%B1%E6%9C%89%E8%87%AA%E8%A9%95%E7%A8%85/">&lt;p&gt;🗳 As I have &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/商周專欄-你來許願-全民-還願/&quot;&gt;mentioned earlier in this column&lt;/a&gt;, this year’s Presidential Hackathon has successfully adopted the newly invented quadratic voting (QV) system so that the voting results for proposals will be more in line with the needs of the people. Incidentally, the Colorado state legislature in the United States had also used QV to vote on their budget priorities. Taiwan and the US have achieved significant milestones in the establishment of a new form of democratic governance in administrative and representative politics respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎪 QV is part of the recent “radical” intellectual current. In 2018, the inventors of QV, Principal Researcher at Microsoft Research Glen Weyl and Eric Posner from the University of Chicago Law School co-authored the book “&lt;a href=&quot;http://radicalmarkets.com/&quot;&gt;Radical Markets&lt;/a&gt;.” In addition to the articulation of QV, the book offers five different proposals on how to change the way our societies are modeled. The book led to heated debates in academia and the community, and was featured by “The Economist” as one of the books of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📢 Glen Weyl and Eric Posner believe that with regard to public affairs, individuals tend to hold different opinions and are reluctant to share their private knowledge with others. If more people can be encouraged to share their genuine opinions through well-designed market mechanisms, the society can work collectively to find better solutions to existing problems. The QV system hinges on the idea that “a higher concentration of votes requires more points,” which encourages people to vote according to their true preferences instead of concealing their actual inclinations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💰 Another novel concept in the book is the Common Ownership Self-Assessed Tax (COST), which allows people to declare the price of their assets but for which they would have to pay an annual fixed tax. If a buyer offers to purchase the asset at the declared price, the owner of the asset cannot refuse to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🛒 The idea behind COST originated from the fact that although a person’s appraisal of value may be subjective (especially for intangible assets), this “Harberger Tax” mechanism can still effectively discourage price gouging as well as promote transparency, increase liquidity, and prevent hoarding. Through market design, people can share their actual preferences and information with others, which is the origin of the radical market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎 Glen Weyl and Vitalik Buterin (co-founder of Ethereum) launched the RadicalxChange (RxC) Foundation to advance these principles, and I was invited to work pro-bono as a board member along with the political philosopher Danielle Allen. In the past, civil servants were prohibited from holding concurrent appointments in foreign non-profit organizations, but after this restriction was lifted by the Ministry of Civil Service in October last year, all civil servants can now participate in international organizations in social innovation with the prior permission of the authorities. This was also a change that we had pushed for in the public sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 The evolution of social innovation is based on different intellectual trends. The theories and methods developed by these currents are an important means by which we can achieve our social mission. Starting from the accomplishments of QV in Taiwan and the US, I hope that my civil servant colleagues can be more active in international non-profit organizations in the future and imbibe prevailing intellectual currents more swiftly. These ideas can be applied to their official work and be a source of inspiration for social innovation in Taiwan, which will in turn be disseminated to the international community and contribute significantly to the world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Aafter this restriction was lifted by the Ministry of Civil Service in October last year, all civil servants can now participate in international organizations in social innovation with the prior permission of the authorities.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/06b90db7e18c8b1d288d2f565ae1141f14483a11.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Open Government meets Open Parliament</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E9%81%87%E4%B8%8A%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%8B%E6%9C%83/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Open Government meets Open Parliament" /><published>2019-06-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E9%81%87%E4%B8%8A%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%8B%E6%9C%83</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E9%81%87%E4%B8%8A%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%8B%E6%9C%83/">&lt;p&gt;⚖️ On May 31st, my office (Public Digital Innovation Space, PDIS) was invited by MP Ch’iu Chih-wei to take part in the preparation and implementation of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=2677074105864517&amp;amp;id=1588286501409955&quot;&gt;Public Hearing&lt;/a&gt; on “Non-Disclosure of Information under Investigation”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎙️ This is the first time that we have tried a new mode of cooperation with the Legislative branch, marking a new chapter in Taiwan’s progress of open government. On this occasion, I would like to express my gratitude and affirmation of MP Ch’iu Chih-wei’s invitation and breakthrough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🆕 There are three main points of difference between this public hearing and those in the past:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👂 First, we conducted a comprehensive series of pre-hearing interviews. Previously, organizers would invite as many stakeholders as possible to take part so that a diversity of opinions could be collected. However, an increase in the number of attendees and speakers often led to time restrictions on each speaker to express and exchange opinions at the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💬 In view of this, the PDIS host team and the committee office conducted a total of 10 interviews prior to the meeting. Through a painstaking investigation of the “non-disclosure of information under investigation regime” and detailed records, we made sure that all participants have received the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mmEO8WPOzB8XDs4V0XMSmbO39I1ZkOZDTxks0J7cx-0/edit#heading=h.jgexw6fafmb&quot;&gt;stakeholders’ complete views and suggestions&lt;/a&gt; one week in advance. In other words, the synchronization and focus of opinions had already begun before the meeting officially started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📊 Second, like other major policy issues, the context of the “non-disclosure of information under investigation regime” is profound and far-reaching. In order to enable all participants as well as viewers watching the live webcast in real time to keep up with the rhythm of the discussion and not “lag behind” in the process, we used &lt;a href=&quot;https://miro.com/app/board/o9J_kx42gKI=/&quot;&gt;Issue Mapping&lt;/a&gt; as an auxiliary tool on the hearing day. That is to say, using the charts, the non-disclosure of information under investigation regime was divided into several major programs, the implementation process and difficulties of each individual program was listed, and the causal relationship between them was linked in the correct order, so that everyone could just “click the map and follow the track” at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📜 Third, the public hearing was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M4laQWtbK4o&quot;&gt;livestreamed&lt;/a&gt; and open to online questions. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2019-05-31-%E8%90%BD%E5%AF%A6%E5%81%B5%E6%9F%A5%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%AC%E9%96%8B%E5%85%AC%E8%81%BD%E6%9C%83&quot;&gt;complete transcript&lt;/a&gt; was published on the PDIS website (&lt;a href=&quot;https://track.pdis.tw/&quot;&gt;track.pdis.tw&lt;/a&gt;) afterwards. The purpose of doing so was not only to have a complete record of the meeting but also to allow relevant discussions to continue beyond the meeting and to provide a reference guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 This successful endeavor paves the way to future cross-institutional collaborations. On the 31st, Executive Yuan member Ch’iu Chih-wei also said that he will be conducting another public hearing three months after the implementation of the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://mojlaw.moj.gov.tw/LawContent.aspx?LSID=FL068478&quot;&gt;Non-Disclosure of Information Under Investigation Act&lt;/a&gt;” on June 15th. We look forward to more Legislative public hearings and to further cooperations with MPs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">This opportunity is not only the first time we have tried a new mode of cooperation with the legislators' office, but also a new chapter in the process of Taiwan's promotion of open government and the opening of the Congress.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/ec5471e279d887cd99eb619ea8960dca9790691f.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The changing and unchanging National Palace Museum</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%85%E5%AE%AE%E7%9A%84%E8%AE%8A%E8%88%87%E4%B8%8D%E8%AE%8A/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The changing and unchanging National Palace Museum" /><published>2019-05-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%85%E5%AE%AE%E7%9A%84%E8%AE%8A%E8%88%87%E4%B8%8D%E8%AE%8A</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%85%E5%AE%AE%E7%9A%84%E8%AE%8A%E8%88%87%E4%B8%8D%E8%AE%8A/">&lt;p&gt;🏰 What crosses your mind when someone mentions the “National Palace Museum”? Is it its rich collection of treasures and solemn courtyards, or its status as an international museum with a long history that is still able to keep up with the times and dare to embrace the spirit of openness and collaboration?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Since last month, my office (PDIS, the Executive Yuan’s Public Digital Innovation Space) has officially launched a collaborative program with the Forbidden City at the invitation of the National Palace Museum’s President, Wu Mi-cha. In the next few months, we will be assisting the National Palace Museum in redesigning programs such as automatic ticket purchases, online bookings and entry lines. Through processes such as interviews with multiple stakeholders; completely recorded collaborative discussions with users and full process preliminary testing and other procedures, the National Palace Museum will be offering visitors a convenient and comfortable ticket purchasing experience that is closer to their true feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📖 This represents another step forward by the National Palace Museum on its path of openness and collaboration. In July two years ago, under the impetus of former president Lin Cheng-i, the National Palace Museum opened more than 70,000 cultural relics in the form of open materials, so that any person could download and use them free of charge. Under the continuing efforts of the two succeeding presidents, Ch’en Ch’i-nan and Wu Mi-cha, the number of open materials has reached more than 100,000. Although the speed and quantity of the materials are still not as strong as the materials offered by the Metropolitan Museum of New York or the National Palace Museum of the Netherlands, the National Palace Museum is already at the forefront and has great symbolic significance compared to similar tier museums in Asia. In the near future, the National Palace Museum will continue to expand and deepen the quality of its open materials with the support of the forward-looking infrastructure budget. This is well worth everyone’s anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔮 Furthermore, the National Palace Museum has demonstrated ingenuity in its innovative use of new media. In February last year, I “inhabited” a free-moving robot that was equipped with a 360-degree panoramic lens. In my first visit to the Southern Court of the National Palace Museum, President Lin Cheng-i and hundreds of people were online at the same time, along with viewers who watched the video afterwards. Together, we viewed the “The Pinnacle of Japanese Art: Exhibit from the Collection of Tokyo/Kyushu National Museum” which was extremely rare to see in Taiwan. For me, this viewing experience that transcended temporal and spatial constraints definitely represented a new path to enable the National Palace Museum to improve publicity and establish new paradigms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌈 The essence of the National Palace Museum lies in its steadfast preservation of its precious collection that captures fleeting beauties in moments of history; at the same time, how the Museum should adapt to the times so that more viewers can use multiple ways to gain access and understand the National Palace Museum represents not only an opportunity for us to grasp but also a responsibility for us to achieve change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">In the next few months, we will be assisting the National Palace Museum in redesigning programs such as automatic ticket purchases, online bookings and entry lines.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/776a1eae5095de146f2e2547fd26e3122ad0b9c6.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">From ”warm power” to ”global impact”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%BE%9E-%E6%9A%96%E5%AF%A6%E5%8A%9B-%E5%88%B0-%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="From ”warm power” to ”global impact”" /><published>2019-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%BE%9E%E3%80%8C%E6%9A%96%E5%AF%A6%E5%8A%9B%E3%80%8D%E5%88%B0%E3%80%8C%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%BE%9E-%E6%9A%96%E5%AF%A6%E5%8A%9B-%E5%88%B0-%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B/">&lt;p&gt;📈 In the business field, whether to invest in a product or service, the investment report rate (Return on Investment, ROI) is often an important reference. Through calculation of the financial formula, the balance of loss and benefit can be understood at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;❓But this approach is difficult to apply directly to activities of public interest. For example, the three-wheeled cars I have introduced, or the “voting guide” website, these innovations result in the public interest which is often hard to represent as the number of input into the report formula. How can we prove that these achievements are effective? This is an important issue in the innovative field of society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄With this increasing demand, many impact assessment methods have been born. For example, the Social Reporting Standard (SRS) set up by the European Union’s Social Reporting Initiative (SRI). Based on the IOOI (input / output / outcome / impact), it presents in its entirety the present organization, related activities, and the aftermath impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💵 The Social Return on Investment (SROI), like the investment rate, combines social benefit and the economic model. For example, the calculation result is $4.5, which means that for every $1 invested, you can create a social price value of $4.5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💁These new evaluation methods, just as the rate of investment and reporting, present the public welfare production of the social association department. They let all those who put into action know how much practical benefit to society and the environment is generated by what they are doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📐Many special cases in the public department will have an impact on society. Therefore, impact evaluation has also been widely valued by the government of various countries as a tool to help make decisions. As far as the “open government” is concerned, as a result of withholding the 16th goal of sustainable development of the United Nations, it has now become the principle of all countries in the world. Whether it is application of cross-departmental data, or coordination with the community of citizens, there is a great need for a global assessment, so that the community and the government can connect with each other and move forward successfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎I am now at the opening of the Open Government Partnership (OGP) Summit in Canada. This year, Taiwan is not only invited to share the experience of “Presidential Hackathon,” but will also cooperate with the scientific and technological community of citizens and representatives of the governments of various countries to make a common endorsement and mutual reference to the evaluation model, so that the effectiveness of the opening will no longer be limited to the number of data sets, but will also measure the impact on people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞There is one of the most active open communities in the world in Taiwan. Based on that, we will adopt the spirit of impact assessment. Through co-creation with citizens, we will condense it into an “Open Government National Action Plan” so that the world can see how the “warm power” of democracy in Taiwan can be transformed into “global impact” for the whole world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Through co-creation with citizens, we will condense it into an ”Open Government National Action Plan” so that the world can see how the ”warm power” of democracy in Taiwan can be transformed into ”global impact” for the whole world.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/32c68698d6b30829ea114ec939c478d0657b2ad2.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Village’s Journey to Sustainable Fashion</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%80%E5%80%8B%E6%9D%91%E8%8E%8A%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E6%99%82%E5%B0%9A%E4%B9%8B%E6%97%85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Village's Journey to Sustainable Fashion" /><published>2019-05-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%80%E5%80%8B%E6%9D%91%E8%8E%8A%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E6%99%82%E5%B0%9A%E4%B9%8B%E6%97%85</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%80%E5%80%8B%E6%9D%91%E8%8E%8A%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E6%99%82%E5%B0%9A%E4%B9%8B%E6%97%85/">&lt;p&gt;💎 Have you ever thought that jewelry we wear could be made from environmental waste?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇮🇩 A little while ago, I heard about a very interesting project—the &lt;a href=&quot;https://issuu.com/sl_studio/docs/fashion_village_lab_roadmap&quot;&gt;Fashion Village Lab&lt;/a&gt; in Cigondewah, Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 This year, in order to promote regional sustainable development, the Ministry of Economic Affairs is conducting the first &lt;a href=&quot;https://apses.asia/award/apply&quot;&gt;Asia-Pacific Social Innovation Cooperation Award&lt;/a&gt;. It has received entrants from as many as 13 countries, and ended up with 62 teams in total. The Fashion Village Lab is one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏭 Indonesia is a garment manufacturing powerhouse. Bandung City accounts for 40% of the national garment output value. Bandung’s Cigondewah area is a distribution center for international brand manufacturers. Five years ago, the Bandung Creative Cities Forum (BCCF) and Dutch researchers established a presence there because the factory’s waste pollution was affecting the quality of life for local workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸After learning more about it, they combined local community strength to launch the Fashion Village Lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;♻️The lab’s vision is to create a self-sufficient “circular creative ecosystem”: transforming solid pollutants produced in factories into products such as building blocks and jewelry; collaborating with students in architecture and design-related fields to build stores that showcase production processes, retain land for dyeing plants, develop new materials, and conduct experiments on sustainable textiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌐 The success of the Fashion Village Lab is based on an effective “3C formula”: connecting with local stakeholders (Connect), inviting everyone to collaborate (Collaborate), and finally incorporating businesses and stakeholders to expand innovative business models (Commerce). This formula is based on the field work of the Bandung Creative City Forum in the past ten years. It has successfully connected the stakeholders in production, government, study, research, and society, and has also made Bandung a member of the UNESCO “Creative City” network (&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.unesco.org/creative-cities/bandung&quot;&gt;UCCN&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎁 Now that the Fashion Village Laboratory is in its final stages, and the Kawasan Wisata Sandang Cooperative, which is run by local women and youths, is ready to sell the finished products of the circular economy through the lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞 This year, Cigondewah’s team was unanimously recognized by a panel of experts from Japan, Singapore, Australia, Thailand, and India, and was awarded the “Special Jury Prize”. They will come to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://apses.asia&quot;&gt;Asia Pacific Social Enterprise Summit&lt;/a&gt; in May this year to accept the award. Everyone is welcome to come to Kaohsiung to meet these excellent teams and explore new possibilities for regional revitalization.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">This year, Cigondewah's team was unanimously recognized by a panel of experts from Japan, Singapore, Australia, Thailand, and India, and was awarded the “Special Jury Prize”.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/718c3380c9efb619b63f7f850fb2a1ed368a5c81.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Keep moving up, gazing at the starry sky</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%8C%81%E7%BA%8C%E5%90%91%E4%B8%8A-%E4%BB%B0%E6%9C%9B%E6%98%9F%E7%A9%BA/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Keep moving up, gazing at the starry sky" /><published>2019-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%8C%81%E7%BA%8C%E5%90%91%E4%B8%8A,%E4%BB%B0%E6%9C%9B%E6%98%9F%E7%A9%BA</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%8C%81%E7%BA%8C%E5%90%91%E4%B8%8A-%E4%BB%B0%E6%9C%9B%E6%98%9F%E7%A9%BA/">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“For four million years, in the midst of the collision between the Eurasian Plate and the Philippine Sea Plate, Taiwan has always been looking up and gazing at the stars -  this is going to continue into the future.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌌 One month before I took office in 2016, I was fielding questions from different quarters on a Q&amp;amp;A platform. At the time, a reporter from Hong Kong’s TVB asked me: “What is your vision for Taiwan? When you think of “Taiwan”, how do you imagine her future is like?” This is the answer I gave at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⛰ The pushing motion of the earth’s plates has created a fault zone under the surface. This is the main reason that Taiwan has so many earthquakes. For me, the civilization living on this land has the same “fault”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇹🇼 In 1987, the government of the Republic of China lifted the martial law that had lasted for almost 40 years. “Authority” and “freedom”, the two major plates that had engaged in a long-term conflict, had finally shifted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗽 In the thirty years since the lifting of the martial law, and despite the frequent conflicts between the generation accustomed to authority and the generation accustomed to freedom, the process of mutual integration and pushing has also created the most open and free civil society in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔢 Traditional dialogues about issues are mostly divided into a positive side and a negative side. It is easy for the discussions to become polarized or to lead to confrontation and mutual attack. In recent years, however, the assistance of digital tool has created multifaceted channels of discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📈 Pol.is is one of the widely used tools. Every person can put forward ideas on the topic page and let other participants express their feelings about each other’s ideas with three options: “Agree”, “Disagree”, and “Skip”. The system follows the participants’ opinions and voting results and calculates the distance between the participants’ and other people’s positions. After that, it uses a visual method to express a spectrum that includes everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞 In 2015, on the digital economic regulation adaptation platform (vTaiwan), the stakeholders discussed the policy direction of “diversified taxis” through Pol.is. This type of design went beyond the previous head-counting, win-or-lose methodology. Apart from making different opinions obvious at a glance, participants might also see that the people who disagree with them are also people whom they know, thereby recondensing the consensus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone is bound to have a different answer to the question that the reporter asked me at the time. Currently, this approach gives us an opportunity to find out each other’s differences and common grounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💬 Starting from the vTaiwan experience, the open source communities in Taiwan, Canada, Spain, Denmark, and Singapore have continued to improve Pol.is, strengthen the information security, implement EU privacy regulations, and add automatic translation capabilities. Since April this year, the American Institute in Taiwan (AIT) and the Executive Yuan have cooperated to readjust the foundation of Pol.is and construct a “digital dialogue platform” ([talkto.ait.org.tw] (https:/ /talkto.ait.org.tw)).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌐 This is also the first time that the US and Taiwan have opened up issues about which both sides are concerned and invited the public to join the discussion. I believe this will become a model for the future: enabling international cooperation is no longer just an agreement between governments; rather, it is also a synergy between the people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">This is also the first time that the US and Taiwan have opened up issues about which both sides are concerned and invited the public to join the discussion.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6e04f33dd4d43861d4f334783209baec38a555bc.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">There is a consensus on the opening of fishing ports: fishing should not affect the operation of fishermen</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%BC%81%E6%B8%AF%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98-%E9%87%A3%E9%AD%9A%E4%B8%8D%E6%87%89%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E6%BC%81%E6%B0%91%E4%BD%9C%E6%A5%AD/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is a consensus on the opening of fishing ports: fishing should not affect the operation of fishermen" /><published>2019-04-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-04-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%BC%81%E6%B8%AF%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98:%E9%87%A3%E9%AD%9A%E4%B8%8D%E6%87%89%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E6%BC%81%E6%B0%91%E4%BD%9C%E6%A5%AD</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%BC%81%E6%B8%AF%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98-%E9%87%A3%E9%AD%9A%E4%B8%8D%E6%87%89%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E6%BC%81%E6%B0%91%E4%BD%9C%E6%A5%AD/">&lt;p&gt;On January 30, 2019, netizen Yu Zeyu proposed on the public policy network participation platform, requesting [&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail /eac7403b-ec58-4337-a605-7930ff2e8e2c&quot;&gt;full opening of fishing port and fishing and construction of fishing platform&lt;/a&gt;&quot;. In his proposal, he pointed out that the port area is a safe fishing place. The government should fully open the fishing port for fishing. At the same time, he also proposed some management rules, such as setting up life-saving equipment, prohibiting fishing from excessive winds, prohibiting throwing garbage, and not blocking. The fishing boat should enter and exit, and the fishing boat should be allowed to pass. After the proposal was approved on February 26th, the Executive Yuan conducted an appeal analysis and feasibility assessment based on the key points of the open government liaison, and the main appointing machine officially responded on the platform on April 26; therefore, PDIS On April 3, 2019, a collaboration meeting was held at the Badouzi Fishery Club to discuss the feasibility of this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;fishing-port-disputes-are-more-than-full-of-fishermen-and-fishermen&quot;&gt;Fishing port disputes are more than full of fishermen and fishermen&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fishermen group pointed out that according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://law.moj.gov.tw/lawclass/lawall. in article 18 of the aspx?pcode=m0050010&quot;&gt;fishing port law&lt;/a&gt;, the competent authorities of the fishing port shall, in the absence of obstructing the operation, safety and pollution of the port area, designate areas and provide relevant measures to publicize the fishing of the public. However, after the regulation was finalized, there were only 222 first-class and second-class fishing ports in Taiwan, and only 18 fishing ports were open for fishing. Most of the fishing ports did not open fishing for fishing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fce01f91eefae8e261b5acf88f9fc44f147eef04.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Fishing fishermen fishing in fishing port &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the 2019 budget review, the Legislative Yuan's Internal Affairs Committee requested the Sea Guard to actively impose penalties on illegal fishers. The patrol of the sea patrol caused the anger of the fishermen, so this proposal was only made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the public policy network participation platform proposal, the fishermen also went to the Legislative Yuan and the Executive Yuan. At the meeting on March 21, Chen Qimai, the deputy dean of the Executive Yuan, listened to the instructions of the fishermen. In the next two months, the Ministry of Communications, the COA and the fishing friends should discuss 50 places in the fishing port, commercial port or other areas of the whole Taiwan. Areas that can be legally fished are intervened by government forces to plan and manage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of the large number of people expected to be concerned about this meeting, in addition to the main venue on the second floor of the Badouzi Fishery Club, the second venue was also opened in the third floor conference room on the same day, and the discussion of the first venue was watched live. And use Sli.do to ask questions, collect the second venue and watch the opinions of the live broadcasters online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8b49804d25485a1fff5aae486851b1db1c92ea32.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Second venue &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-mutual-trust-between-the-two-sides-has-not-been-established&quot;&gt;The mutual trust between the two sides has not been established.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Deputy Director of the Fisheries Department first clarified at the collaboration meeting that the &quot;50 fishing spots&quot; mentioned by Vice President Chen Qimai is not &quot;50 fishing ports&quot;. It may also be a region such as a commercial port, not just a fishing port. The Fisheries Department also pointed out at the meeting that at present, the &quot;Fishing Port Law&quot; has designated designated areas, and relevant measures have been formulated to announce the opening of the people's fishing regulations. It is recommended to follow the existing mechanism. As for the fishing port where the fishing area has not been designated, it is planned that the competent fishing authorities will collaborate with the fishing club, fishing group and sea patrol unit to discuss whether to demarcate the open area. The content of the consultation shall include the management mechanism and fees. The relevant management measures may be jointly negotiated and developed by the competent authority in conjunction with the fishery associations and sea patrol units, and shall be managed by the fishing group autonomously, and the relevant fees shall be charged to the fishermen according to the principle of user payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/angelhaung66/videos/2941953119178916/&quot;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt; provided by the proponent pointed out that the fishing port was built by all taxpayers and should not be monopolized by fishermen. He believes that the fishing port is relatively safe. The government should open a fishing port for everyone to fish. He also suggested planning relevant management rules. The practice of throwing rubbish and entering other people's ships in the port area should be severely punished according to law, and should not affect the navigation channel. However, he also pointed out that the littering in the port area is not only for the fishermen, but the fishermen or tourists may also throw rubbish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sponsor's statement triggered the anger of the representatives of the Fisheries. They pointed out that the fishing port was not only funded by the government. When it was built, the fishermen also provided land and funds, and still have to pay fees. As for the littering in the sponsor's film, they also clarified that it was using non-toxic paint to clean the vessel. Many fishermen’s representatives have suffered from the pain. Fishing in the fishing port has caused many chaos. In addition to throwing garbage, some fishermen like to use the method of throwing and throwing on the fairway to make the fishing boat stir the fishing line, causing many disputes; By driving away the fish, the fishermen will also be dissatisfied with the fishermen. The fishery club also pointed out that after the opening of fishing, once the danger occurs, the family of the fishermen may seek compensation from the government, and there will be many problems in the future. However, the participants in the second venue were angered by some of the speeches, and many fishermen rushed to the first venue, hoping to express their opinions. Although there was some confusion on the spot, some fishermen still spoke and expressed their concerns and asked their fishermen’s representatives to withdraw from the protest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;consensus-fishing-should-not-affect-fishermens-operations&quot;&gt;Consensus fishing should not affect fishermen's operations&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fishermen's group clarified that they fully agreed that fishing activities could not affect the safety of vessels entering and sailing, and agreed that they should not cause mess in the fishing port. Some of the fishermen’s unruly behavior should be curbed by heavy penalties. For safety issues, in addition to self-confidence safety, fishermen should be required to wear life jackets, non-slip shoes when fishing, or insurance can be introduced to allow the fishermen to have corresponding claims after the danger occurs. The fishermen group also proposed that they can try to manage by means of a fishing license or a fishing ticket. Although the atmosphere of the two sides was quite hot, after the moderator intervened and clarified, there was a certain degree of consensus on the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7b6878475d29d832108bf0fdd4eb914f822adc3a.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The host clarified the issue &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fishing rights meeting pointed out that the Taichung Port area is for them to fight for open fishing. I am very grateful to the Taichung Fisheries for providing assistance to the local authorities. They also reiterated that the fishermen’s group should abide by the relevant regulations and agree that There is a reasonable charging mechanism to allow the fishing area to have more resources to manage, and it is recommended to open the plastic bottle to allow the fishermen to go fishing, instead of using the crew card, and also allow the fishermen to have additional income and create a win-win situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The local government statement pointed out that the Executive Yuan should not promise to open 50 fishing spots before discussing it, which is likely to cause public concern; they pointed out that the control measures given to local governments in Article 18 of the Fishing Port Law There should be a nationally stipulated regulation; for the same violations in different regions, such as fishing ports and commercial ports, the current penalty is too large, and there should be a uniform standard of punishment. In terms of regulation, civil servants cannot ask the public to confirm their identity during inspections. They must be checked together with the sea patrol and the police. This is also a difficult point in the use of public power. The New Taipei City Government offered to propose that they would use the Caili Fishing Port as a model fishing port to open up discussions on management rules.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kaohsiung City Government also shared the way to successfully discuss the criteria for designing. The fishery and fishing groups were invited to discuss with the local government. Although the atmosphere was hot, it did get the open standards and specific management that everyone agreed to. rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the collaborative meeting procedure, when entering the group discussion, the representatives of the Fisheries Association thought that the way of speaking in turn was very good, and they hoped not to enter the group discussion; however, under the insistence of the moderator, everyone continued the dialogue and focused in group discussions. discuss. The group discussion topics are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to plan a fishing area for the fishermen to fish in the appropriate fishing port area under the condition that the fishermen and fishermen are accepted by the fishermen?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How to implement the operation and management rules of the fishing area in the fishing port so that the fishermen's operations are not disturbed, the fishermen are self-disciplined and safely fishing, and the administrative organs are also easy to manage?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the Fisheries Association proposed that the open principles of other regions should be discussed, the moderator considered that the meeting should focus on the fishing port and therefore did not agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;both-parties-agree-that-they-should-take-into-account-multiple-positions&quot;&gt;Both parties agree that they should take into account multiple positions&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After more than an hour of discussion, it is followed by a group report that reports on the views and consensus of the group discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/31a1c1aa07de6ef7afbdc88a16f2835cfd234874.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the first question, how to plan some of the appropriate fishing areas for the port area, the two groups have similar views: the competent authorities, the fishermen's association and the fishermen's group should be invited to participate in the survey and decide where to decide. Suitable for opening and making announcements. There should also be obvious indications for open areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the second question, how to implement the relevant business management rules, the two groups have different views. The first group believes that the competent authority should first propose some restrictions, and then the self-managed fishing group will propose a business plan, and after discussion with the fishermen and fishermen of each place, they will open again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0bc8e196b4c62417f139f1ef6926468a853014b6.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group report &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the second group was concerned that it was easy to have problems with the group of fishermen. He is worried that the management of the fishermen's group may cause the group to be accused by the fishermen of being profitable, questioning the opaque use of funds; some fishermen's groups are not appropriate and may use it to collect money. In the event of a danger to the fisherman, the family may sue the management unit to the court, causing trouble; when the law is illegal, it is difficult for the fisherman group to have public power to restrict the fisherman. Therefore, he suggested that it should be managed by the government to avoid disputes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these questions, the second group of discussions pointed out that it may be necessary to disclose the corresponding plan to ensure that the corresponding services are implemented and the finances should be open and transparent. In addition to insurance, the safety part should also establish safety regulations and exemption clauses. In terms of public power, it may be necessary to formulate correspondingly reasonable penalties and encourage fishermen to record video. However, some local governments have pointed out that even if they are operated by the government, they often fail to catch people. Therefore, it may be necessary to build a video recorder and conduct personal control to ensure that illegal passengers can be caught.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-meeting-has-a-consensus-that-the-fishery-club-and-the-fishing-group-are-thankful&quot;&gt;The meeting has a consensus that the fishery club and the fishing group are thankful&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, the Director General of the National Fisheries Association said that he is very happy to see that everyone has a consensus at today’s meeting, and he agrees that the fishing port cannot open fishing. It affects the safety of fishing vessels and the safety of navigation. It is also hoped that the fishing boats will jointly safeguard the cleanliness and beauty of the fishing port in the future. He pointed out that many fishermen who are concerned about the issue are worried that the inappropriate opening will lead to endless conflicts in the future. He hopes that the rules will be set in the future, and the management unit will find out that if it is done well, it will relieve the fishermen's doubts. He also suggested that each fishing port has different characteristics. Whether it is open or not, it must go to the grassroots to communicate with fishermen and fishermen. They will also make good suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e2b8da9d43a67857f9fbf4421ae539d4ce9f5840.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Speech by the Director General of the National Fisheries Association &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fishing rights club also said that it is very grateful to the platform of the collaborative meeting for everyone to have the opportunity to communicate. After the opening of the future, the fishing group can not enjoy it without fulfilling its obligations. He suggested that in addition to the fishing port in the future, it is possible to plan to build a sea fishing platform in the area near the windmill, and also allow the fishermen to take the fishing boat to the platform for fishing. The proponents pointed out that they are not in a hurry to ask for 50 fishing spots. They are willing to wait a little longer if they can communicate and improve planning and management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tang Feng said at the end, thank you very much for the patience and suggestions of today's participants. The collaborative meeting can be carried out smoothly, and it means that everyone has the willingness to dialogue. This is the first step towards success; since the audience has a complete record, He will bring these opinions back to the Executive Yuan for confirmation and faithful response to the views of the parties to the Dean, Vice President and Zhang Jingsen Political Commissar of the future planning. The relevant topic manuals, mind maps, verbatim drafts, and live videos of the conference will also be made available on the Internet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/dd3b8b9c4c4299a34b1b803aaa54773d4001c877.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Tang Feng clarification &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tang Feng also clarified again that Vice President Chen Qimai means to count 50 fishing areas on the coastline of the country. It is definitely not a fishing port. He also wants to ask the friends of the fishery club to bring the message back to friends. know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;participants-are-worried-about-archery-and-then-painting-the-target-and-expecting-future-communication-to-be-implemented&quot;&gt;Participants are worried about archery and then painting the target and expecting future communication to be implemented&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someone said that the meeting was a bit out of control at first, but the result was ok, he was surprised to use the team The discussion analyzes the problem once and finds the solution in a short time in a logical and orderly manner. However, they also suggest that friends from the grassroots should have a way to express their opinions and participation, otherwise they will feel bad. On the agenda, another participant said that there had been a rumor that 50 open phishing was selected, and I was worried that this would become the first archery target and the beauty of the collaborative meeting communication. &quot;The government has to do something that everyone feels, not to solve small problems and create big problems.&quot; He greatly appreciated the proceedings of the meeting and was very pleased that the meeting had a consensus and expected the meeting consensus to be implemented in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">On April 3, 2019, PDIS held a collaborative meeting at the Badouzi Fishery Association to discuss the feasibility of fishing in the fishing port. The fishing group and the representatives of the participating fishermen reached a consensus that the fishing port should not affect the operation of the fishermen. Relevant planning should also invite all parties to discuss and implement relevant management.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/fce01f91eefae8e261b5acf88f9fc44f147eef04.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Starting from Zero: Taiwan’s democratic innovation</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E9%9B%B6%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B-%E8%87%BA%E7%81%A3%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Starting from Zero: Taiwan's democratic innovation" /><published>2019-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E9%9B%B6%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B-%E8%87%BA%E7%81%A3%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E9%9B%B6%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B-%E8%87%BA%E7%81%A3%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0/">&lt;p&gt;📹 In 2012, the Executive Yuan launched the “Economic Power-Up Plan” advertisement, which was based on the phrase “Everything is accelerating”. Four citizen hackers were dissatisfied with the government’s rash response and decided to respond with positive actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗺 They made the “Central Government Budget Visualization” project to make the data easy to understand, and the public can also rate and comment on each budget. This project is one of the most active citizen technology communities in the world today, and the prototype of the g0v government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🤝 Since then, Taiwan has taken the core concept of “taking technology to the realm of people’s lives, rather than requiring people to enter the space of technology”, incorporating the spirit of collaboration into government governance. I therefore decided to accept the government’s invitation to serve as an executive public official, promote administrative innovation, and create digital cooperation possibilities between citizens and the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌻 We believe that the government must first trust the people to have the power to set agenda, and the people can make democracy work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📶 The existence of democracy and freedom in Taiwan is not taken for granted. In 1987, the Government of the Republic of China lifted the martial law for nearly 40 years. The first presidential direct election was held in 1996. At this time, Taiwan has a fairly solid civil society. People are used to joining the community and NGOs to join hands with community partners. It is also this year that the Internet has begun to rise around the world, and Taiwan is no exception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚅 Taiwan’s main island is 394 kilometers long and takes about one and a half hours from Taipei to Kaohsiung. This kind of geographical environment gives us great advantages in the development of the network. “Broadband human rights” is the core policy of the current government. The Internet access rate of people over the age of 12 is 87%. For the 23 million people in Taiwan, using the Internet as a public discussion space is more natural than voting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 “The generation of customary authority” and the “generation of habitual freedom” coexist in the Taiwan society, and there are still conflicts and running-in. And we find “practical collaborative participation” as a common link in democracy in the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗺 Since the g0v project is openly licensed and encouraged to change, the Executive Council’s “Join” online participation platform and the Taipei City Government have successively adopted the budget visualization system as the basis for the “participatory budget”, making it easy for the public to understand budget allocation and engage in discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙋 The Join platform, which attracts more than 4 million people, the function is certainly not limited to watching the budget. Join’s “ideas” area is open to public proposals, as long as there are 5,000 people signing the e-petition, the relevant responsible department will have to respond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔗 In addition, we have set up an “Participation Officer” team in each ministry as a single window for inter-departmental cooperation and a bridge between the public sector and the citizens. For example, whenever there is a proposal on the Join platform, we will hold a collaborative meeting, inviting the people and relevant government departments to join the discussion, in order to unite the consensus of all parties, and then innovate the policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍲 Currently, we have had more than 40 collaborative meetings, whether it is improving online tax filing software, local medical resources, or exploring the fisheries and ecological balance of marine national parks, inviting stakeholders to collaborate and find a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄 We have found that the public sector needs to adopt social innovation, and it needs to form an ecosystem for the government, the community, and the enterprise, and has a clear mechanism to regulate its maintanence and accountability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏖 At the same time, only by letting the legal system keep pace with the times and backed by regulations can we promote social innovation and drive regulatory innovation. Therefore, the Executive Yuan launched the “Innovation Laws and Regulations Sandbox Platform” in 2017, allowing people who are engaged in innovation to experiment freely within a certain period of time without being bound by regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 The vTaiwan platform, initiated by the g0v community, is another important driver of the establishment mechanism. Prior to the government’s proposed Diversified Taxi Service Program in 2016, Uber’s legitimacy was discussed enthusiastically through an online collaboration mechanism. In 2018, vTaiwan succeeded in facilitating the adjustment of platform economic regulations and the legalization of financial supervision sandboxes and unmanned sandboxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏡 We also apply the spirit of the “ecosystem” to the development of Taiwan. This year’s “Local Creative National Strategic Plan” is a combination of local production, government, learning, research, and society. It calls on residents to take concrete actions to participate in and unite their own visions of the local community as an ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞 These practices not only lower the threshold of democracy, but also the process of mutual understanding between the people and the government. When people see that collaboration can bring results, they can stimulate their willingness to participate and give substantial feedback, and even further use and change to contribute to the citizen technology community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏  One of the goals of the Executive Yuan’s Public Digital Innovation Space (PDIS) is to bring such experimental results to friends around the world. Therefore, we continue to visit cities such as New York, Toronto, Madrid, Tokyo, and Hong Kong, and co-organize workshops with the civic tech community to share the democratic and innovative mechanisms of the PO system and collaborative meetings with friends around the world. The plan for g0v has also been transplanted abroad, such as “budget.g0v.it” in Italy, established in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚰 Today’s international cooperation is no longer just an agreement between the government and the government, but also a synergy between the people and the people. For example, in the “Presidential Hackathon” held for the first time last year, the “Water Saviors” team composed by Taiwan Water Company and folk friends used the “deep learning” algorithm to introduce the experience of the missing masters into the machine. Successfully made a water pipe inspection system with an accuracy rate of 70%. The team was therefore invited by the New Zealand government to participate in the local acceleration plan to provide the New Zealand people with solutions to the water shortage problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 Many people often ask me: What will democracy look like in the future? I believe that the future of democracy will be based on the “culture of listening.” Taiwan has a highly developed online environment with no historical burdens, so it is possible to experiment with a new model of democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎨 As President Tsai Ing-wen said when he took office three years ago: “Before, democracy was a showdown between two opposing values. Now, democracy is a conversation between many diverse values.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗽 At a time when the world is rethinking basic elements of governance, Taiwan’s democracy, in which the people actively participate and the government responds in the here and now, is demonstrating the synergy and dialogue of the new citizenship in the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">Audrey Tang, Digital Minister of Taiwan, believes that the most important thing is the spirit of public dialogue and collaboration.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c2061a5cd697744724d0462de0dd744ce66aea4f.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">You make a wish, the whole people are ”willing to”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%A0%E4%BE%86%E8%A8%B1%E9%A1%98-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91-%E9%82%84%E9%A1%98/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You make a wish, the whole people are ”willing to”" /><published>2019-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%A0%E4%BE%86%E8%A8%B1%E9%A1%98,%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91%E3%80%8C%E9%82%84%E9%A1%98%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%A0%E4%BE%86%E8%A8%B1%E9%A1%98-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91-%E9%82%84%E9%A1%98/">&lt;p&gt;This coming Saturday is the 33rd hackathon of g0v. When I saw the &lt;a href=&quot;https://g0v-jothon.kktix.cc/events/g0v-hackath33n&quot;&gt;registration page&lt;/a&gt;, I was reminded of my first time organizing a hackathon. That was 14 years ago, and I organized 14 hackathons in a year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌐 At that time I had saved some money, and I decided to give myself a half-year sabbatical so that I could dedicate myself to the implementation of the new programming language Perl 6. When I put this idea forward on the Freenode platform, hundreds of people quickly joined me as collaborators. As a result, I traveled all over the world and made friends with many like-minded people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏃 What is a hackathon? It combines the words “hack” and “marathon.” “Hack” refers to the quick completion of tasks as well as problem-solving, and if it involves a group of people like in a “marathon” who are trying to accomplish the same thing, the activity is referred to as a hackathon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🕯 In the process of organizing these 14 hackathons, I had a realization: for a lot of things, you just need to get down to work and then openly say, “this is really difficult, can I get some help?” Saying this works everytime, and people who have knowledge in this area will definitely offer their help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🧞 Years later, I saw this idea reflected as the “wishing well” in &lt;a href=&quot;https://grants.g0v.tw/&quot;&gt;g0v Civic Technology Grants&lt;/a&gt;. The wishing well allows anyone with ideas to publicly submit a “wish” so as to attract the attention of others who are interested and are willing to help to accept the idea and help to realize it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆This year marks the second annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://presidential-hackathon.taiwan.gov.tw/en/&quot;&gt;Presidential Hackathon&lt;/a&gt;, and we have also set up a “public wishing well.” Anyone with good ideas but lack the time to work on them can submit a wish for others who have the time to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗳 Voting on proposals for the Presidential Hackathon will be based on the newly developed Quadratic Voting (QV) from 2013. You will have a fixed amount of points, and you can cast a vote for ideas that you like, which would require 1 point. If you cast 2 votes for an idea, it would require 4 points, and so on, i.e. the points required will be the square of the number of votes. Since casting a larger number of votes for the same proposal will require a lot more points, the winning proposal is bound to be the most eagerly anticipated one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏙 At the same time, proposals for prefectural and city chiefs are also open this time. Many people who work in social innovation often tell me that Taiwan’s many localities have their own unique traits, and there is significant variation in the challenges these places face as well as their own hidden potential. Allowing the respective local chiefs to participate in raising questions allow specific local needs to be addressed, so that the area’s citizens can come together to find a solution for the problems they face and make the area better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 African Bantu languages have a word “Ubuntu” which means that people do not exist alone, but require mutual support and assistance in order to complete and surpass themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 14 years ago, I was awakened to the principle of connecting different parts of the world by helping others. I hope that more people can share what they have learned and contribute their own strengths so that every hackathon can be the embodiment of the Ubuntu spirit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">This year, the second ”Presidential Hackathon” will be held. The ”Citizens Wishing Pool” is also set up. If you have a good idea, you can make a wish and let people who have time come to collaborate.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4cd56562902bcfb46c32309b5d438cbdc4d1dc2d.jpeg" /></entry></feed>