<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-04-06T07:03:50+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Keep up, look up at the stars</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/04/05/%E6%8C%81%E7%BA%8C%E5%90%91%E4%B8%8A-%E4%BB%B0%E6%9C%9B%E6%98%9F%E7%A9%BA.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Keep up, look up at the stars" /><published>2019-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/04/05/%E6%8C%81%E7%BA%8C%E5%90%91%E4%B8%8A,%E4%BB%B0%E6%9C%9B%E6%98%9F%E7%A9%BA</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/04/05/%E6%8C%81%E7%BA%8C%E5%90%91%E4%B8%8A-%E4%BB%B0%E6%9C%9B%E6%98%9F%E7%A9%BA.html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“For four million years, in the collision between the Eurasian plate and the Philippine Sea plate, Taiwan has continued to look upwards and look up at the stars - this is the future.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌌 2016 I took office the previous month On the Q&amp;amp;A platform, I asked questions from all walks of life. At that time, a reporter from Hong Kong TVB asked me, “What is your vision for Taiwan? When you think of “Taiwan” in your mind, how do you imagine her future?” This was when I gave The answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⛰ The plate pushes and creates a fault zone under the surface, which is the main cause of many earthquakes in Taiwan. For me, the human civilization in this land has the same “fault”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇹🇼 In 1987, the government of the Republic of China lifted the martial law for nearly 40 years, and the two major sectors of the long-term conflict were “authoritarian” and “freedom”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗽 In the past 30 years, although the generations who have experienced authoritarianism and customary freedom have often disagreed, the process of mutual integration and pushing has also created the most open and free civil society in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔢 Traditional conversations on topics, most of which divide participants into positive and negative sides, tend to be polarized during discussion, and even lead to confrontation and attack. But in recent years, with the help of digital tools, there has been more ways of dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📈 Pol.is is one of the widely used tools. Everyone can put forward ideas on the topic page, and then let other participants express their feelings about each other’s ideas with the three options of “Agree”, “Disagree”, and “Skip”. The system visualizes the spectrum of all people based on the participants’ opinions and voting results, and then calculates the distance between the participants and other people’s positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞 In 2015, on the digital economic regulation adaptation platform (vTaiwan), stakeholders discussed the policy direction of “diversified taxis” through Pol.is. This kind of design is beyond the past few people’s heads, and wins and loses. In addition to presenting different opinions at a glance, participants can also see people who disagree, may be people they know, and then reunite consensus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🤝 When the reporter asked me questions, everyone’s answers must be different. Today, through this approach, we have the opportunity to find out the intersection of each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💬 From the experience of vTaiwan, the open source communities in Taiwan and Canada, Spain, Denmark, and Singapore continue to improve Pol.is, strengthen security, implement EU privacy protection regulations, and add automatic translation capabilities. . Since April this year, the cooperation between the American Association of Taiwan (AIT) and the Executive Yuan has been based on the newly adjusted Pol.is to build a “digital dialogue platform” (&lt;a href=&quot;https:/ /talkto.ait.org.tw&quot;&gt;talkto.ait.org.tw&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌐 This is also the first time that the issue of mutual concern between Taiwan and the United States will be open to the public to discuss. I believe this will become a model for the future: letting international cooperation is no longer just an agreement between the government and the government, but also a synergy between the people and the people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會創新" /><summary type="html">This is also the first time that the issues that the two sides will pay close attention to will be open to the public to discuss.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6e04f33dd4d43861d4f334783209baec38a555bc.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Starting from Zero: Taiwan’s democratic innovation</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/03/12/%E5%BE%9E%E9%9B%B6%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B-%E8%87%BA%E7%81%A3%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Starting from Zero: Taiwan's democratic innovation" /><published>2019-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-03-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/03/12/%E5%BE%9E%E9%9B%B6%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B-%E8%87%BA%E7%81%A3%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/03/12/%E5%BE%9E%E9%9B%B6%E9%96%8B%E5%A7%8B-%E8%87%BA%E7%81%A3%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0.html">&lt;p&gt;📹 In 2012, the Executive Yuan launched the “Economic Power-Up Plan” advertisement, which was based on the phrase “Everything is accelerating”. Four citizen hackers were dissatisfied with the government’s rash response and decided to respond with positive actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗺 They made the “Central Government Budget Visualization” project to make the data easy to understand, and the public can also rate and comment on each budget. This project is one of the most active citizen technology communities in the world today, and the prototype of the g0v government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🤝 Since then, Taiwan has taken the core concept of “taking technology to the realm of people’s lives, rather than requiring people to enter the space of technology”, incorporating the spirit of collaboration into government governance. I therefore decided to accept the government’s invitation to serve as an executive public official, promote administrative innovation, and create digital cooperation possibilities between citizens and the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌻 We believe that the government must first trust the people to have the power to set agenda, and the people can make democracy work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📶 The existence of democracy and freedom in Taiwan is not taken for granted. In 1987, the Government of the Republic of China lifted the martial law for nearly 40 years. The first presidential direct election was held in 1996. At this time, Taiwan has a fairly solid civil society. People are used to joining the community and NGOs to join hands with community partners. It is also this year that the Internet has begun to rise around the world, and Taiwan is no exception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚅 Taiwan’s main island is 394 kilometers long and takes about one and a half hours from Taipei to Kaohsiung. This kind of geographical environment gives us great advantages in the development of the network. “Broadband human rights” is the core policy of the current government. The Internet access rate of people over the age of 12 is 87%. For the 23 million people in Taiwan, using the Internet as a public discussion space is more natural than voting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 “The generation of customary authority” and the “generation of habitual freedom” coexist in the Taiwan society, and there are still conflicts and running-in. And we find “practical collaborative participation” as a common link in democracy in the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗺 Since the g0v project is openly licensed and encouraged to change, the Executive Council’s “Join” online participation platform and the Taipei City Government have successively adopted the budget visualization system as the basis for the “participatory budget”, making it easy for the public to understand budget allocation and engage in discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙋 The Join platform, which attracts more than 4 million people, the function is certainly not limited to watching the budget. Join’s “ideas” area is open to public proposals, as long as there are 5,000 people signing the e-petition, the relevant responsible department will have to respond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔗 In addition, we have set up an “Participation Officer” team in each ministry as a single window for inter-departmental cooperation and a bridge between the public sector and the citizens. For example, whenever there is a proposal on the Join platform, we will hold a collaborative meeting, inviting the people and relevant government departments to join the discussion, in order to unite the consensus of all parties, and then innovate the policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍲 Currently, we have had more than 40 collaborative meetings, whether it is improving online tax filing software, local medical resources, or exploring the fisheries and ecological balance of marine national parks, inviting stakeholders to collaborate and find a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄 We have found that the public sector needs to adopt social innovation, and it needs to form an ecosystem for the government, the community, and the enterprise, and has a clear mechanism to regulate its maintanence and accountability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏖 At the same time, only by letting the legal system keep pace with the times and backed by regulations can we promote social innovation and drive regulatory innovation. Therefore, the Executive Yuan launched the “Innovation Laws and Regulations Sandbox Platform” in 2017, allowing people who are engaged in innovation to experiment freely within a certain period of time without being bound by regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 The vTaiwan platform, initiated by the g0v community, is another important driver of the establishment mechanism. Prior to the government’s proposed Diversified Taxi Service Program in 2016, Uber’s legitimacy was discussed enthusiastically through an online collaboration mechanism. In 2018, vTaiwan succeeded in facilitating the adjustment of platform economic regulations and the legalization of financial supervision sandboxes and unmanned sandboxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏡 We also apply the spirit of the “ecosystem” to the development of Taiwan. This year’s “Local Creative National Strategic Plan” is a combination of local production, government, learning, research, and society. It calls on residents to take concrete actions to participate in and unite their own visions of the local community as an ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞 These practices not only lower the threshold of democracy, but also the process of mutual understanding between the people and the government. When people see that collaboration can bring results, they can stimulate their willingness to participate and give substantial feedback, and even further use and change to contribute to the citizen technology community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏  One of the goals of the Executive Yuan’s Public Digital Innovation Space (PDIS) is to bring such experimental results to friends around the world. Therefore, we continue to visit cities such as New York, Toronto, Madrid, Tokyo, and Hong Kong, and co-organize workshops with the civic tech community to share the democratic and innovative mechanisms of the PO system and collaborative meetings with friends around the world. The plan for g0v has also been transplanted abroad, such as “budget.g0v.it” in Italy, established in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚰 Today’s international cooperation is no longer just an agreement between the government and the government, but also a synergy between the people and the people. For example, in the “Presidential Hackathon” held for the first time last year, the “Water Saviors” team composed by Taiwan Water Company and folk friends used the “deep learning” algorithm to introduce the experience of the missing masters into the machine. Successfully made a water pipe inspection system with an accuracy rate of 70%. The team was therefore invited by the New Zealand government to participate in the local acceleration plan to provide the New Zealand people with solutions to the water shortage problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 Many people often ask me: What will democracy look like in the future? I believe that the future of democracy will be based on the “culture of listening.” Taiwan has a highly developed online environment with no historical burdens, so it is possible to experiment with a new model of democracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎨 As President Tsai Ing-wen said when he took office three years ago: “Before, democracy was a showdown between two opposing values. Now, democracy is a conversation between many diverse values.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗽 At a time when the world is rethinking basic elements of governance, Taiwan’s democracy, in which the people actively participate and the government responds in the here and now, is demonstrating the synergy and dialogue of the new citizenship in the 21st century.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">Audrey Tang, Digital Minister of Taiwan, believes that the most important thing is the spirit of public dialogue and collaboration.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c2061a5cd697744724d0462de0dd744ce66aea4f.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: You make a wish, the whole people are “willing to”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/03/07/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%A0%E4%BE%86%E8%A8%B1%E9%A1%98-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91-%E9%82%84%E9%A1%98.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: You make a wish, the whole people are &quot;willing to&quot;" /><published>2019-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-03-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/03/07/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%A0%E4%BE%86%E8%A8%B1%E9%A1%98,%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91%E3%80%8C%E9%82%84%E9%A1%98%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/03/07/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%A0%E4%BE%86%E8%A8%B1%E9%A1%98-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91-%E9%82%84%E9%A1%98.html">&lt;p&gt;The second Saturday of March is the thirty-third hackathon of the government at g0v. I saw &lt;a href=&quot;https://g0v-jothon.kktix.cc/events/g0v-hackath33n&quot;&gt;registration page&lt;/a&gt;, remembering myself when I first hacked. That was fourteen years ago, I had 14 hackathons in one year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time, I saved some money and decided to put my half-year leave into the implementation of the new programming language Perl 6. When I put forward this idea on the Freenode platform, hundreds of partners soon joined the collaboration, so I traveled all over the world and made friends with like-minded people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is Hackathon? It is a combination of Hack + Marathon. Hack refers to the quick completion of tasks, problem solving, and if a group of people “marathon” gather together, what they want to do is hackathon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the process of running these 14 hackathons, I found a flaw: Many things need to be implemented, and then openly said, “This is really too difficult. Can you help me a little?” When I talk about this sentence, I will try my best and everyone who knows this will help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After many years, I saw the specific appearance of this idea in the “Wish Pool” system of &lt;a href=&quot;https://grants.g0v.tw/&quot;&gt;g0v Citizenship Technology Grants&lt;/a&gt;. The wishing pool allows anyone with an idea to “make a wish” to the public - to write down ideas, and anyone with a willingness and interest can claim and complete the idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This year, the second “&lt;a href=&quot;https://presidential-hackathon.taiwan.gov.tw&quot;&gt;Presidential Cup Hacker&lt;/a&gt;” will be held, and the “Citizens Wishing Pool” will be set up. It is a good idea but it is a good idea. If you don’t have time to do it, you can make a wish and let people who have time come to collaborate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposal for the President’s Cup will be based on the newly invented Quadratic Voting (QV) in 2013: everyone has a fixed amount of points. If you like a case, vote for it. It only takes 1 point, but if you want to vote for two votes, you will spend 4 points, and so on, that is, the number of points paid is the square of the number of votes. In the case that the more votes are more expensive, the election is bound to be the most eagerly awaited proposal of the society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, this time, the prefecture and city leaders’ proposal is also opened. Many friends who do social innovation work often tell me that there are thousands of different places in Taiwan, and the difficulties and potentials vary greatly from place to place. It is precisely for the heads who know the local needs and problems to ask questions, so that the whole people can find answers together and inject live water into the place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 African Bantu has a word called Ubuntu, which means: people do not exist alone, but through mutual support and help, they can complete and surpass themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;连结 By helping others to connect the world, this is what I realized fourteen years ago. I hope that more people can share what they have learned and what they have contributed, and that every hacking is a practice of Ubuntu spirit.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>唐鳳、彭筱婷</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="社會創新" /><summary type="html">This year, the second &quot;Presidential Cup Hacker&quot; will be held. The &quot;Citizens Wishing Pool&quot; is also set up. If you have a good idea, you can make a wish and let people who have time come to collaborate.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4cd56562902bcfb46c32309b5d438cbdc4d1dc2d.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Guarding a Cup of Coffee in Dawushan</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/31/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%AE%88%E8%AD%B7%E5%A4%A7%E6%AD%A6%E5%B1%B1%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%80%E6%9D%AF%E5%92%96%E5%95%A1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Guarding a Cup of Coffee in Dawushan" /><published>2019-01-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/31/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%AE%88%E8%AD%B7%E5%A4%A7%E6%AD%A6%E5%B1%B1%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%80%E6%9D%AF%E5%92%96%E5%95%A1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/31/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%AE%88%E8%AD%B7%E5%A4%A7%E6%AD%A6%E5%B1%B1%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%80%E6%9D%AF%E5%92%96%E5%95%A1.html">&lt;p&gt;Early this month, the National Development Council invited the new Executive Yuan Youth Advisory Committee for a &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2019-01-11-%E5%9C%B0%E6%96%B9%E5%89%B5%E7%94%9F%E6%94%BF%E7%AD%96%E5%BA%A7%E8%AB%87%E6%9C%83&quot;&gt;policy discussion&lt;/a&gt; on the “National Strategic Plan for Regional Revitalization.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://advisory.yda.gov.tw/02/userpost/27&quot;&gt;Fuyung Xiyi&lt;/a&gt;, a participant, shared his experience of running a computer information labor cooperative. He said when introducing science and technology to support local industrial reform, people should work together to cultivate indigenous talents to foster a sustainable culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;☕ It reminds me of a cup of coffee I tasted in Pingtung. This cup of coffee came from the Ulaljuc tribe, with a story about the creation of the original countryside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⛰ In 2009, the Morakot typhoon destroyed the old Taiwu tribe and the village changed its name to Ulaljuc after moving away. In order to rebuild, the people began to explore the mountains. They found the Japanese coffee garden and chose “organic boutique coffee” as their development goal. Today, there are 126 hectares of coffee grown in Taiwu Township, by 178 coffee farmers. The Coffee Industry Development Hall opened in 2016 is the only post-production factory in the country that can verify the back-end processing of organic coffee; students from all over the world can study here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 Now, Taiwu coffee has spread its aroma around the globe. The International Coffee Appraisal (Coffee Review) evaluated Taiwu Nature Typica at 93 points in 2016 and ranked it among the top three in the Asia-Pacific region, making it one of the most representative coffees of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏠 One of the keys to Ulaljuc’s success lies in the establishment of the Pingtung Native Taiwu Coffee Production Cooperative, which uses its own brand to integrate upstream and downstream industrial chains, supporting each other and marketing together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔗 According to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://coop.moi.gov.tw/&quot;&gt;Ministry of the Interior website&lt;/a&gt;, there are currently more than 4,000 cooperatives of 10 categories in Taiwan, including production, distribution, labor, and consumption. In addition to selling goods, cooperatives can also operate insurance and provide services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📜 In the past, there were different interpretations of laws and regulations, and unclear demarcations between coop members and employees. Coops often ran into a wall when they approached government contracts because they could not provide “documents of employment.” Therefore, we are coordinating with the Ministry of the Interior, the Ministry of Labor, and the Public Construction Commission to add a clause on “protection of the rights and interests of cooperative members” in the contract template for the purchase of labor services. In that way, the authorities can better understand the nature of co-ownership and co-governance in cooperatives. We can also recognize the labor rights and interests of members and give full play to the strength of the cooperative economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍯 According to the Paiwan people, in ancient times, the sun laid eggs in a pottery kettle with a hundred-step snake guarding it. Finally, a man and a woman were hatched, that is, the ancestors of the tribe. As a result, the Ulaljuc Village Monument is surrounded by three symbols: the sun, a hundred-step snake, and a pottery kettle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌞 The Coffee Hall and the Cooperative, like hundred-step snakes and pottery kettles, guard the reborn Ulaljuc tribe. I sincerely hope that with the support of the regional revitalization strategy, the development of all parts of Taiwan will shine like the sun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">The Coffee Hall and the Cooperative, like hundred-step snakes and pottery kettles, guard the reborn Ulaljuc tribe.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/9/99b5176d6b7441531c1fb302aacc48f10481b2ca_2_1380x802.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How to improve the open government contact system? Consensus camp discussion possible solution</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/26/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E6%94%B9%E5%96%84%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E8%81%AF%E7%B5%A1%E4%BA%BA%E5%88%B6%E5%BA%A6-%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98%E7%87%9F%E8%A8%8E%E8%AB%96%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to improve the open government contact system? Consensus camp discussion possible solution" /><published>2019-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/26/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E6%94%B9%E5%96%84%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E8%81%AF%E7%B5%A1%E4%BA%BA%E5%88%B6%E5%BA%A6%3F%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98%E7%87%9F%E8%A8%8E%E8%AB%96%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/26/%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E6%94%B9%E5%96%84%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E8%81%AF%E7%B5%A1%E4%BA%BA%E5%88%B6%E5%BA%A6-%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98%E7%87%9F%E8%A8%8E%E8%AB%96%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E8%A7%A3%E6%B3%95.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://po.pdis.tw&quot;&gt;Open Government Liaison System&lt;/a&gt; has been in operation for more than two years now, and many ministries have experience in connecting through the open government liaison system, as well as many ministries. Due to the joining of the Join platform, there is cooperation with PDIS to hold collaborative meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to understand the working conditions of these open government liaisons (POs) and how PDIS can assist them in the future, PDIS held two echelon consensus camps on January 18 and 25, 2019. I hope that PO can talk about the current working conditions, and let the new PO have an opportunity to understand how the open government contact system (hereinafter referred to as the PO system) works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This consensus camp is planned to be a collaborative meeting. PDIS is used as a business unit to make its own proposals, and each PO is invited to discuss as a participant. The purpose of the establishment of PDIS is to achieve &quot;public-private trust&quot;. Therefore, by introducing the four complementary elements of &quot;opening&quot;, &quot;transparency&quot;, &quot;responsibility&quot; and &quot;conclusion&quot; as a tool, I hope that it will be facilitated. The result of &quot;public-private trust&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beginning of the PO system is the hope that the past problems can be solved. In the past, the success of the Join platform was often in the business unit, so the experience also accumulated in the business unit, the need to have a dedicated person to force; at the same time, this person should also become a window of the inter-ministerial meeting. PDIS's expectation for PO is to host, translate and record. It is hoped that it can host meetings of multi-stakeholders. It can translate public sector press releases into words or languages that can be understood by ordinary people. Finally, the conference should record as much as possible. Words or video records, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tang Feng once helped translate the &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://audreyt.github.io/trust-zh-tw/&quot;&gt;Evolution of Trust&lt;/a&gt;&quot; game. In the game, if you cooperate for a long time, people will There is no incentive to deceive each other. The PO system gives the windows of the various ministries to the dedicated people. The original intention is also to hope that through long-term cooperation, there will be opportunities for mutual trust between the ministries, and then actively cooperate on the issues of inter-ministerial meetings. However, in the long-term operation, the PO system only uses the form of collaborative meetings to solve the problems raised by the joint platform on the Join platform. Is there an opportunity to improve this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in the process of organizing the conference, there are actually many points that need improvement. After each collaborative meeting, they will feel that the public sector is very sincere in the interviews of the sponsors. Such meetings make them feel good; but the participating ministries all say that the preparation period for the collaborative meeting is really tired. Time is pulling longer. Is there a way to spend less time but achieve a certain effect? Or does the division of labor have room for adjustment? At the same time, in the process of preparing for the meeting, how is the authorization of PO in the ministry, and how to coordinate the various business organs and inter-departments?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further on the selection of collaborative conference topics, in addition to the issues on the Join platform, can there be more topics raised by the ministry, and it can really help the conference to help the ministry to formulate the future. Policy, or assist the ministry to solve business needs?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lai Zhixiang finally asked, if PDIS has the right to propose, will it be better? He asked, if there is a proposal, you can let PDIS intervene in some of the issues that are being dealt with, or let cases that some ministries would not dare to mention can be dealt with. If there is no better solution, is this better?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senior PO of the Welfare Department shared that there are several types of cases in their ministry. The first category is the “pushing point” of the Join platform. After 5,000 people have been involved in the case, about 50 cases a year, and 3 cases entered the collaborative meeting. Since the final result PO will be checked, the direction is usually in the direction of the research, and the comparison can actually respond to the point of concern of the public. The second category is the part of the high-level designated collaborative meeting. In this year, the big case of the Welfare Department was the development of the health insurance card virtual card program. A total of three collaborative meetings were held, and there will be a pilot project in the future. The third category is self-governing within the ministry. If it involves openness, live broadcast, transparency, and participation, PO is the object of consultation within the department. The demand may come from the chief or colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/5/51f2ac63b3a4b2de6fce81398f6c6ad264c29786.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Wei Fu Department shared experience &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The PO believes that the notices and even the cases on the first type of Join platform will continue to appear. This is more like continuous operation and foundation construction, and continues to promote the construction of open operations. The second type of high-level designation, which compares Like an emergency. In this type of case, there are many internal communication units and relatively high costs. On the other hand, there are more trial space on the edge of the case. She pointed out that there is a whole set of collaborative meeting rooms, but it is impossible to introduce a whole set of topics, so now I try to put the elements of these collaborative meetings, such as the diversity of the participants, the private can sign up, the third party, or It is a more open and transparent record, etc., and is dismantled and introduced as needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She expects that the future collaboration meeting can be more flexible and smaller, so that the ministry will have the opportunity to make independent attempts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c4ac5099d0d4987a72b3011c962a788457300a37.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; group discussion &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a round of discussions between the public PO and the group discussion in the afternoon, both groups aimed at two directions to strengthen PO: one is to seek the authority of the chief, and the other is to have energy to convince the business unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the part of persuading the chief, although the PO system has been in operation for a year, many of the heads of the ministry are still unfamiliar with the PO system and collaborative meetings. Although quarterly meetings are held every season, they participate in the quarterly meetings. The sergeant often has a lot of contact with the collaborative meeting, and he has no feelings, or the governor who visits each time is different, so he is not clear about the situation. Under the unclear situation of the sergeant, the authority of the PO will be limited, and it is difficult to promote the open government culture that the PO system wants to bring up and down. This part may require PDIS assistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/e2258e4fdbe4201b93b4531e61be9cde9fa9629c.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Participation report &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the part of the business unit, it may be necessary to give incentives, such as telling them that through the process of collaborative meetings, you can suspend the sensational stagnation, or let the public understand the difficulties of the government. Some people think that if PO proposes to handle collaborative meetings, business units will be more stressed because they are already busy. If the bottom-up launch fails, PO will face great pressure. But if there are 5,000 people, the legitimacy will be enough, or proposed by PDIS, perhaps a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to let the chief and the business unit know, or many of the education training is a solution, it is also possible to encourage the ministry that allows the PO system to be relatively complete to participate in the collaborative meeting with the department that is more unfamiliar with the system. At the same time, in the PO system, we can also consider the combination of the existing sensational and congressional liaison system, so that PO has the opportunity to know the major sensation and direction that the ministry or the Executive Yuan has recently been concerned about. Master the development of the situation. It has been mentioned that some departments will have more sensational pressures and will promote the PO system more vigorously because of external forces. However, if they are closer to the aides, the driving force for PO will be smaller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/1/10b2907ef4bc2eaec8deb0f2fea4e98402ac357e.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Participation report &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, they also share, perhaps consider converting the public hearings or related meetings into a form similar to a collaborative meeting, incorporating some elements of an open government, or even replacing them with collaborative meetings, and perhaps implementing public-private trust. The main goal.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">In order to understand the working conditions of these open government liaisons and how PDIS should assist them in the future, PDIS held two echelon consensus camps on January 18 and 25, 2019, hoping to let PO talk about the current working conditions. It also gives the new PO an opportunity to understand how the Open Government Liaison System (hereinafter referred to as the PO System) works. Participants suggested that striving for the authority of the chief executive and convincing the business unit's energy is the direction for improving the open government liaison system in the future.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c4ac5099d0d4987a72b3011c962a788457300a37.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week column: Five pillars to keep the winter warm</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/03/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%95%E6%89%80%E5%86%AC%E6%9A%96-%E4%BA%94%E5%AE%B6%E7%82%BA%E9%84%B0.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week column: Five pillars to keep the winter warm" /><published>2019-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-01-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/03/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%95%E6%89%80%E5%86%AC%E6%9A%96-%E4%BA%94%E5%AE%B6%E7%82%BA%E9%84%B0</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2019/01/03/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%95%E6%89%80%E5%86%AC%E6%9A%96-%E4%BA%94%E5%AE%B6%E7%82%BA%E9%84%B0.html">&lt;p&gt;Towards the end of the year, I attended a special gathering at the Social Innovation Lab: “Taiwan GSG NAB warmup meetup.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇬🇧 Most people probably don’t know what “GSG” and “NAB” stand for. The full name of GSG is “Global Social Impact Investment Steering Group”. Launched by Britain’s Sir Ronald Cohen at the G8, the group is dedicated to connecting the financial, commercial, and public welfare communities. Since 2015, it has established National Advisory Boards in 21 countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 Why is it called “warmup meetup”? Ray Chen, general manager of the Living Water Enterprise Investment Development Company which helped facilitate this meeting, has exchanged with GSG several times to study the possibility of establishing NAB in Taiwan. In February 2018, NTU Professor Feng Yan, Corey Lien  of the B Corp Association, and Ray Chen were invited to Seoul to take part in the first “Asia-Pacific Impact Investment Workshop”, jointly organized by GSG, British Culture Council, and the United Nations Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific (UNESCAP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 The two-day workshop started off with the launch of the Korean NAP. With the assistance of Ray, I participated through telepresence in the discussion of NAB representatives from various countries, and have gained a better understanding of GSG. It turns out that GSG hopes to promote Impact Investing to drive the capital market and achieve the UN sustainable development goals, which will lead to more social innovation and social entrepreneurship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📈 GSG argues that social and environmental challenges often come from the adverse long-term consequences in the pursuit of short-term profits by investors. In addition to socially responsible practices corporations implement to avoid harm and promote public interests, Impact Investment hopes to go further and encourage innovative teams committed to proposing solutions to global problems, to scale mature solutions and build credibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👪 GSG emphasizes five pillars of the social innovation ecosystem: “demand, supply, intermediaries, ecosystem enablers, and government”. Many people in Taiwan have long been working in these five areas and there are sufficient conditions to establish NAB. Everybody’s enthusiasm is reflected in this small gathering — there were more than a dozen attending representatives from the financial industry and investment funds alone. If all goes well, Taiwan’s NAB will have the chance to become GSG’s fourth member in Asia at the end of this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙏 In the past year’s column, I have shared with you 12 stories — &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%82%BA%E6%9C%89%E6%84%9B%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%BA-%E8%A7%A3%E6%B1%BA%E5%9B%B0%E9%9B%A3/&quot;&gt;Social Enterprises&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%8D%E8%A6%81%E8%87%89%E5%85%AC%E5%9C%92-%E7%9A%84%E8%83%8C%E5%BE%8C/&quot;&gt;Regional Revitalization&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%BD%BF%E5%91%BD%E7%84%A1%E5%83%B9-%E5%95%86%E6%A9%9F%E7%84%A1%E9%99%90/&quot;&gt;Land Rehabilitation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E5%B8%B6%E5%8B%95%E6%B3%95%E8%A6%8F%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0/&quot;&gt;Food Reuse&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%9C%A8%E5%9C%B0%E5%A4%A5%E4%BC%B4-%E5%85%B1%E5%89%B5%E4%BA%9E%E6%B4%B2%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/&quot;&gt;Circular Economy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%9C%A8%E9%B1%89%E8%91%89%E7%9A%84%E5%95%9F%E7%A4%BA/&quot;&gt;Indigenous Culture&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-AI-%E8%88%87%E8%80%81%E5%B8%AB%E5%82%85/&quot;&gt;Smart Pipelines&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E8%88%87%E7%84%A1%E4%BA%BA%E8%BB%8A%E5%85%B1%E8%88%9E/&quot;&gt;Autonomous Vehicles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%BE%9E%E8%AA%B0%E5%BE%97%E6%8C%87%E5%8D%97/&quot;&gt;Civic Technology&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%99%82%E9%9B%A8%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%88-%E9%81%A9%E7%95%B6%E5%85%B6%E6%99%82/&quot;&gt;STEM Education&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%B4%E5%9C%8B%E7%84%A1%E9%82%8A%E9%9A%9B-%E5%90%8C%E8%81%B2%E5%92%8C%E8%80%85%E5%A4%9A/&quot;&gt;Human-computer Interaction&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C/&quot;&gt;Democratic Innovations&lt;/a&gt;. In the new year, I hope that more people can support Taiwan’s warm power and establish a closer partnership with the global sustainable community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">If all goes well, Taiwan's NAB will have the chance to become GSG's fourth member in Asia at the end of this year.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/0/0eb95b1632fcac7b85a35f55c75fabbfa5a9f585_2_1332x1000.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Insufficient energy for the invigilators, aggravated penalty, and a collaborative meeting focused on public-private partnerships</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/28/%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E5%93%A1%E8%83%BD%E9%87%8F%E4%B8%8D%E8%B6%B3-%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E5%8A%A0%E9%87%8D%E7%BD%B0%E5%89%87%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E8%81%9A%E7%84%A6%E5%85%AC%E7%A7%81%E5%8D%94%E5%8A%9B.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Insufficient energy for the invigilators, aggravated penalty, and a collaborative meeting focused on public-private partnerships" /><published>2018-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/28/%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E5%93%A1%E8%83%BD%E9%87%8F%E4%B8%8D%E8%B6%B3-%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E5%8A%A0%E9%87%8D%E7%BD%B0%E5%89%87%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E8%81%9A%E7%84%A6%E5%85%AC%E7%A7%81%E5%8D%94%E5%8A%9B</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/28/%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E5%93%A1%E8%83%BD%E9%87%8F%E4%B8%8D%E8%B6%B3-%E5%8B%95%E4%BF%9D%E5%8A%A0%E9%87%8D%E7%BD%B0%E5%89%87%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E8%81%9A%E7%84%A6%E5%85%AC%E7%A7%81%E5%8D%94%E5%8A%9B.html">&lt;p&gt;On December 27, 2018, PDIS held the &quot;42nd Collaboration Meeting of Open Government Liaisons&quot; in the reporter's office of the Council of Agriculture (https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/ 2018-12-27-Opening the 42nd Collaboration Meeting of Government Liaisons), Discussion &lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/ef7dfc73-465a-4f32-9835 -c2695ad75f7b&quot;&gt;Aggravation of Animal Protection Law&lt;/a&gt; The case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This proposal was proposed by the netizen &quot;Su&quot; on August 10, 2018. After three days of approval, the proposal was met. The proposal pointed out that at the end of May, there was a continuous cat incident in Yanji Street. In July, there was a repeated dog-walking incident in Taipei’s Guangfu Bridge. In early August, there were also incidents in which Pingdonglang dogs were killed. The incidents of abusing waves and waves were frequent. It is proposed to aggravate the rules for ill-treatment of stray animals, fully publish names and photos, enforce psychological treatment, and cover all animal medical expenses, hoping to ensure that vulnerable stray cats and dogs will not be harassed, hurt or even killed by those who are concerned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-number-of-times-of-the-law-is-too-imbalanced&quot;&gt;The number of times of the law is too imbalanced&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The law has been revised up to 13 times in the past 20 years since the Republic of China 87. Some scholars believe that most of the current provisions of the law Related to pets, the rest of the standard density of economic animals and experimental animals is not enough, I am afraid that it has been out of balance. At the same time, some of the relevant provisions of the Sports Protection Law are difficult to implement, and there are many differences with the Wildlife Conservation Law. At present, in dealing with such cases of animal cruelty, the biggest problem is that it is difficult to find the perpetrator or to obtain evidence. Therefore, it is worthwhile to discuss whether the practice of aggravating the intensity of the penalty can improve the animal abuse. In addition to this, some provisions of the current insurance law are too strict, I am afraid that there is a big difference between the actual effect and the actual effect, and may even be difficult to implement. There have always been suggestions in the society that a start-up summit should be held, or a state-level insurance law modification committee should be comprehensively reviewed and combed with the provisions of the law or related laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proposal proposes &quot;enhancement of penalties&quot; as a solution, but the problem that I hope to solve is &quot;to ensure that stray cats and dogs are not harassed, hurt or even killed by people who are interested&quot;, so we begin to analyze the problem from this perspective. The problem of animal cruelty was pre-prevented and post-processed, and a topic manual was prepared for the participants' reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This topic is divided into two aspects: pre-existing prevention and post-processing. In terms of prevention in advance, it includes life education, breeding of pets, adoption registration, responsibility of the owner, and the containment of stray animals and TNVR. In the case of post-processing, it includes penalties and legal issues, as well as issues that are difficult to convict. These topics are written into the issue manual after the host team has assembled the current issues and the direction of government administration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-coa-proposes-to-improve-the-animal-protection-needs-to-strengthen-the-function-of-the-invigilator&quot;&gt;The COA proposes to improve the animal protection needs to strengthen the function of the invigilator&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the meeting, the proponent pointed out that there will be a relatively large number of dynamic insurance cases every other time, but generally The public cannot understand why the parties often fail to pay off? He believes that public institutions and the people seem to have a large generation gap. He believes that the general public is too easy to get pets. If it is too easy to adopt, everyone will easily throw away cats and dogs, leading to conflicts between stray animals and wild animals. He thinks this is the result of many people taking pets as items. He hopes to make Taiwan a better country by teaching everyone to respect life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Agriculture Committee mentioned that the law of sports protection has been amended more than ten times since the Republic of China in 1987. In fact, the damage caused by the intentional or negligent animal has been divided into four different penalties. The most serious penalty is the use of drugs and firearms, which cause the animals to die in full. There will be one to five years of imprisonment, and a fine of more than 500,000 and less than 5 million will be required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, for the part of the perpetrator, the competent authority may publish the name, photo and facts of the violation. If it is slaughtered or deliberately caused animal damage, and its limbs are severely disabled, or lose vital organs, there are also two years of imprisonment, as well as criminal penalties of more than 200,000 and less than 2 million. Deliberately caused animal damage, but did not cause serious death or death, or negligence caused serious animal death or injury, or even death, this part of the fine of more than 15,000 yuan, less than 75,000 yuan fine. Deliberate harassment of animals, although it did not cause an animal to have an injured or physiological condition, or deliberately negligent did not cause animal death, this part will be fined NT$3,000 or more and less than RMB15,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/48530d8e77a51c4d83e27e2a3126ebaee9292eae.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The COA reports the current challenges of the law &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Council pointed out that compared with the current criminal law, the child law and the welfare law for the elderly, the animal protection law is not relatively light in the criminal law or the part of the penalty. In terms of penalties in the six countries, Taiwan’s Republic of China penalties are relatively the heaviest in terms of criminal law or part-time fines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The COA shared the results of the survey in May 2018. There are 153 mobile protection workers in Taiwan. On average, each person has more than 1,100 mobile insurance complaints to be processed each year. Dealing with each case, approximately one can be assigned to the survey time of 1.64 hours. The pressure of the first-line staff is very high, which also causes the turnover rate to become high and the experience is difficult to accumulate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The COA shared that in recent years, it has actively promoted the quality of public shelters, and hopes that in the future, it will be able to reverse the impression of the whole animal shelter society and transform towards education, tourism and leisure. For private places where a large number of cats and dogs are kept in large numbers, the COA will also establish a model of graded counseling, hoping to improve the environment and animal welfare of private breeding sites in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Council recommended that the professionalism and functions of the overall grassroots animal protection personnel be improved so that public power can be effectively extended and the public feels. The COA also shared that this year's animal protection law has included the animal life education part into the 12-year curriculum. In the future, we hope to cooperate with the Ministry of Education and the community to provide opportunities for the society to have access to life education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;issues-to-clarify-the-legal-status-of-animals-into-disputes&quot;&gt;Issues to clarify the legal status of animals into disputes&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participants pointed out that there is a provision in the Law of Protection Act 25-1 that &quot;the use of drugs, firearms, and the number of animal deaths is significant&quot; In the five years of imprisonment, she pointed out that the comma behind the original &quot;arms&quot; was a comma. As a result, even if no drugs or firearms were used, it would not be possible to apply this legal punishment simply for the death of multiple animals. However, the COA responded that even if 25-1 is not applicable, it can still apply Article 25 of the Sports Protection Law, and can be sentenced to fixed-term imprisonment of two years or less, or a fine of more than 200,000 yuan and less than 2 million yuan in criminal detention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was also a discussion about the legal status of animals. Sharing with the participants, she only knew when she was doing legal counseling. In the definition of the legal profession, animals are considered as items, so the abuse of animals is a crime of damage, and even depreciation. The participating groups also shared that there is a provision in the German Civil Code that states that animals are not items, but in fact it is inevitable that some parts of the animal still apply the property law when applicable, and later amended the constitution to include animal protection in the national goals and policies. . He believes that the positioning of animals in the legal system is a problem that must be pondered. The Taiwan Society for Animal Society wants to know whether the government has a way to conduct research on this issue. The COA responds to the analysis of the scope of administrative capacity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/5/561cb85ed69353c3318cddbbc17adf46d3c2a663.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The participating scholars explained the problem of the law of insurance &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Legal scholars pointed out that the original aggravated penalty was to avoid animal cruelty, but he wanted to remind everyone that when the criminal law was used, it should be discussed. In Germany, for example, they have only one article, three years or less, but Germany does not have enough protection for animals. He suggested that everyone should think about how public-private partnerships can help the insured to prove, including the bonus method, and tell the public how to assist in the proof, such as the angle of the photo, which can be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was pointed out that he hopes that in addition to penalties, he should also publish his name and the facts of the crime. However, some scholars have reminded me where the purpose of publishing names is. If the name is to be humiliated, it is important to note that it may violate the interpretation of Chief Justice Interpretation No. 656. He believes that he can do counseling education. He believes that Taiwanese are more anxious and the pressure of the class is actually greater than the fine. He believes that the country must make animal protection a social consensus. Further, it is the right thing to do to raise the cost of raising animals and to have each animal fully registered to avoid wandering animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the pet registration system, the Council of Agriculture said that it has been implemented for almost 20 years, and the owner of the animal family has already registered as a pet. However, there is still a group of owners who know that they only feed him, give him a little meal, and don't think they have animals. They shared that in the past few years, there have been three-in-one actions to sterilize and register pets. They hope to make such a donor identity clear and break through the current bottleneck. The Taiwan Society for Animal Science reminded that the most fundamental problem is the values of the people. If they are not resolved, the conflict will always exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the status of voluntary insurance workers, civil society groups said that due to lack of experience and cases, most of the civil security commissioned commissioners are actually not sure how to use regulations in practice, so the voluntary insurance staff is large. Part is the part that assists in the search. The Taiwan Association for the Prevention of Animal Abuse also shared that in the sharing of information, it is sometimes difficult for the compulsory insured to obtain the follow-up information of the case, and the cooperation is prone to problems. However, some insurance practitioners shared their experience and said that some volunteers will be in charge of supervising the role of the government. Some even enter the door is the action for live broadcast, video recording, and fundraising, which in turn causes troubles for the work of the athletes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Taiwan Society for Animal Society said that animal protection inspectors are not recognized by the society. &quot;The principle of how people should treat animals is not clear. There is no basic consensus in this society. The COA has more movements. There is no way for the inspectors to &quot;implement animal protection&quot;, only &quot;father and son ride&quot;.&quot; They believe that raising the legal level of animals can make people pay attention to animal protection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the morning discussion, the afternoon group discussion focused on &quot;how to improve the energy of animal protection under existing manpower to avoid more stray animals being abused?&quot; and &quot;How to improve the immobilisation, police It is a matter of witnessing the people’s search for the problem of ill-treatment of stray animals and avoiding the abuse of more stray animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;group-discussion-public-private-partnership-to-assist-the-law-enforcement-staff-to-enforce-law&quot;&gt;Group discussion public-private partnership to assist the law enforcement staff to enforce law&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group of reports shared two questions, the first one is about the lack of manpower. They believe that they can be resolved by public-private partnerships or civil insurance workers, but there may be obstacles to communication or unclear rights and responsibilities. Therefore, they suggest that a clear cooperation mechanism can be established, which can be handled by civil security workers in the form of administrative entrustment. These private volunteers can find relevant operators or groups to train relevant volunteers. However, the general public can promote the public's awareness of the law of protection through the long-term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the part of the search, the second group shared, many times the search has a lot of problems, for example, the general public may directly discard the body of the cat and dog, or the site is a private place, the local insured may be human Insufficient to feel the scene and so on, resulting in the difficulty of the search. They suggested that they could create high-risk maps for mobile insurance, and set up monitors where human dogs and cats have high conflicts. Participants also mentioned that a netizen, Zuo Xiangmin, already has some courses to teach the public how to search for evidence on the SPCA website. There are also some lists of searches. It may be overcome through education and publicity, and the SOP for the search is clear. Attach a sample photo and ask the lieutenant or the insurance group to help. The second group will share, when the insured's ability is insufficient, they may want to use the public and private department's propaganda activities to talk to them about the TNR during the Limin Conference and seize what the lieutenant wants, such as the ballot. To encourage the participation of the people. In terms of private dog farms, there is usually not much problem with feed, but it is lacking in the medical sector. The second group recommends that public shelters establish medical centers to improve medical energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bacb8bfaa54cdf32ceea23b85d7e04530553e356.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group report &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the medical expenses after the animal has been abused, it is recommended that the COA can do relevant research to see how it can be overcome by regulations. In the search section, you can create a manual for animal protection and a DM to let the public know how to search for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the aspect of accessing the monitor, the second group suggested that the police can be accompanied, and the chance of cooperation with the store is relatively high. If the police can't, please ask the insured to review it in the past. In terms of adoption, the second group pointed out that many people were enthusiastic about adopting animals and found that the animals were not suitable at home and wanted to return. As a result, they would violate the laws and regulations and be blacklisted. Instead, they could no longer adopt animals. The second group believes that it can improve the adoption and maintenance mechanism. When it is adopted for one month, it is familiar and then changed to adoption, and it can handle related problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Tang Feng summed up, the COA is collecting the “White Animal Welfare White Paper” on the Join platform. The deadline is January 20th. Anyone can go to the message and ask the COA to amend it. The results of the conference will be shared by Tang Feng at the government meeting next week for reference in future policy development; related issues manuals, films, mind maps and verbatim records will also be made available on the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;there-are-many-issues-in-the-insurance-policy-i-look-forward-to-the-collaborative-meeting-to-help-understand-the-structural-issues&quot;&gt;There are many issues in the insurance policy. I look forward to the collaborative meeting to help understand the structural issues.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Participants pointed out that this meeting will help them understand the topic, but the topic manual is too late, There are also many people who don't know about this meeting, which is a pity. They also mentioned that the teachers at the meeting explained that the law was complete and that the discussion was much deeper, but they needed a little time to digest the nouns. &quot;You need to go home to review.&quot; Participants said that the issue of motion insurance is complex and complex, and it requires a lot of experience or understanding of issues to properly guide. They think that the host and the desk director are also very experienced, so that the topic can be carried out in the right place, and the small table leader has good control over time. Participants said that at the beginning they did not know what the post-it was doing, but it was found to be very useful. However, they think the discussion is still relatively vague and there is no good solution. The settlement of the law of protection will take a long time, including the rebound of non-governmental labor unions, the training of veterinarians, etc. I am afraid that it will take some time to really solve the problem. Participants are eager to see more of such meetings, on the one hand, to see real structural problems, and in addition to promote friendly dialogue between the public sector and the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">On December 27, 2018, PDIS held a collaborative meeting on the aggravation of penalties by the Law on Insurance. The meeting focused on how to implement the concept of animal protection as disclosed in the Sports Protection Law through public-private partnerships to protect more animals from harassment, injury and even kill.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/48530d8e77a51c4d83e27e2a3126ebaee9292eae.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Business Week Column: Democratic Innovation, Open Source Sustainability</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/06/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business Week Column: Democratic Innovation, Open Source Sustainability" /><published>2018-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/06/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/06/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E9%96%8B%E6%BA%90%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C.html">&lt;p&gt;I have been “dressing the same” with more and more friends recently. This is not because we buy clothes at the same store, but the result of openness. My colleagues made a unique T-shirt with open-source materials. The T-shirt is printed with the Sustainable Development Goals’ “17 color wheel” logo and the words “Taiwan Can Help” on it. The design drawings are all open and everyone can print one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎 In early November, I visited Canada with my coworkers. Together with the local citizen technology community, we ran a workshop in Toronto to discuss the topic of “platform economy” with civil servants, people and NGOs at all levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍁 In the workshop, we shared vTaiwan’s experience in dealing with the platform economy issue. “vTaiwan” is a project conceived by the “gov zero” (g0v.tw) community in Taiwan. Through collaboration between the private sector and the government, it collected the ideas of stakeholders such as relevant ministries, service providers, platform operators and users, and finally concluded with consensus. The local citizen technology community in Toronto was amazed and immediately began to plan “g0v.ca”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍕 On the other side of the Atlantic, “g0v.it” has emerged in Europe. In June of this year, a minister who is responsible for “direct democracy” appeared in the joint cabinet of Italy for the first time. How civil society works with the government has become a top priority for the Italian community. The establishment of g0v.it was also inspired by the Taiwanese experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌍 When I was invited to the Vatican in March this year, I introduced g0v’s spirit, that is, “Don’t ask why no one is doing this; first admit that you are ‘no one’.” One of the audiences, Stefano Quintarelli, the Italian Congressman who invited me to the Holy See, immediately learned from Taiwan, and together with his like-minded friends, finally chose to introduce g0v’s first project “Budget Visualization”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄 Our Italian friends believe that this project is presented very intuitively, helps people understand the budget allocation and leaves room for discussion. Therefore, they used the original project’s open-source material to describe how Italian government uses the budget. Just click on the website “g0v.it” and you are free to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 The experience in Canada and Italy reminds me of a friend I met in the Vatican, Jeffrey Sachs, a Columbia University professor who was responsible for designing the Sustainable Development Goals. At g0v.it’s opening ceremony, he said: What g0v does makes the discussion of the matter become “interesting” again. This is the infrastructure that global democracy now needs most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 I agree with Sachs: The more people make contributions, the more opportunities there are to reimagine and build new democracy. The complete open source of g0v is not only social innovation but also democratic innovation. “Taiwan Can Help” is not just a slogan on a T-shirt.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang、Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">&quot;Taiwan can help&quot; is not just a slogan on a T-shirt.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c2fc370f07085dd84216a64f6fc6f7aa11d19dd5.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">There is a consensus on the steam fuel cost collaboration meeting, and it is more fair to collect with the mileage.</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/01/%E6%B1%BD%E7%87%83%E8%B2%BB%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98-%E9%9A%A8%E9%87%8C%E7%A8%8B%E5%BE%B5%E6%94%B6%E6%9B%B4%E5%85%AC%E5%B9%B3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="There is a consensus on the steam fuel cost collaboration meeting, and it is more fair to collect with the mileage." /><published>2018-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/01/%E6%B1%BD%E7%87%83%E8%B2%BB%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98,%E9%9A%A8%E9%87%8C%E7%A8%8B%E5%BE%B5%E6%94%B6%E6%9B%B4%E5%85%AC%E5%B9%B3</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/12/01/%E6%B1%BD%E7%87%83%E8%B2%BB%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E6%9C%89%E5%85%B1%E8%AD%98-%E9%9A%A8%E9%87%8C%E7%A8%8B%E5%BE%B5%E6%94%B6%E6%9B%B4%E5%85%AC%E5%B9%B3.html">&lt;p&gt;On November 30, 2018, PDIS held the 41st Collaborative Meeting in the Information Center of the Ministry of Finance to discuss &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail /c038fdae-0667-45b0-93cd-0ab761338758&quot;&gt;Automobile fuel tax changed with oil&lt;/a&gt; Proposal. On June 29th, the case was proposed by netizen billy on the Join platform. He pointed out that the fuel consumption fee for motor vehicles is to repair the road surface. It should be levied with oil according to the principle of user payment, using mass transportation vehicles. People do not have to be forced to pay extra fees, and drivers who use more roads have the power to save fuel and reduce carbon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Article 27 of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://law.moj.gov.tw/lawclass/lawall.aspx?pcode=k0040001&quot;&gt;Road Law&lt;/a&gt;: “the highway authority, for road maintenance, construction and for the safety management, it is necessary to levy a vehicle fuel use fee (hereinafter referred to as &quot;steam fuel charge&quot;…&quot;. from this, it can be seen that the fuel charge is collected for road maintenance, construction and safety management. the current collection method is based on the vehicle. the fixed fee is levied each year (season) for the type, purpose of use (self-use or business) and displacement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;there-are-three-similar-systems-in-the-gas-burning-fee-collection-schemes&quot;&gt;There are three similar systems in the gas burning fee collection schemes&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every country has a similar system to collect related expenses to maintain the road surface, but according to the calculation method, it can be divided into Collected by car, &quot;levied with oil&quot; and &quot;levied with mileage&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The levy on the vehicle is generally levied on the weight of the vehicle. In Taiwan, the displacement is calculated based on the displacement of the vehicle. Although the collection cost is relatively low, it is less in line with the principle of &quot;user pays&quot;. With oil, it is levied with fuel, but nowadays, with the continuous innovation of technology, it is necessary to consider the situation in which the roads such as electric vehicles and hybrid vehicles do not use oil, and the situation in which oil is not used, such as agricultural machinery and generators. In terms of oil and so on, it is more difficult to plan, and it is even necessary to create additional pipelines in response to the situation of electric vehicles. With regard to mileage collection, although it is more in line with the principle of user payment, I am afraid that it is necessary to install the corresponding interface on the vehicle to record, or to need to transmit and log in the pipeline, which is more complicated and may also violate privacy. Doubt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Research Report of the [Automotive Fuel Consumption Fee Collection System] made by the Transportation Research Institute of the Ministry of Communications in October 2017 (https://www.iot.gov.tw/file.ashx?id=9fc1e9c8 -a2f5-4e2a-a243-c8a2a8bc53cd)&quot;, as well as pre-interview interviews, the factors that people, government or industry care about are not the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the public, the elements they care about are fair, simple, and private. In terms of fairness, the public hopes to implement the principle of user payment, so that the payment can be more fair; the fee collection mechanism should be simple and convenient, if it is too unsocial, it may lead to public grievances; in the end, it is hoped to protect privacy and not excessively expose too many personal actions. Information to the government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the government's focus is on administrative costs, law enforcement, impact on the transportation industry, and income from finance. In terms of administrative costs, the government does not want the administrative costs to be too high, resulting in a larger workload for civil servants. In law enforcement, the relevant fee collection mechanism cannot be illegal, beyond the authority of the government, and cannot be implemented and cannot be implemented; if the transportation industry costs increase due to charges It may affect prices and cause public grievances; in financial terms, the new fee collection mechanism cannot lead to insufficient fees. As for the relevant industry players, most of them do not want to change the fee mechanism to increase operating costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications believes that regardless of the method of collection of steam fuel costs, it should ensure that the financial resources are stable to meet the requirements for road maintenance and construction and safety management. Changes in the mode of expropriation should avoid a substantial increase in administrative costs, and minimize the level of socio-economic impact, and choose the right time to promote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;with-the-oil-collection-problem-with-the-mileage-collection-program-ministry-of-communications-research&quot;&gt;With the oil collection problem with the mileage collection program Ministry of Communications research&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the meeting, the Ministry of Communications explained that in order to avoid public misunderstanding, the Ministry of Communications recommended that the fuel burning fee be renamed Road maintenance fees, so as not to be confused with foreign fuel taxes. Regarding the content of the proposal, the Ministry of Communications said that according to the constitutional content of the Chief Justice, there is no problem with the collection of steam fuel charges. If it is levied with oil, such as the passenger transportation and taxis that were originally exempted, how to collect them in the future and how to refund them is a problem. At the same time, with the oil collection, prices may also rise, which may require more social communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Transportation shared the foreign case and pointed out that due to the fuel efficiency of many vehicles, the fuel tax revenue has also been continuously reduced, and because of the increasing number of electric vehicles, the US fuel tax has gradually evolved under fair consideration. Turn to &quot;road use fees.&quot; Currently in the US state of Oregon, it has been piloted. In 2015, the two-track system was implemented. About 700 vehicles are using the “road use fee”. Washington State and California are also actively testing the mileage-levied scheme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Communications also pointed out that according to the American AASHTO design guidelines, the damage degree of pavements of different vehicles is about 4 times of the axle load ratio. The damage caused by heavy trucks to the pavement and the maintenance cost in the future are much higher than the average. For self-use vehicles, in the future, it is possible to establish a fee collection mechanism with the weight of the vehicle plus the mileage of the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 13, 2017, the Legislative Yuan has decided to ask the Ministry of Communications to conduct relevant research on the mileage collection as soon as possible. The current study will be closed on May 29, 2019. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that the future discussion includes five levels, including feasible technologies, discussions on privacy, charging systems, and information security. The administrative level should consider how to save personnel costs. The most important part is the financial aspect. In order to take into account the stability and sustainability of finance, we need to know how much money we need to receive in the future. Since the gas burning fee collection system involves people's rights and interests, the Ministry of Communications will also develop plans and field test plans in the future, and then make policy decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8cbd75a50f2b806efa3881e7b4f71cd63e4c547d.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group discussion status &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Touring Car Dealer believes that the current Ministry of Communications' exemption policy is only for mass transportation and taxis. It is not fair in the industrial circle. The tour bus is also a kind of mass transportation and should also be included in the exemption scope. The gas station trade union pointed out that the current air pollution charges were imposed, which led to an increase in the oil price of the gas station, which increased the turnover of the gas station, increased the business tax, and increased the handling fee of the bank card, thereby reducing the profit of the gas station. They are worried that if the fuel cost is levied with the oil, I am afraid that a similar situation will occur, which will lower the profit of the gas station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the charging plan, some people pointed out that the Ministry of Transportation’s charging standard now estimates the weight of the vehicle by the amount of exhaust, but now even large-scale transportation vehicles are lighter, and the large displacement may not necessarily represent the weight of the vehicle. . He believes that such a standard is probably the result of the Ministry of Communications's cheaper actions. It is recommended that the weight of the vehicle be used as the charging standard. As for the name changed to the road management fee, he thinks that there is no problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another participant pointed out that the government should maintain good accountability and use market mechanisms to make the system better. It has also been pointed out that they hope that the quality of the road surface can be better, not to build roads too frequently, resulting in poor road quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;us-oregon-province-builds-a-mileage-based-system-with-new-technology&quot;&gt;US Oregon Province builds a mileage-based system with new technology&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Transportation shares the technology of mileage collection. The Oregon State requires OBD2 to be installed on a new car. It will detect the speed and oil condition; OBD2 will transfer the mileage and GPS data to the management platform. The Ministry of Communications team said that their research team is currently studying several programs, such as car code tables, but they are worried that they will be tampered with; if OBD2 is used, the advantage is that it can be read, but there may be errors; if the returned data contains GPS, There may be issues that violate personal privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other is OBE, for example, OBU with many car networking technologies; Beacon can also be connected to the mobile phone using near-field communication, and then return the information. Using ETC detection may also be a method, but it may become that ETC is installed on every road, which may be troublesome. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that Beacon's new mobile phone and the possibility of using ETC tracking are relatively low, so the main evaluation of the first three options, namely the code table, OBD2 and OBE. The Ministry of Communications pointed out that a feasible plan is currently being developed, and the industry will come back to discuss it in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;create-a-new-form-to-help-the-group-focus-on-the-discussion&quot;&gt;Create a new form to help the group focus on the discussion&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to facilitate discussion, the afternoon discussion produced a different form to help you discuss. The table is divided into four quadrants, representing the status quo, with the oil collection, with mileage and mileage + vehicle weight and other four programs; in the current situation, the plan is also included in the vehicle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c194663d51670de3cc3035a9883849b784159e52.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; New form designed for discussion &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each program has its own fields of fairness, complexity, administrative costs, related industry costs, user costs, and “other” fields to classify the types of opinions of participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the group discussion, it is followed by the time of each group report.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;discussion-in-each-group-believes-that-the-mileage-is-more-fair&quot;&gt;Discussion in each group believes that the mileage is more fair&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first group pointed out that if &quot;maintaining the current situation&quot;, regardless of the actual road conditions, all the equal costs will be paid. More similar to the public welfare mentioned in other advanced conferences than fairness. They believe that the current classification of exhaust gas has nothing to do with the actual frequency of use and road damage, which is unfair. Perhaps this collection method is simple and simple, but now it seems to be a bit cheaper. This set of recommendations, the levy standard should be recalculated. Since the public has no way to identify how the 50 billion levy is distributed to the actual use and support of local governments, the fairness of the levy will be repeatedly verified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although there is no other technology in the current stage, the &quot;levy with oil&quot; program can best reflect the situation on the road, but the progress of science and technology makes the fuel consumption performance better and better, and the use of oil does not represent the road. The situation may be doubtful in fairness and justice. At the same time, the implementation of the gas station identification mechanism may be required. The administrative work is relatively complicated, and the increased operating expenses may also lead to loss at the gas station. For oil and electric vehicles, electric vehicles may also require additional matching methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3accdad2bd00872b2ccb00fbf55c715b25620b0b.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Group report site &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the part of the mileage collection, according to the report of the Institute of Transportation, in the international trend, in order to stabilize the financial resources and truly reflect the status of the vehicles, the countries have changed their mileage in recent years. It is undeniable that this may be the final The fairest way. If you want to make the actual damage degree of the road can be measured, you can add the weight of the car as a consideration. However, the burden of government investment in construction costs and on-board installation costs is quite large. When technology is fully licensed and mature, it can be popularized with mileage. At the same time, the government may consider personal privacy in addition to collecting mileage. The part of protection should protect personal data in accordance with the individual law. In response to the increase in costs of related businesses, the government needs to consider supporting the use as a stable price. The first group also suggested that all fees should be divided into business and own use, and plan different payment plans. The second group believes that the cost of steam fuel charges is necessary, but in the method of collection, it can be considered to adjust the base fee plus the way of collecting according to different usage conditions. In the current situation, the second group pointed out that some business vehicles are for the public interest, so there is no need to levy steam fuel costs, but they still have damage and use on the road surface, which may be unfair. In terms of calculation standards, the second group believes that the standard calculated by the exhaust volume is outdated and can be calculated by using horsepower and vehicle weight. As part of the oil collection, the second group is concerned that the electric vehicle will not receive the cost; at the same time, the fuel consumption of the car may not be completely fair. If you want to consider the use of oil purchases, it will be more difficult to collect fees. The second group also believes that if the cost is charged by the gas station, it is necessary to be careful that the fee is included in the business tax, resulting in additional taxes on the gas station. It may be possible to give the fuel dispensers a modest fee and compensate for such losses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the participants in the second group believe that the mileage is more fair, and it is recommended to set the basic fee and then add the fee according to the different mileage. The second group also suggested that it is more fair to add the weight of the vehicle as a calculation factor. However, the second group pointed out that there may be ways to distinguish the rates of highways or other roads, and the reliability of mileage is also a problem. They suggested that the government can set standards so that the industry can compete fairly, as long as it can make standards-compliant ways to compete in this market and promote the development of the industry. In the system design, we must consider the old car that can not use the new technology, as well as the cost of installing the new car. The second group of discussions also mentioned the Japanese tax system, which can be taxed on the weight of the car, plus mileage fees, combined to become a new road use fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the second group also reminds that people who are in the middle of the country may need to have a corresponding package to give relief because they do not have public transportation means, otherwise it may be unfair. How to pass back the mileage of the local network environment is also a problem. In the early stage of the second group of proposals, the two-track parallel approach can be used to allow the public to choose the current method, or to add mileage pricing, and then consider the industry status to set a sufficient time limit so that the industry can have sufficient time to introduce it in stages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9b11cdbb2447313db77b4fad10714fa23a3ad77d.JPG&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Tang Feng’s live broadcast of the second session &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tang Feng concluded that the results of this meeting will be shared with the dean or other political council members at the government meeting next Monday after the team is fully organized. If there is a clear cut, it will make relevant The open government contact person knows; the hosted ministry will also share the discussion thread and the comprehensive comments of the meeting to the second person on the platform of the agreement, the future &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov. tw/2018-11-30-%e9%96%8b%e6%94%be%e6%94%bf%e5%ba%9c%e8%81%af%e7%b5%a1%e4%ba%ba %e7%ac%ac%e5%9b%9b%e5%8d%81%e4%b8%80%e6%ac%a1%e5%8d%94%e4%bd%9c%e6%9c%83%e8 %ad%b0&quot;&gt;Verbatim Draft&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1r98q8vigmbtppljwzj68ey5-4hezzijt82uqaszie4w/edit&quot;&gt;issue manual&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/board/o9j_kyje69o related information such as =/&quot;&gt;mind map&lt;/a&gt; will also be made public. However, since the fuel burning fee involves legal amendments, even if the name is changed, it is necessary to return to the Legislative Yuan for processing. But if other legislators are interested in this matter in the future, they can refer to the information of this meeting to discuss it, and they will not discuss the same issue again and again. Finally, Tang Feng sincerely thanked the friends who attended the meeting, &quot;Thank you for your advancement in legislation and administrative quality.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; title=&quot;Realtimeboard&quot; src=&quot;https://realtimeboard.com/app/embed/o9J_kyjE69o=/?&amp;amp;pres=1&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RJ9iL3GIRGw&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-director-of-the-table-led-the-discussion-to-be-well-received-the-appreciator-agreed-with-the-direction-of-the-ministry-of-communications&quot;&gt;The director of the table led the discussion to be well received. The appreciator agreed with the direction of the Ministry of Communications.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The civil servants who attended the meeting said that the meeting was as expected, but some tools were used, such as Mind map, they are hard to master. Trade union representatives are more concerned about the continuity of the policy. I hope that the government's policies will have consistent results and will not change at any time. Some people suggest that stakeholders can be more subdivided. For example, in this mileage-levied scheme, the garage is an important role in confirming the correctness of OBD, and their lack may be relatively important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second party believes that the government should not only hear the voice of the industry, but also the voice of the consumer group. Otherwise, it may end up with the consortium and manufacturers. They pointed out that the general public may think &quot;how to discuss for so long?&quot; They often feel that the official response is slow and half-time, and I hope to know when there will be changes. At the same time, they also pointed out that the people want the explanations that are easy to understand, and some of them are too literary and may not help communication. They hope that they will not want to find someone to come to the meeting and become a meeting, or that the government can be good for the country and listen to the voice of the people in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this meeting, the congressors at the meeting thought it would be helpful. When the discussion of the group was divergent, the table leader would pull back the discussion in due course. Some people in the public sector will come up with ideas that they have not heard before, and many union representatives share practical problems. The congressmen who help to discuss together understand the ideas of different stakeholders. The second person said that they would agree with the direction of the Ministry of Transportation to collect the mileage, and they will continue to care about this issue in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The participating scholars said that the team's ability to gather and information is very strong, so it can be effectively discussed; when the group discussion, everyone can further discuss specific suggestions from emotional or intuitive speech, the public department can let It is very useful and valuable for the public sector to provide opinions, participate in the process of policy planning, and make a list of the advantages and disadvantages of the program. However, he believes that the stakeholder is not diversified. Although there are many people in the industry, the voice of the second person is not enough. It is suggested that people with more different positions can be invited to participate. The scholar shared that in this meeting, he felt that there was a good chance of citizen participation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">On November 30th, PDIS held the 41st Collaborative Meeting with the Ministry of Communications in the Treasury Center. To assist in the discussion, the PDIS team designed a new form to facilitate discussion among participants. Participants felt that the Department of Transportation's mileage-based program was more equitable with oil.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/8cbd75a50f2b806efa3881e7b4f71cd63e4c547d.JPG" /></entry><entry><title type="html">How is the health insurance card virtualized? Three collaborative meetings to clarify possible directions</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/11/27/%E5%81%A5%E4%BF%9D%E5%8D%A1%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E8%99%9B%E6%93%AC%E5%8C%96-%E4%B8%89%E5%A0%B4%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E9%87%90%E6%B8%85%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E6%96%B9%E5%90%91.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How is the health insurance card virtualized? Three collaborative meetings to clarify possible directions" /><published>2018-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/11/27/%E5%81%A5%E4%BF%9D%E5%8D%A1%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E8%99%9B%E6%93%AC%E5%8C%96%3F%E4%B8%89%E5%A0%B4%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E9%87%90%E6%B8%85%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E6%96%B9%E5%90%91</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/2018/11/27/%E5%81%A5%E4%BF%9D%E5%8D%A1%E5%A6%82%E4%BD%95%E8%99%9B%E6%93%AC%E5%8C%96-%E4%B8%89%E5%A0%B4%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E9%87%90%E6%B8%85%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E6%96%B9%E5%90%91.html">&lt;p&gt;Do you have a chance to virtualize your health insurance card? In 2018, PDIS opened three collaborative meetings to try to clarify: If the health insurance card is virtualized, what functions are expected to be owned by the public, and what risks should be avoided? These corresponding materials are important reference materials for the trial of future health insurance cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the review of the second-generation health insurance card program on April 10, 2018, the National Development Association invited the Public Digital Innovation Space Group (PDIS) of the Executive Yuan and the Open Government Contact (PO) of the Ministry of Health and Welfare to introduce a civil participation mechanism. Use multi-party collaboration and other methods to broaden the opinions of all walks of life and complete innovative planning operations. It is hoped that if technology and cost are feasible, if anyone wants to use the health insurance card in a purely mobile vehicle, there must be a viable solution for them to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-first-collaborative-meeting-to-clarify-the-expectations-and-concerns-of-the-people&quot;&gt;The first collaborative meeting to clarify the expectations and concerns of the people&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the beginning, the Health Insurance Agency had some doubts about the case. The first one is how to implement the medical environment and the action credentials in the future when the physical card is completely used. The first is the information stored on the health insurance card. Currently, the health insurance card can store data. The clinic or hospital needs to upload the cloud within 24 hours, but sometimes there may be a drop, but if it is to be stored on the mobile vehicle, this may need to be overcome. Then there is the technology of identity authentication. There is a way to confirm the cardholder's own, how to use the action certificate to confirm? The third is the certification of the authorization mechanism. Some people do not have mobile phones, or children, how to use virtual credentials to seek medical treatment? Can I authorize a guardian to use it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, if the physical card and the action voucher are in parallel, the medical institution may have different equipment to respond to, which may increase the cost of the medical institution; in some places, the network is not very good, if the action certificate is used Is there a problem?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To answer these concerns, PDIS begins with an inventory of the health care card. Take a look at the current process before you can start working on the virtualization part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the journey of health insurance card, it can be divided into the journey of the card itself, from the card, card replacement, to recovery; in the medical situation, there are procedures such as registration, consultation, pricing, and drug collection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first collaborative meeting was held on July 4, 2018. On the same day, various health insurance users, doctors and first-line health insurance card changers were invited to be divided into six groups to provide health insurance. Discussions on the feasibility of the development of action voucher, how to reduce the cost of introduction, etc., are expected to receive the expectations and concerns of the new generation of health insurance certificates. The host team also developed some questions and wanted to invite participants to share their vision and concerns. These issues include mobile payment or e-wallet, virtual card, contactless and mobile, authorization mechanism, biometrics, health card replacement, insurance card, device binding, lost replacement, non-medical use, etc. Discuss the use of medical situations in various situations, such as drug collection, hospitalization, and emergency department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f3fded9525c967f8700ba95cc08836302fdeafbe.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; First collaborative meeting &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the nature of this meeting is more divergent, the groups have received a lot of worries and visions about their use. At the end of the meeting, PDIS received comments on two large posters. For the part of the action payment, the participants believed that there were many payment tools and no need to use the health insurance card. For the virtual card, the participants believed that the health insurance card must exist, and the security and accountability mechanism should Perfect; at the same time, explicit information should also be provided for identity identification. If the phone is changed or lost, the data should be completely eliminated. The participating medical institutions are worried that they will have to spend a lot of money to purchase related equipment in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/823fc8288d79c04bc0bdd0467fcc8db2aabc8d6c.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/38c1bffb674d8648ecd5db1e5cf2d25458ad5a9c.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The first collaborative meeting outcome &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-second-collaboration-meeting-is-aimed-at-the-peoples-expectation-of-planning-possible-solutions&quot;&gt;The second collaboration meeting is aimed at the people's expectation of planning possible solutions&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the first collaboration meeting, the Health Insurance Agency also &lt;a href=&quot;https://join .gov.tw/policies/detail/dc226809-6651-406e-8841-87fefec51875&quot;&gt;through the &quot;opening&quot; function of the Join platform&lt;/a&gt;, invite netizens to express their expectations and concerns about the new generation of health insurance cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these worries and visions gathered in the first collaborative meeting and network, PDIS and the Health Insurance Department gathered the relevant opinions after the meeting and spent hours to cast these concerns and visions into the core. Challenge Statement:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine how to make health insurance cards more convenient under the premise of information security and at affordable cost, with good authorization mechanism, identity identification, and offline experience. To promote an action life policy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; Imagine how to improve the reading and writing speed of the hospital, reduce the consumption of card reading equipment, and upload the medical information immediately to improve the quality of medical services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the second collaborative meeting, these &quot;core challenge sentences&quot; allow relevant experts to think about possible solutions together. The second collaborative meeting was held on July 25th. The planning was closer to the expert meeting. The planning first discussed the technical solutions and precautions in the context of “institutional visits” and “home medical care”. The regulations experts and cost experts will then review and check the plan. If there are opportunities for modification, they can immediately discuss possible solutions on the spot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/335c8139db63a477fbda163a2578dfece3633166.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Second collaborative meeting &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the discussion and meeting of the second collaborative meeting, the application process of the virtual card can be applied through the physical card or online through the physical card, and the mobile phone hardware is bound; or directly input enough basic information. , download from the website. Offline home medical situation providers should obtain health insurance information before reaching the patient's home, and have a mechanism to ensure that the doctor can see the doctor; after the consultation, the prescription can be opened, but the network connection is required. When taking the HIS system, upload the medical consultation information to the Health Insurance Department immediately. In the case of general outpatient visits, the assistants must first obtain a health insurance card to facilitate the preparation of case data during the waiting time; after the visit, a mechanism is required to write back the health insurance card, including physical and virtual. If you want to try it later, you should also consider the issue of device update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This discussion also discusses the three-card authentication process built on the asymmetric public key architecture. Through the public key of the Health Insurance Agency, confirm whether the medical card, the information given by the medical institution can be unlocked, and whether the information after the disassembly is correct, in order to achieve the three-card authentication process. If there is a need to exchange data, you can use the public key encryption of the other party or exchange the one-time key of the symmetric encryption through the public key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a8f1f9a97c00139d3367b16e4d1132bceab89489.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/44efc11de5a770bd13d5a1c68858e8b36cdb2071.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2a45e54f27f2e882453851a6a6090e25d2c31a5e.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/f/f0a8f7a6f89e36b5ed47b74838aae32fcfaae1b1.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0a0179db0cf0ae1b5487a6db2ae497b582938dd0.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; The outcome of the second collaborative meeting &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These considerations and related technical solutions need to be discussed in the third collaborative meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-third-collaborative-meeting-invited-people-to-provide-opinions-on-solutions&quot;&gt;The third collaborative meeting invited people to provide opinions on solutions.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the process is described in a graphic description, it may be misunderstood by the participants, making it difficult to focus on the discussion; after discussion, health insurance The department filmed the film of the future health insurance card usage process and played it in a collaborative meeting to facilitate the participants to unify the use of the process before the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to allow participants to have the opportunity to speak and exchange ideas, the third collaborative meeting, held on November 26, divided the users into six groups, each group being as diverse as possible; The process invites participants to express their opinions. These opinions are further classified into &quot;design well&quot;, &quot;somewhat problem&quot;, &quot;problem problem&quot; and &quot;other matters&quot;. In the process of discussion, there are three options for &quot;Bluetooth connection at home&quot;, &quot;NVI reading virtual health insurance card at the clinic&quot; and &quot;QRCode for consultation at the clinic&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/2/2faea692df4e8a2e16befcca934b0bb5926e2e4f.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Third collaborative meeting &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the handling of virtual cards, some groups think that they need to handle the case for the first time, but some groups think that if they change their mobile phones, they need to handle them. I am afraid that they will provoke people’s complaints; others suggest that they should be able to apply online. More convenient. In the consultation section, the institute still worried that the cost of related equipment was too high, or the sensory was poor; some groups pointed out that online or telephone registration does not use the cabinet, this is just to confirm whether the health insurance card can be used and the patient's basic information, it is recommended that QRCode should It should contain relevant basic information so that it does not need to be read from the cloud. If the physical card and the virtual card are lost at the same time, they should be able to re-apply at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the home examination section, if there is a network in the patient's home, it is recommended to be able to interface with the information system of the medical institution to inquire about drugs, consumables and inspection forms, and to sort out common drug data and packages. It can also increase the related convenience functions such as recording the questions to be asked about the consultation. However, if there is no Internet in the patient's home, you need to download the relevant information in advance. The prescription is also recommended to be transmitted to the patient's virtual card device. If the doctor returns to the hospital within 24 hours, he or she should have the opportunity to modify the prescription. Of course, the security protection should be done well. It is recommended that the hospital allocate a business jet to carry out related work, or develop a mobile information system interface to retain the flexibility of the information system of the medical institution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the consultation section, if you use the QR Code to remake the public, it may be blurred, and sometimes the problem will be lost; it is recommended that the relevant information can be directly transmitted to the public device; if the mobile phone is lost, it is recommended to be able to re-create from the cloud. download. According to the current law, prescriptions need to be stored for 3-5 years. After the digitization in the future, they can be signed after the pharmacist adjusts and the prescriptions are stored in the cloud. If the pharmacist finds that the prescription may be wrong, he also hopes to establish a conduit to facilitate communication between the pharmacist and the physician, and help the pharmacist to confirm the content again. If a controlled drug requires a medical certificate, you can use the virtual signature of the physician card to resolve it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6b351d3bdb1b67183d4dc5650820bb454f500ea3.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/a/abaa5e6ad389f2fff1dc58a22b5020b7fcf8da23.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4b8048894979b0465024ad1f8f1d7fd4d5714d9b.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/1/1c45b293cecafdb0f40d784e0baaf982d1f782d9.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/eaec4b8a23e52a2920e9e85fe4bcdf7e071f33eb.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/3c267f877e84c5ba777f3672766ac54506aa0c02.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compared with past collaborative meetings, this collaborative meeting can be more detailed in planning because it has three times. The first collaborative meeting collected the opinions of each user, the second time gathered the specific feasible plan, and the third time invited the interested parties to express the suggestions for the process. The Future Health Insurance Agency will also plan public testing, hoping to find problems in the early stages of the policy, so that the policies can be more detailed and closer to the needs of the people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt; 
 &lt;img src=&quot;https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9fd5e06598a09b02315606da910ee6b4fece38a7.jpeg&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;figcaption&gt; Health Insurance Card Collaboration Conference Planning &lt;/figcaption&gt; 
 &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;three-collaboration-conference-participants-evaluation-high&quot;&gt;Three Collaboration Conference Participants Evaluation High&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For these several collaborative meetings, what did the participants say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was a participant who said that these collaborative meetings allowed opportunities to communicate between different roles. &quot;Multipleness is more&quot;; the way in which tables are presented during discussions is also very special. He said that in order to help everyone understand the film is very accurate, let everyone know the difference between NFC and QR Code programs, the difference will be known in the preview. He said that in the case of the government, such a meeting has been very flexible, and most of them have given positive recognition. If there is an opportunity in the future, he is interested in participating in such a meeting to provide advice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another physician pointed out that he had had many meetings before, but the form of collaborative meetings was refreshing. He hopes that in the future, many organizations can use this method to integrate pre-implementation opinions. He pointed out that in this meeting, we can see the good ideas put forward by many stakeholders and the future can be included in the initiative. However, he observed that after splitting into six groups of discussions, although there were many identical views, there were also conflicting views, which were difficult to clarify in a short time, and there was no clear clarification of these differences at the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The doctor's partner who participated in many collaborative meetings pointed out that there were many functions in the first discussion, but because of the restrictions of the regulations, many functions were excluded; he suggested that the focus of discussion in the future can be Let's give you a reference before the meeting. You can think about it before you meet it, or discuss it with your friends on various occasions. It may be more clarifying the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the record of the meeting, he shared that the traditional meeting only records the summary, it is easy to be distorted, and these opinions must return to the context at the time, otherwise it is easy to be distorted. If there is a verbatim record, it will not be misunderstood. In terms of the procedural aspects of the discussion, the tables used in the discussion are more focused on the discussion, and the post-it notes are also suitable for discussion. He highly praised the host team and thought that these moderators could be used as seeds to introduce many conference venues and make the conference more effective and effective. He believes that such a meeting is very different from the traditional one, and the suggestion can be introduced in the public sector or in the enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He expects that after these meetings have been opened, they can organize their opinions well. Even if they are not adopted, at least the ruling party is willing to fully think about it and face the opinions of various ethnic groups. The future policy will be more continuous. He hopes that such an approach can be used as a mirror for future public policy. &quot;I personally rate it very high.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>雨蒼</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="JOIN平台" /><summary type="html">Is there a chance for the health insurance card to be virtualized? In 2018, PDIS opened three collaborative meetings to try to clarify: If the health insurance card is virtualized, what functions are expected to be owned by the public, and what risks should be avoided? These corresponding materials are important reference materials for the trial of future health insurance cards.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/9/9fd5e06598a09b02315606da910ee6b4fece38a7.jpeg" /></entry></feed>