<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-12-24T07:02:42+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Empathy and dialogue building in the “Divine Pig” case</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E-%E7%A5%9E%E8%B1%AC%E6%A1%88-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0-%E7%9C%8B%E5%90%8C%E7%90%86%E8%88%87%E5%B0%8D%E8%A9%B1%E5%B9%B3%E5%8F%B0%E7%9A%84%E5%BB%BA%E6%A7%8B/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Empathy and dialogue building in the “Divine Pig” case" /><published>2019-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E%E3%80%8C%E7%A5%9E%E8%B1%AC%E6%A1%88%E3%80%8D%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0,%E7%9C%8B%E5%90%8C%E7%90%86%E8%88%87%E5%B0%8D%E8%A9%B1%E5%B9%B3%E5%8F%B0%E7%9A%84%E5%BB%BA%E6%A7%8B</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%9E-%E7%A5%9E%E8%B1%AC%E6%A1%88-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0-%E7%9C%8B%E5%90%8C%E7%90%86%E8%88%87%E5%B0%8D%E8%A9%B1%E5%B9%B3%E5%8F%B0%E7%9A%84%E5%BB%BA%E6%A7%8B/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;origin&quot;&gt;Origin&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In mid-August this year, netizen “Happy Mumu” proposed on the public policy network participation platform a signed case called &lt;a href=&quot;https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/09ae5b7b-b8d9-4c92-bc51-46416f4b2df4&quot;&gt;“Stop the Divine Pig Weight Competition Sacrifice”&lt;/a&gt;. The proposer pointed out that during the process from breeding to slaughter, the “Divine Pigs” suffer a lot of abuse and pain, so it is hoped that the weight competition can be terminated and replaced by some friendly and innovative method. The case received media attention at the endorsing stage, and it quickly broke through the threshold of 5,000 endorsements to qualify as a case in early September.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the Executive Yuan, the mechanism for deciding what cases to conduct collaborative meetings is the “Open Government Liaison Work Promotion Conference” (referred to as “PO Monthly Meeting”). When the Participation Officer (PO) monthly meeting in October was held, the representatives of the Council of Agriculture and the Hakka Affairs Council as hosting organizations, offered to collaborate on this case. The COA PO explained at the time:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What are involved in this case are issues such as the people’s belief culture, animal protection, and so on. Although the Council of Agriculture does not agree with the pig weight competition from the standpoint of animal protection, sometimes there is no way for the law to completely solve folk customs problems, so we must communicate with believers, contestants, and cultural and historical workers, hoping to reach a consensus on adjustments.” (quoted from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2019-10-07-%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9Cpo%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%89%E5%8D%81%E4%BA%8C%E6%AC%A1%E6%9C%88%E6%9C%83#s332435&quot;&gt;transcript&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the coordination of the National Development Council, the Hakka Affairs Council that is considered to be related to the weight competition culture of the divine pig, is the main organizer, while the Ministry of the Interior and and the Ministry of Culture, responsible for religion and folk culture, are the co-organizers. In the four-ministry case, the two-month preparatory process for the “Divine Pig” issue began. On November 15th, stakeholders were invited to attend a collaborative meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;alignment-and-tone-setting-of-administrative-departments&quot;&gt;Alignment and tone setting of administrative departments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This proposal is not a brand new topic for the executive branch, and all the ministries have been involved in the business related to the Divine Pig competition. The Hakka Affairs Council, one of the organizers, also posted on Facebook this year, “Respecting the sacrifice culture and combating animal cruelty” to express the stand of the government unit. Inter-organizations first carried out the work of “cognitive alignment” within the administrative department, that is, “not using law to forcibly intervene in religious sacrifice culture” as the basic line, but using softer methods, such as counseling and reward, to gradually promote the transformation of the Divine Pig Weight Competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ministries agreed that it is not appropriate to intervene in religious rituals with public authority. From the point of view of the proposer’s hope that the government will be more actively involved, at first glance, this option may be considered to have been narrowed in advance. However, various agencies also took the opportunity to clarify the existing measures. In particular, the Council of Agriculture has written to the local government to strengthen the guidance of the temples, religious groups, and pig breeders within their jurisdiction who still hold sacred pig rituals, and track and manage the feeding. The Hakka Affairs Council drew up the historical context of the Divine Pig Competition and pointed out its connection with the Hakka culture. The Ministry of Culture and the Ministry of the Interior also publicly expressed their stance on the transformation of the sacrifice rituals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, from the standpoint of the “Divine Pig Weight Competition,” all the agencies and the proposer share the same goal, that is, to allow the existing form of Divine Pig sacrifices to be changed to a certain degree. It is only that the means of intervention needs to consider the people’s religious freedom. The government departments have actually expressed the core value of “respecting folk beliefs,” and hoped to discuss them on this premise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;admit-opinions-during-the-preparatory-phase-and-set-issues-for-discussion&quot;&gt;Admit opinions during the preparatory phase, and set issues for discussion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the basic tone was established, each ministry began to interview the stakeholders, including the proposer, the animal protection group, the temples that hold the Divine Pig Weight Competition and are supposed to transform, the believers who participated in the competition, the Divine Pig raisers, the main agencies of animal protection in the county and city governments, and experts and scholars. Since the positions of the administrative departments have reached a consensus and are quite firm, policy communication has been initiated from the preparatory stage. But in the process, it was found that the parties in the civil society have different priorities and their respective positions on the competition also scattered between the two ends of the spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, the process of raising the pigs is difficult to standardize. The law violations of animal abuse need to be determined based on the facts of each case. The representatives of the Ministry followed the local government ’s animal protection office to visit the actual site of the pig farmers. What they saw was indeed different from the previous situation of the animal protection group’s evidence, which showed the importance of case identification. The temples believe that the key lies in the believers. However, the motivation for the competition is often a dynamic process between the believers and the temples, rather than being driven in one direction. It is also affected by changes in external ideas, policy encouragement, and changes in the social and economic structure. The cultural value and historical context of sacrifice that believers care about are also difficult to measure directly under the same standards as animal welfare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, colleagues from various agencies and the PDIS team decided to set the case as a more inclusive theme—”How to discuss the possibilities of alternative rituals on the premise that the people are spontaneous?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the actual operation of the meeting, there were mainly two-stage group discussions. In the first half, “How to encourage believers to choose pigs raised in a natural way to sacrifice to God?” to ensure that we did not completely exclude the option of raising pigs. In the second half, “How to encourage believers to use different ways to repay God?” in response to the request of the proponent to carry out a stimulus of transformation forms and incentives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-diverse-composition-of-the-scene-brings-tension-and-dynamics&quot;&gt;The diverse composition of the scene brings tension and dynamics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the collaborative meeting, the groups were broken up, so that the temples, pig farmers, animal protection agencies, case proposers and endorsers, experts and scholars, and representatives from various ministries were seated around different groups. As mentioned earlier, even if the administrative authorities unanimously determined that there would be no compulsory involvement in the sacrificial culture, the position on the competition was actually quite obvious. The pig farmers at the scene felt “targeted” and some wanted to leave even before the group discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The working team, herein, in addition to ensuring a friendly atmosphere at the scene, also needed to persuade and communicate outside the meeting area. The team originally thought that the conflict might be imminent. However, after entering the group discussion, a temple representative on the spot, who was from the temple that successfully transformed to the creative solution from the Divine Pig Competition, played the role of being able to empathize and identify with the pig farmers in a timely manner. The pig farmers, therefore, were willing to stay in their seats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the animal protection groups, with very firm positions different from the pig farmers, also realized that it was very precious for the farmers and temples to be willing to come to Taipei from faraway and to endure voices that might be completely opposed to their job for survival. Therefore, even if they put forward sharp arguments, they were still willing to soften their attitude in a timely manner, and mentioned their common ideas with the pig farmers and temples. The public sector representatives not only explained their positions and existing actions, but could also play a neutral and integrating role, and even further deconstruct the situation on the demand side, and propose alternative possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relying on the communication between the agencies before hand, and the mutual understanding of the invitees, this collaborative meeting, which might have been parted on bad terms, was successfully completed in the end even if there were several highly-intensified discussion situations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;review-of-the-soul-of-the-meeting-public-service-po&quot;&gt;Review of the soul of the meeting: Public Service PO&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The preparation process of more than a month before the meeting was the key to the successful completion of this afternoon’s collaborative meeting. In addition to “internal communication” to establish a consistent benchmark for all agencies, it is more important to use this benchmark to empathize with all stakeholders and allow people with extremely different positions to listen to each other and sit together till the end of the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, at the micro level, what was relied on was the on-site host, who treated all participants equally, gathered all opinions fairly and clearly, and promptly reminded the meeting to set the tone and the issues to focus. The moderator of this meeting came from the PDIS team, and most of the discussions were held in group, relying on three POs from the Ministry of the Interior, the General Accounting Office, and the Engineering Society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three POs personally participated in the preparation process of working meetings, pre-meetings, etc., and grasped the development of the case before serving as the small table heads (review moderators) of each group. They carefully read the conference manual and did their homework carefully on the topic content. Prior to the formal meeting, the three POs also spent time with the PDIS team to “sandbox” deduce possible discussion scenarios. Together, they designed a “tool list” to assist in the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the day of the meeting, POs took full advantage of the “hosting” technology that open government liaisons should have, allowing participants to reach effective dialogue within a limited time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;not-only-the-public-sectors-collaborative-meetings-can-also-be-a-platform-for-people-talking-with-people&quot;&gt;Not only the public sectors, collaborative meetings can also be a platform for people talking with people&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collaboration meetings have developed close to sixty themes so far, each of which looks different due to the nature of its issues, the policy stage, and the status of its stakeholders. This case had a high degree of social concern, which touched on different fields such as animal protection and religious sacrifice. The stakeholders of all parties had different thinking directions and positions. If it had not established the discussion issues at each stage first, or the moderator couldn’t have guided in a timely manner, the discussion process had been very likely to diverge and fall into the state of each sticking to their own words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As mentioned earlier, the government agencies limited the bottom line for public authority intervention and did not play the role of enforcer in this case, but all units were still actively participating in the preliminary preparation and internal and external communication processes, and the non-ministry POs also devoted to it. Therefore, what we see in this case is that, as a deliberative meeting within the system, the focus of the collaborative conference is not necessarily on the level of public authority intervention, but rather letting the administrative department as the builder of the platform so that the diverse voices of the people can have a field of mutual listening and understanding. The invitations from various ministries also made the conference more diverse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter from the perspective of the proposer, the animal protection group, or the temples, or pig farmers, although the measures to completely satisfy any party have not been summarized, all parties can fully clarify the current situation and express their own opinions to ensure the boundary between action and inaction of the government units. The value of this collaborative meeting is that when the conflict between religious sacrifice culture and humanitarian values occurs, the seemingly incomprehensible and opposing parties can have a chance to see each other’s true situations, and also promote the parties to move a small step towards mutual empathy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>En-En Hsu</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">The value of collaborative meetings is sometimes not the extent to which administrative power is enforced, but rather how much it serves as a platform for communication between dissenting positions among the people.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6493bf8de04293cc04844bab441007e87becc4bc.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/6493bf8de04293cc04844bab441007e87becc4bc.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">My first “judge” experience</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%88%91%E7%9A%84-%E6%B3%95%E5%AE%98-%E5%88%9D%E9%AB%94%E9%A9%97/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My first “judge” experience" /><published>2019-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%88%91%E7%9A%84%E3%80%8C%E6%B3%95%E5%AE%98%E3%80%8D%E5%88%9D%E9%AB%94%E9%A9%97</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%88%91%E7%9A%84-%E6%B3%95%E5%AE%98-%E5%88%9D%E9%AB%94%E9%A9%97/">&lt;p&gt;👩🏻‍⚖️ On the morning of December 11th, the Shilin District Court held a “Let’s Go To Court” event. The highlight was a mock court held by classmates from the 9th class of the Lanya Junior High School and staff members from the Shilin District Court. As for me, I was being the judge of this “trial” remotely, but in real time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⚖️ In order to let the people understand the justice system, and to show how technology can improve the efficiency of the judicial system and reduce the cost and threshold of using judicial resources, the Shilin District Court combines the off-site teaching of Lanya Junior High School. Through a full day of visits, interaction, and practical work, let students and teachers have the first-hand experience in the feeling of “participating in justice”, and deliberate on how to further “open and transparent justice” and “justice close to the people”. These are exactly the goals as the result of the 2017 “National Congress of Judicial Reform”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏫 The court where I participated in the “trial” was just a simulation, but all the details were complete, which is exactly like a proper court. The presiding judge is Judge Jiang Zhewei, who is a real judge from the Shilin District Court, and the accompanying judge is Mr. Wu from the Lanya Junior High School. Through the video robot on the judge’s seat and wearing a robe, I am a remote judge. Classmates from the the Lanya Junior High School together with judges from other Shihlin courts acted as prosecutors, defenders, defendants, informants, witnesses, bailiffs, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💬 Routine judicial procedures, such as case statement, cross-examination, prompting of testimony, judge’s review, and sentencing, are all carried out step by step. During the two-hour hearing, the court’s operation was shown in detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💻 During the review process, the Division of Justice’s “Sentencing Trend Suggestion System” was used. Judge Jiang also demonstrated its operation on the spot. Its main function is to integrate the content of tens of thousands of rulings into a database and target different crime scenarios and constituent elements. This will not only help a judge in sentencing, but anyone who is curious or has doubts about sentencing can enter relevant parameters on the system, such as the alcohol exhalation concentration of drunk driving, or the type of transportation, then the recommended sentencing reference range will be displayed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💁 Based on this system, my colleagues in the Information Division of the Court of Justice this year teamed up with civilian information experts to participate in this year’s “Presidential Cup Hackathon” competition. The new version of the system produced can directly read judgments through artificial intelligence, and can get sentencing suggestions without having to enter individual parameters. This proposal has also been selected as one of this year’s outstanding team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗺️ The sentencing information system and the Shilin District Court’s “Let’s Go To Court” event are aimed at creating a justice system that people are willing to get close to. This is consistent with the concept of “open government”, that is, the use of transparency and participation to build mutual trust. And in the process of service design, how to balance justice, quality and efficiency? The answer lies in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ndc.gov.tw/en/Content_List.aspx?n=E35FD251AA134CA4&quot;&gt;Government Digital Services Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">The highlight was a mock court held by classmates from the 9th class of the Lanya Junior High School and staff members from the Shilin District Court.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0a7b70bfdaf3a3ad2ee76bf8d676d5d49cf67723.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0a7b70bfdaf3a3ad2ee76bf8d676d5d49cf67723.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Collaborating for Democracy</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91%E5%8D%94%E5%8A%9B-%E9%81%B8%E8%B3%A2%E8%88%87%E8%83%BD/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Collaborating for Democracy" /><published>2019-12-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91%E5%8D%94%E5%8A%9B-%E9%81%B8%E8%B3%A2%E8%88%87%E8%83%BD</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%85%A8%E6%B0%91%E5%8D%94%E5%8A%9B-%E9%81%B8%E8%B3%A2%E8%88%87%E8%83%BD/">&lt;p&gt;🔝 As the election approaches and the relevant discussions become more heated, the topic of disinformation has become the focus once again. This April, the transnational political science research project Varieties of Democracy (V-Dem) released the latest annual database, which pointed out that the degree of attack to Taiwan by overseas actors in 2018 was “No. 1 in the world,” highlighting this this issue as one of our most imminent challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✍️ How can we tackle such a complex issue? In December 2018, the Executive Yuan issued “A Special Report on the Preventing and Countering Disinformation,” committing to provide real-time clarifications on government-related issues. More importantly, the government encouraged major social media platforms to sign the “Self-Regulation and Best Practices for Disinformation Prevention and Control.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔢 For example, LINE launched a &lt;a href=&quot;https://fact-checker.line.me/&quot;&gt;Digital Accountability Dashboard&lt;/a&gt; this year. In collaboration with four organizations, among which was the g0v grant winner — the “Cofacts” project — LINE they set up an official account to allow the public to report disinformation, which are sent to collaborating organization will provide clarified information. At present, more than 140,000 rumors have reported there, and the total number of unique messages has exceeded 30,000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🤹 At the same time, the civil society volunteered themselves into the mission of preventing the harm of disinformation. In May 2019, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.readr.tw/project/fact-check-2020&quot;&gt;2020 President Candidate Fact Checking Project&lt;/a&gt; was born in Hackathon run by the civic tech community “g0v” (gov-zero) in Taipei.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🧩 This large-scale planning, which involves news media, web platforms, and civilian communities, originates from the Internet platform Readr. The team founder H.C. Chien, also a long-time participant in the public community, got this idea when he took part in the Hackathon, “The more media are willing to collaborate, the more likely it will be to complete the whole collage.” Then, he began to reach out across various communities in the Hackathon, which led to the involvement of many media platforms and citizen communities, such as the PTS “P# News Lab” and “Watchout”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚧 There are several steps in this plan: first, find out a candidate’s public speech video, allow the netizens to transcribe it verbatim, which will then be verified, sorted, and then submitted to the news media to verify the content. At present, 14 media and cooperative units and nearly 1,000 netizens have joined the team of verbatim transcribing and fact checking. The verification is currently in full swing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗽 Many people are worried that disinformation will mislead the public and change the results of the election. In my opinion, the greatest harm of disinformation lies in ruining people’s understanding of democracy, leading us to feel that democracy makes it impossible for us to listen to each other, letting alone achieving consensus. No matter whether it is the “LINE Information Verification,” or the “2020 President Candidate Fact Checking Plan,” they embody the social spirit of “everyone’s matter, everyone helps,” deepening our democracy through civic participation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">“The more media are willing to collaborate, the more likely it will be to complete the whole collage.”</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7174287ad0e4063fdb6b84ac8882406c3c6805be.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/7174287ad0e4063fdb6b84ac8882406c3c6805be.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Social innovation for a better world</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%81%8B%E7%94%A8%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E6%88%90%E5%B0%B1%E6%9B%B4%E5%A5%BD%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Social innovation for a better world" /><published>2019-12-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%81%8B%E7%94%A8%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0,%E6%88%90%E5%B0%B1%E6%9B%B4%E5%A5%BD%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%81%8B%E7%94%A8%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%89%B5%E6%96%B0-%E6%88%90%E5%B0%B1%E6%9B%B4%E5%A5%BD%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C/">&lt;p&gt;“Social innovation” has become a worldwide trend in recent years, leading to countless conscious and spontaneous movements from citizens. In a nutshell, social innovation is “everyone’s problem, everyone helps”: Everyone uses innovative methods to spontaneously invest and participate in things that contribute to the world, and then change the relationship between different groups in society and find solutions for the common problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This cross-departmental collaboration not only blurs the boundary between society and business, which transforms the thinking of non-profit organizations, but also allows organizations with different missions to exist in various forms. How to assist the organizers who have worked hard on their own to become a symbiotic ecosystem is my goal as the Digital Minister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Executive Yuan has a total of 32 ministries, each with a different mission. Except for the Central Bank, it can be considered as 31 non-profit organizations (NPOs). Social innovation covers a wide range of levels and involves a large number of stakeholders. A single ministry is often limited by planning schedules and budget constraints. If the administrative department decides on the development strategy alone and then hands it to the social sector for implementation, the latter is a subordinating “assistant,” which is difficult to effectively reflect the trend of the new era or provide the most appropriate solution. On the other hand, if social innovation is initiated by the social sector and government agencies become “partners” in collaboration, this system is not only more flexible but also more effective in grasping the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Switching from assistants to partners has been a major shift in the government’s public policy in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;partnership-in-taiwan&quot;&gt;Partnership in Taiwan&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2014, the government launched a three-year “Social Enterprise Action Plan,” an important step in ecosystem construction. The Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), which began in 2015, have made social innovation the common language of the world. At that time, the United Nations Development Summit released the “2030 Sustainable Development Policy,” which proposed 17 sustainable development goals, including 169 specific projects, as the global vision for 2030.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the advent of SDGs, friends who had worked hard alone started to see each other again. Regardless of environmental work, social work, or economic work, as long as the spirit of sustainable development is entertained, all work is like a puzzle and can be put together. For a shared mission, it is easier for people from different fields to come together and exert more power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, in 2018, we launched the “Social Innovation Action Plan” promoted by various ministries. Different from the previous attempts, the Plan includes social sectors such as social enterprises and non-profit organizations. As long as there is a clear social mission and innovation model, any type of organization can become a “social innovation organization,” and partner with various ministries to assist each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;three-links-in-social-innovation&quot;&gt;Three links in social innovation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on this concept, the “Social Innovation Platform” was officially established this year. On the Platform, anyone can see the current status of the 400 social innovation organizations across Taiwan and the ongoing development goals. As the partnership progresses, the main axis of the current “Social Innovation Action Plan” is gradually being shaped, which can be summarized as “three links.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-first-link-is-the-link-between-society-and-business&quot;&gt;The first link is the link between “Society” and “Business.”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From public fundraising to block chain, the social sector has broken through the linear development of traditional enterprises. At the same time, whether it is circular economy or green energy and other industrial innovations, everyone needs to get involved, and all parties need each other’s innovations. In this process, the government plays a role in helping both sides focus. Therefore, I travel around Taiwan to meet and talk with local social innovation organizations on a regular basis, so that issues in the social sector can be responded to promptly, and that government departments can also be aware of the energy of innovation in the social sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, through the social innovation platform, anyone can come to the social innovation experiment center to talk with me for up to 40 minutes. In March last year, the “Ucarer Platform,” which provides short-term home care for the matches, put forward the concept of “time coin” in the Social Innovation Center. Thus, volunteers can store their contributions and love for future use when needed. In addition to assisting in confirming the responsible business unit, I also provide the “Platform Economic Development Regulations Adaptation Reference Principles” as a development basis for the suggestion. This year, they have established the form of B2B cloud services and decided to set up a company with a mission of public benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In response to the rapid development of cross-departmental and cross-organizational entities, regulations must also keep pace with the times. Based on the spirit of “innovation regulations sandbox platform,” we allow those who innovate to be free from laws and regulations within a certain period of time, to experiment all they want, and to promote law and other administrative plans after things get focused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, last year, we completed a demonstration case of a corporate legal person setting up a closely held corporation. This year, we have also added a “Protection Clause for the Rights and Interests of Cooperative Members” in the labor procurement contract. These measures not only move the barriers for the folk people, but can also promote government departments to drive legal innovation through social innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-second-link-is-the-link-between-mission-and-organization&quot;&gt;The second link is the link between “mission” and “organization.”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the perspective of the social innovation organization, as the organization may expand in the future, the mission will inevitably turn around. Conversely, to promote a mission, it may be appropriate to use this organizational type now and switch to another in the future. An example is the transformation of Good Sheperd Associations into a closely held corporation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the journey of social innovation, whether it is promoting the mission or operating the organization, it is often part of achieving the 17 global sustainable development goals. How can abstract missions be mapped onto specific indicators? This is called accountability in the public sector and, in the parlance of the social sector, “giving an explanation.” The internal explanation is given to employees, stakeholders, and acquaintances, which aims at the cohesion of the organization. The external explanation is to spread the mission so that more friends can continue the idea and carry it further on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, we now encourage social innovation organizations, be they for-profit, non-profit, or cooperative, who have registered on the social innovation platform, to disclose their purposes, constitutions, and public welfare reports. In this way, whether it is the continuation of the organization or the sustainability of the mission, it can be guaranteed through the culture of “public accountability.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-third-link-is-the-link-between-sustainability-and-transformation&quot;&gt;The third link is the link between “Sustainability” and “Transformation.”&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Transformation” happens in various aspects, such as the baton between generations—how to invite the youth to set the direction, and then the elders to use their wisdom to ensure its feasibility. When talking about digital transformation, many people think of getting paperless and electronic. In fact, the significance of digital transformation is to use digital methods to do something with other people first, and then recognize each other, so as to establish a collaborative relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the whole world, no matter what kind of transformation, if it is confined to a single field, it often lacks social cohesion, and can hardly significantly improve the overall development. The value of Taiwan is that friends from all walks of life who are engaged in social innovation are thinking about the common interests of the next generation and the next two generations. Upholding the spirit of “sustainability,” this generation, whether committed to economic, environmental, or social transformation, recognizes the real beneficiaries will be our future generations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;looking-at-the-earth-with-a-telescope&quot;&gt;Looking at the earth with a telescope&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In August of this year, NASA announced that the James Webb Space Telescope was officially assembled. It will be launched to the second Lagrangian point on the extension line of the sun and the earth in 2021. In the future, no special power will be required to maintain its relatively stable distance with the earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter where we are on the earth’s surface, our vision is always limited and we cannot see its other side. But from space, observing the rotation of the earth through a telescope, we may really think about the whole picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, this telescope symbolizes all friends who are engaged in social innovation. The main lens on the James Webb Space Telescope is a splicing of 18 hexagonal lenses, just like each of us as a part of society. At first we get together and then we go our own ways, but we can still be like a puzzle to work together to build a vision for the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I look forward to more people joining the puzzle in the future, looking at the earth from space, and using social innovation together to achieve a better world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Switching from assistants to partners has been a major shift in the government's public policy in recent years.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/389c86bb31c3831eb2924187e65709c96ac95d2c.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/389c86bb31c3831eb2924187e65709c96ac95d2c.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Make railways more friendly to companion animals</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%89%93%E9%80%A0%E5%B0%8D%E5%90%8C%E4%BC%B4%E5%8B%95%E7%89%A9%E6%9B%B4%E5%8F%8B%E5%96%84%E7%9A%84%E5%8F%B0%E9%90%B5/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Make railways more friendly to companion animals" /><published>2019-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%89%93%E9%80%A0%E5%B0%8D%E5%90%8C%E4%BC%B4%E5%8B%95%E7%89%A9%E6%9B%B4%E5%8F%8B%E5%96%84%E7%9A%84%E5%8F%B0%E9%90%B5</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%89%93%E9%80%A0%E5%B0%8D%E5%90%8C%E4%BC%B4%E5%8B%95%E7%89%A9%E6%9B%B4%E5%8F%8B%E5%96%84%E7%9A%84%E5%8F%B0%E9%90%B5/">&lt;p&gt;🐶 In August of this year, the blog “Travel of Rice” proposed “Pet-friendly cars on rails: Specification and specific measures” on the Join.gov.tw participation platform, asking the Taiwan Railway Administration (TRA) of the Ministry of Transport to relax the “Article 46 of the Passenger Transport Contract” so that large and medium-sized cats and dogs can also ride with their owners. This is also the second time the blogger “Mi Da” has made a proposal on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚆 Even before the proposal received 5,000 joint signatures, Taiwan Railways proactively raised this issue through Ministry of Transport’s “Participation Officers Network”, at the inter-ministerial meeting of “Monthly Participation Officer Meetings”, proposing to organize collaborative meetings for this case. This courageous attitude and willingness to discuss the solution face-to-face with netizens is highly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚃 According to Article 46 of the Passenger Transport Contract of the Taiwan Railway, except for guide dogs such as guide dogs and deaf dogs, If pets are to board the railway with their owners, they must be packed in pet boxes and bags with a length, width, and height of 43, 32, and 31 cm, respectively, and must be packed and placed under the seat. On the one hand, such a size limitation will inevitably cause difficulties for larger pets and will make some owners feel timid. However, on the other hand, the space and conditions for pets on the train must not be without standards, otherwise, it may crowd other passengers and affect the operation of the Taiwan Railway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎨 In order to make the collaborative meeting more focused, and at the same time to find a solution that is acceptable to all parties and concrete and feasible, my office (Public Digital Innovation Space, PDIS) and colleagues of the Taiwan Railways carried out a series of stakeholder meetings before the collaborative meetings. In addition to pet owners and general passengers, a number of train captains and station attendants are also included to understand the experience and feelings of frontline staff. On the day of the collaboration meeting, we also invited a number of seconders of the case and veterinarians to participate in the discussion to ensure the diversity and equity of opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✅ Today, it’s great to know that just over a month after the coordination meeting, the Taiwan Railways decided to adopt the consensus of the meeting and conduct a three-month trial since December. Compared with the high-speed rail, the size restrictions for the length, width, and height of pet cages were relaxed to 55, 43, and 38 cm. This allows more owners of medium and large pets to choose one more means of transportation and reduce the inconvenience caused by different standards when transferring between the Taiwan Railway and different vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚄 Finally, in addition to wishing the trial a complete success, I also want to thank all the participants and Minister Lin Chia-lung for their contributions in this matter. I hope there will be more opportunities for collaboration in the future, let us work together to make Taiwan Railways more friendly to companion animals.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">The Taiwan Railways decided to adopt the consensus of the meeting and conduct a three-month trial to relax the size restrictions of pet cages.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/85e2d3ea857fa9f8f79910c37b73e080c02f4136.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/8/85e2d3ea857fa9f8f79910c37b73e080c02f4136.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Collaboration meeting: “Core Question Discovery” across sectors</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0-%E5%85%AC%E7%A7%81%E7%A3%A8%E5%90%88%E7%9A%84-%E6%89%BE%E5%87%BA%E6%A0%B8%E5%BF%83%E5%95%8F%E9%A1%8C/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Collaboration meeting: “Core Question Discovery” across sectors" /><published>2019-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0-%E5%85%AC%E7%A7%81%E7%A3%A8%E5%90%88%E7%9A%84%E3%80%8C%E6%89%BE%E5%87%BA%E6%A0%B8%E5%BF%83%E5%95%8F%E9%A1%8C%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0-%E5%85%AC%E7%A7%81%E7%A3%A8%E5%90%88%E7%9A%84-%E6%89%BE%E5%87%BA%E6%A0%B8%E5%BF%83%E5%95%8F%E9%A1%8C/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;agenda-setting-or-core-question&quot;&gt;Agenda setting or core question?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Open Government-Collaborative Meeting”, as a type of policy discussion for citizen participation, has a similar but not the same idea as a regular deliberative meetings, called “finding the core questions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This link may be called “agenda setting” in the design of civic participation or deliberative processes. “Double Diamond”, also known as “confirmation problem definition”, is explained by PDIS as a feature of collaboration meeting: starting from the concept of service design, hoping that participants can try to use “How Might We?” Thinking as a question or challenge and start a discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter what these details are called, the things they are doing are actually very similar, hoping to allow participants to discuss under a focused problem awareness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the reading of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/notes/%E6%9E%97%E5%9C%8B%E6%98%8E/%E5%A4%9A%E5%85%83%E5%AF%A9%E8%AD%B0%E8%88%87%E5%85%AC%E6%B0%91%E7%A4%BE%E6%9C%83%E5%AF%A9%E8%AD%B0%E6%B0%91%E4%B8%BB%E6%8C%87%E5%8D%97%E5%B0%8E%E8%AE%80-%E6%9E%97%E5%9C%8B%E6%98%8E/442060615817584/&quot;&gt;Guide to Deliberative Democracy&lt;/a&gt;, when collating the differences between various review forums, Mr. Lin Guoming mentioned that the “agenda setting” is oriented towards: “some review modes, such as citizen consensus at the conference, the participants can set the discussion topics themselves, let the participants identify the problem and find solutions; some can only discuss the topics provided by the organizer such as a citizen jury, or from a set options to express opinions such as deliberative polls. “&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From this we can see that the agenda is set up with the two ideals of “open up for the common development of the people” and “the organizers have set up in advance”, and collaborative meetings can hardly be classified as either. The reason is that most of the launch of the collaborative meeting comes from the public’s proposal, that is, from the “idea” of the National Development Association’s public policy network participation platform (Join platform). The current mechanism, in addition to the ministry’s own proposals, is usually the National Development Council that first counts the proposals that have reached the threshold for joint signing, and then enters the monthly meeting of the PO (Participation Officer, Open Government Contact Person) to vote and select the topics for the collaborative meeting. The authority responsible for this issue will be the host of the collaborative meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;is-it-for-the-public-or-government-to-decide&quot;&gt;Is it for the “Public” or “Government” to decide?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the source of the proposal originates from the people, the general direction of the issue is of course highly related to the content of the proposal, but the proposal comes from the people. The executive organs of the meeting are held.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, according to the design process of the “Double Diamond” mentioned above, in the first half of a collaborative meeting, a divergent issue inventory will usually be performed first, and then the “core questions” defined by participants expect will be summarized. So ideally, this process is at the scene of the collaboration meeting, which was jointly formulated by government agencies and the participating people, such as Case 4 of the collaboration meeting: “Promote the concept of universal driving, improve the quality of the driving environment of the entire public, and lift the slow lane of the embargo machine. “Release the forced two-step left turn”, on the day of the meeting, through the brainstorming of the participants, the major issues of the proposal were condensed, such as: the proportion of driving safety and traffic smoothness, because the two-step pending transition was unclear or sub-topics such as poor design, and extended discussions on the basis of consensus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there are also many collaborative meetings that emphasized the “find the core questions” during the preparatory period, and adjusted the agenda before the formal meeting. Taking the collaborative conference in the second half of 2019 as an example, the so-called “issue setting” link, or the process of “finding the core questions”, actually takes place in more advanced preparation processes, such as the “work conference” and the “pre-conference meetings”. These preparatory processes have public verbatim records that present the context of discussions at the conference site. From the many records, the most important process of the pre-conference meeting of the collaborative meeting is the PDIS team and the main co-organizer confirm the “core questions” discussed on the day of the collaborative meeting. And usually the title of a public proposal is not the same as the “core question.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pulling the setting of “core questions” from the conference to the early stages of preparations seems to reflect that the organizer has “the power to set the agenda” before the conference. Why would such intervention be needed? Although the ideal of a collaborative meeting is to follow the shape of “Double Diamond”, it is actually difficult to condense all the links in one and a half days. As a result, the collaborative meeting developed links such as “ex-ante interviews” and “writing topic manuals”. First, the work of the first Diamond should be completed as much as possible, which is equivalent to using mental maps to try to face various issues and issues as much as possible. Inventory is complete. I hope that at the conference site, we can focus on “core questions” for discussion under the situation of information synchronization and confirmation of disputes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-core-question-is-not-your-core-question&quot;&gt;My core question is not your core question&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on my limited observations at the moment, the on-site discussions are not always in the direction of the “core questions” expected by the PDIS team and the organizer, and the participant may still emphasize the points he originally intended. However, the tool list designed with the core questions and chaired by the small table leader during the group discussions can indeed make the scope and focus of the discussions more biased toward the “core questions” expected by the organizer. There are good and bad ways to do this, and what to do depends on the positioning of the collaborative meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter where the core questions are formulated, there may be situations where “my core is not your core”. For example, the proposal on the Join platform in 2018 (Collaborative Meeting No. 38): “Revised the implementation of the memorial day and festival in Article 5, section 2 and paragraph 4, adding paragraph 5 that police, firefighters in during the collaborative meeting of the Police Festival and Fire Festival, we issued the direction of “regression problems and analysis from the causes of overwork”. Although we can claim that this is the “core of the problem”, we should extensively check and find out a “fundamental” solution, but the proponent believes that &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/zh-TW/blog/%E8%AD%A6%E6%B6%88%E4%BC%91%E5%81%87%E5%8F%AF%E8%A1%8C%E5%97%8E-%E5%8D%94%E4%BD%9C%E6%9C%83%E8%AD%B0%E7%99%BC%E6%83%B3%E7%9B%B8%E9%97%9C%E9%85%8D%E5%A5%97/&quot;&gt;“the conference should not discuss the issue of overwork, but should focus on the feasibility of a day off as a tangible benefit for the frontline police.”&lt;/a&gt;, which shows that he still hopes that his proposed solution is the focus of this focused discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;core-questions-are-not-rigid&quot;&gt;Core questions are not rigid&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some collaboration issues seem to be “core questions” have been “set” first, but at the scene of the collaboration meeting, members of the PDIS team will play the role of hosting and recording during the meeting. The core questions will also be adjusted in real time depending on the state of mind map inventory and the content of live speeches. Before the collaborative meeting was held, the ministry also conducted interviews and data collection based on the problem awareness of the proposal, and the original title of the proposal was used as the name of the meeting at the scene and live broadcast of the collaborative meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the day of the collaboration meeting, before the discussion begins, the step will arrange the first report of the sponsor to remind all participants of the starting point of the collaboration meeting. The “core questions” set through the collection and consolidation of data in advance are the driving force that the organizers hope to guide, but not every case can be carried out at the scene as expected. Trying to balance the “core questions” that different stakeholders care about is the hardest and most important task for the host team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;meaning-of-civil-participation&quot;&gt;Meaning of civil participation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does the case 38 of the above-mentioned collaboration meeting have a process of “pulling back higher-level structural problems, taking a broader inventory, and finding out the core of the problem based on factual information,” many cases of holding collaboration meetings have opinions or solutions from the public, going back to the higher structure system to explore the retrospective process of core questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the perspective of the people, it seems that the government has not directly responded to their need. However, from the perspective of the administrative departments, “civic participation” does not mean that the administrative departments must accept 100% of the public’s suggestions. After all, the 5,000 people attached to the Join platform proposal do not necessarily agree with every point of the proposal, only the problems and dilemmas behind it. If a collaborative conference can truly become a routine and normal operation mechanism, and encourage more administrative agencies to take the initiative to organize a conference of convening multiple stakeholders and promoting communication and dialog, the importance of taking into account the position and opinions of the host and co-organizer when setting agendas are greatly enhanced. Moreover, the administrative departments related to the issue are equivalent to the stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The PDIS team encourages administrative agencies to first disclose the feasible solution scope of the policy. In this way, they have a better chance to deal with the issue and achieve the desired effect of the public. As the administrative agencies and the public have different positions, understandings, and familiarity with policies, it is necessary to find a pragmatic agenda direction that is taken into account by all parties. Because if the proposal is too far away from reality, or if it is implemented only in accordance with the literal recommendations of the public, it may face short-term obstacles and difficulties, and the scope of the solution will not significantly improve the issue itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, the PDIS team implements the “open government” business. In the implementation process of the open government, it must pay attention to the original intention of the people’s proposal. In addition to playing a more neutral role (relative to the main ministry) in the presiding process, it must also from the perspective of the executive, the public sector is convinced that “citizen participation” is not so far away from them, and “cooperative meetings” are a dialog platform for mutual understanding, rather than a role that is only one-sided and passively accepting needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breaking away from the dichotomy between the public and the government of the proposal, if it is expected that the discussion results of the collaborative meeting can become the direction of policy participation, the alignment of internal positions of the agency and the scope of the solution are inherently necessary. Many constructive opinions and solutions are the effects that collaborative meetings trying to promote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the proposal of the people, the space for discussion was started, and then the administrative organs thought about the setting of a meeting, until the on-site opinions were run in. This cross-sectoral process that enabled participants to “discover” together an unsatisfactory but acceptable solution is, to me, one of the most interesting and unique aspects of PDIS “collaborative meetings” that sets it apart from other “citizen participation” or “deliberative meetings”.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>En-En Hsu</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">The government is not acting unilaterally to accept the demand for proposals, so collaborative meetings have a unique “core question discovery” process.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b0a083062fe581db4cdb9084050e70ff0ce40e4f_2_1380x776.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/optimized/2X/b/b0a083062fe581db4cdb9084050e70ff0ce40e4f_2_1380x776.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Talents don’t get lost, only circulated</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E4%BA%BA%E6%89%8D%E4%B8%8D%E6%98%AF%E6%B5%81%E5%A4%B1-%E8%80%8C%E6%98%AF%E5%BE%AA%E7%92%B0/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Talents don't get lost, only circulated" /><published>2019-11-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E4%BA%BA%E6%89%8D%E4%B8%8D%E6%98%AF%E6%B5%81%E5%A4%B1-%E8%80%8C%E6%98%AF%E5%BE%AA%E7%92%B0</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E4%BA%BA%E6%89%8D%E4%B8%8D%E6%98%AF%E6%B5%81%E5%A4%B1-%E8%80%8C%E6%98%AF%E5%BE%AA%E7%92%B0/">&lt;p&gt;🛰 This April, the Talent Circulation Alliance (TCA), jointly sponsored by the American Institute in Taiwan (AIT), the Ministry of Economic Affairs and the Ministry of Economic Affairs, was officially established.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 My office (Public Digital Innovation Space, PDIS) was also invited to provide technical services for the online public consultation conducted by TCA. Similar to the Digital Dialogue series jointly organized by AIT and the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, the pol.is system has been used to construct a dialogue platform (📲website: &lt;a href=&quot;https://tca.talksto.tw&quot;&gt;tca.talksto.tw&lt;/a&gt;) to enable participants interested in this topic to express opinions and brainstorm ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄 Brain drain is regarded by many people as a serious national issue. Yet, when we consider the example of Morris Chang, founder of TSMC, we can see that as long as a conducive environment and system exist, talents do not just flow in one direction but rather in circulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📶 The experience sharing, cultural integration and social interaction promoted by a transnational mobility process enabled the value of talent circulation flow into all levels of society. Of course, teleworking arises with 4G and 5G technologies, further enabling mutual exchange of talented people at speed of light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍀 TCA aims to cultivate a talent pool that possesses professional competence, international vision and digital technology expertise. Four goals have been proposed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔭 First, recreating a success story for Taiwan’s industry in a digital age. In fact, one of the key reasons that Taiwan’s industry has been able to develop to its current state is because of the repatriation of talents who have studied or worked abroad. As long as this story can continue, the circulation of talents in Taiwan will surely extend into the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💼 Second, promoting the circulation of talent among like-minded economies, including the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎫 Third, building a local talent pool and laying a foundation for Taiwan’s transformation into an innovation-based economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌐 Fourth, enhancing Taiwan’s international visibility through professional exchange in the private sector, academic circles, and international NGOs, expanding Taiwan’s participation in and contribution to global solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📖 In addition, TCA will summarize the key content of the above public consultation into the “Talents Program Big League Plan White Paper”, which will be incorporated into the annual “Taiwan White Paper” of the American Chamber of Commerce. It will target the administrative, regulatory and legal barriers to talent circulation and propose concrete and pragmatic solutions as a reference for subsequent governments to work on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🥇 In September this year, the “Expat Insider” survey released by the world’s largest foreigner community “InterNations” indicated that Taiwan is considered by foreigners all over the world as the “best place to move to and work in”. It came first in a list of 68 countries and this is the second time that Taiwan has won this award. This confirms that Taiwan indeed possesses excellent conditions for attracting talents from around the world and can definitely hold its own in the global talent cycle.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Taiwan is considered by foreigners all over the world as the “best place to move to and work in.”</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d2d9c7bf3088d67c5150e2e658a5dcae2f3a6e66.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/d/d2d9c7bf3088d67c5150e2e658a5dcae2f3a6e66.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sharing not only a Common Origin, but also a Common Future</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AA%E5%85%B1%E5%90%8C%E8%B5%B7%E6%BA%90-%E6%9B%B4%E8%A6%81%E5%88%86%E4%BA%AB%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sharing not only a Common Origin, but also a Common Future" /><published>2019-11-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AA%E5%85%B1%E5%90%8C%E8%B5%B7%E6%BA%90-%E6%9B%B4%E8%A6%81%E5%88%86%E4%BA%AB%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AA%E5%85%B1%E5%90%8C%E8%B5%B7%E6%BA%90-%E6%9B%B4%E8%A6%81%E5%88%86%E4%BA%AB%E6%9C%AA%E4%BE%86/">&lt;p&gt;🌍 Over the past three years, I have led a delegation to participate in the “Social Enterprise World Forum” every year. This year was no exception. The conference was held in turn on each of the five continents. In October, myself and 45 partners from all over the world went to Ethiopia in Africa to share Taiwan’s experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔬 For many people, the African continent seems far away. But in this forum, I have seen that the challenges faced by our friends in Africa are the same problems that Taiwan has faced. For our African friends, our experience is precious. The “$1 Fast Screening for Tuberculosis” treatment from WellGen Medical in Taiwan is one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;😷 At present, the main detection method for tuberculosis is the analysis of sputum, collected by the hospital, through a microscope by an laboratory technician. This practice is not only time- and labor-consuming, but also makes it difficult to accurately confirm the results. The global infection cases are still high. In 2018, more than 250,000 children and 1 million adults died of tuberculosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏥 To this end, the automatic microscopy system developed by WellGen Medical, combined with AI image recognition, can greatly reduce the cost of tests, in addition to improving case detection sensitivity and solving the issue of insufficient medical staff in remote areas. Take the example of the WHO-recommended xPert detection tool, where each use costs almost US$10. Through this new system, the quick tuberculosis screening costs US$1 each time. At present, WellGen Medical’s revenue is gradually expanding, and they are already planning on deploying the system worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇹🇼 The practice of the Taiwanese government has also struck a chord locally. Before, the CEO of Skills for U, Huang Weixiang, proposed in the Executive Yuan’s Youth Advisory Committee that after the team received the award from the national vocational skills competition, they can also participate in on the spot education. Not only will they be cheered in the National Day parade, but they will also be self-sufficient. At the “Youth Participation in Innovation” session, I explained how the youth lead our policies. Eleni Zaude Gabre-Madhin, an economist on the panel, was impressed. After the meeting, Eleni invited me to visit blueSpace, her co-working space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🍹 Three years ago, Eleni founded blueMoon, Ethiopia’s first innovation incubator that combines agricultural enterprises and youth development while striving to train outstanding young entrepreneurs aged 15 to 29, as an investment in agricultural improvement and innovation. BlueSpace is a service provided by blueMoon. “How can we spread African food to the whole world?” When I arrived, many young innovators were discussing the brand marketing of African agriculture. I received a warm response when I brought up the case of successfully converting Taiwanese bubble tea into various products and how it became an example of a creative global cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👣 The unearthing of the famous hominid fossil “Lucy” in Ethiopia has made East Africa widely regarded as the origin of mankind. I believe that discussing social innovation in our ancestral continent is indeed of great significance. The descendants of Lucy stepped out of Africa and opened up human civilization. Just like many pioneers on the road to social innovation — they have become an example for others to follow.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Discussing social innovation in our ancestral continent is indeed of great significance.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0ce59c16b3a62d6c85908d7370e1fe69664dacd0.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/0ce59c16b3a62d6c85908d7370e1fe69664dacd0.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Can’t Stop This Party</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%97%E5%85%B6%E6%AD%A1%E6%A8%82/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Can't Stop This Party" /><published>2019-11-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%97%E5%85%B6%E6%AD%A1%E6%A8%82</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%BE%97%E5%85%B6%E6%AD%A1%E6%A8%82/">&lt;p&gt;🔽 The “Can’t Stop This Party” is holding its founding meeting this afternoon. In recognition of the idea that joy promotes generational integration and realizes freedom and democracy, I sent a flower basket based on catmint as a token of my blessing and support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌱 More than 20 years ago, several young people put forward the concept of “Happy &amp;amp; Hope,” in an attempt to dilute the tragic atmosphere accumulated in the development of democracy, and to open up more communication and understanding between generations and ethnic groups through different means. The results are well known: They have turned politics around in Taipei, and further, Taiwan’s fortunes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🥭 Today, the so-called “Dried Mango” reminds us that we are indeed facing formidable social and environmental challenges. For many friends, caution and seriousness are essential. There’s nothing wrong with that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌳 But, a brave, confident, and undivided Taiwan is the premise of all answers. In other words, if we get caught in the internal conflict and stop listening to each other, we might risk losing the liberal democracy we cherish today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏡 Therefore, any way to promote dialogue and build consensus deserves encouragement and experiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 That is where the hope is.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">A brave, confident, and undivided Taiwan is the premise of all answers.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bd6de5956479ae028b84d4b3c6e9196d9bf766f1.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bd6de5956479ae028b84d4b3c6e9196d9bf766f1.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Taiwan Can Help in Bangkok</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/Taiwan-Can-Help-%E5%9C%A8%E6%9B%BC%E8%B0%B7/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Taiwan Can Help in Bangkok" /><published>2019-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/Taiwan-Can-Help-%E5%9C%A8%E6%9B%BC%E8%B0%B7</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/Taiwan-Can-Help-%E5%9C%A8%E6%9B%BC%E8%B0%B7/">&lt;p&gt;🇹🇭 On October 21, I participated in the “Conference on Social Innovation and Civic Participation”, jointly organized by the Taiwanese Ministry of Foreign Affairs’ Representative Office in Thailand, the Faculty of Communication Arts of Chulalongkorn University and the German Friedrich Naumann Foundation (FNF). In addition to the Participation Officers of the National Development Council, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and the Public Construction Commission, there were also a representative from IISI International, Inc.; Johnson Liang, the co-founder of the Cofacts project; and a meteorologist, Dr. Chi-Ming Peng.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸 It is worth noting that the main contents of this seminar include Taiwan’s promotion of the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), the use of open-access materials to improve the quality of life, countering internet disinformation, and expanding citizen participation in public policy, and so on. Every item is the result of cooperation between government, business, and citizen communities. In other words, the focus of the discussion is not just “what we did”, but “how we did it together”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Taking social innovation as an example, I shared the story of the development of the Innovation Center; the social issues dealt with by the winners of the Presidential Hackathon winners of the past two years and the implementation of sustainable development goals; opening up a weekly Office Hour as well as touring town halls, minimizing the information gap between urban and rural areas;  and using the “Social Innovation Lab” to really grasp issues immediately by responding to social issues encountered by our friends, and letting social innovations drive regulatory innovation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎙️ In addition, thanks to the arrangements of the Representative Office, I took separate and in-depth interviews on the same day with the Thai Public Broadcasting Service, Chulalongkorn University, A DAY, Post Today, and Workpoint. It is readily apparent that Taiwan’s practical experience has received attention from across Thai society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙋 The section on citizen participation was presented by the Ministry of Foreign Affair’s Public Affairs section chief, Mr. Qian Muxian, and the Public Construction Commission committee member Mr. Zhang Zhaoqi. The presentation opened with the government’s four key values of “Transparency, Participation, Accountability, and Inclusion”, and then explaining the functions of the NDC Public Policy Network Participation Platform (JOIN), and then continuing to the inter-departmental openings of the government liaison system. “Requesting a National Airborne Service Corps at Hengchun Airport” and  “Using Tax-Income Software Leads to Blowups” are two examples of the network process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🤝 They introduced the inter-departmental participation officers networks; how to clarify petitioner’ core demands; interviews with multiple stakeholders to collect opinions weekly; inviting service users to join in the process and participate in actual planning, and completing the meeting process and publicly responding to specific procedures to find feasible and innovative solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌏 “Taiwan Can Help” is the core message of the government in recent years. This is not just a slogan, but a dependable experience and resource that can contribute internationally. With help from all sectors of Taiwan, I’m glad to see that this Bangkok trip proves yet again: Taiwan Can Help.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">The focus of the discussion is not just “what we did”, but “how we did it together”.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/66f950eecd95b45469cbb174f3f7d4dee281c484.jpeg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/6/66f950eecd95b45469cbb174f3f7d4dee281c484.jpeg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>