<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-07-30T14:06:17+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/feed.xml</id><author><name>PDIS</name></author><entry><title type="html">Apple column: Discussing “empty house tax” stop watching</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E8%A8%8E%E8%AB%96-%E7%A9%BA%E5%B1%8B%E7%A8%85-%E5%81%9C%E7%9C%8B%E8%81%BD/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple column: Discussing &quot;empty house tax&quot; stop watching" /><published>2019-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E8%A8%8E%E8%AB%96%E3%80%8C%E7%A9%BA%E5%B1%8B%E7%A8%85%E3%80%8D%E5%81%9C%E7%9C%8B%E8%81%BD</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E8%A8%8E%E8%AB%96-%E7%A9%BA%E5%B1%8B%E7%A8%85-%E5%81%9C%E7%9C%8B%E8%81%BD/">&lt;p&gt;In May of this year, netizens participated in the platform proposal of the China Development Council’s public policy network, arguing that “the empty house tax should be levied”. The case was approved by the Executive Yuan’s “Open Government Liaison Meeting” and became the theme of the 51st Collaborative Meeting. A collaborative meeting was held on July 19th. It is expected to be confirmed by the Ministry of Finance and the Ministry of the Interior at the end of this month. Publicly respond on the platform](https://join.gov.tw/idea/detail/348212d3-179e-4789-9e1e-ff2bcf4c00c8).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here, it can be pre-shared that during the preparation of the collaborative meeting, by interviewing stakeholders and analyzing statistical data, my office (Public Digital Innovation Space, PDIS) found that if you want to explore The feasibility of the “empty housing tax” has at least the following three questions, which must be clarified first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, the proportion of “low-use (electricity) housing” in each county and city has no significant positive correlation with house prices. “Low use (electricity) housing” is a statistical analysis of the use of tax information and Taipower electricity data by the Construction Department of the Ministry of the Interior. According to the latest statistics, there were nearly 865,000 low-income (electricity) dwellings in the country in November and December 2017, accounting for 10.12% of the total number of houses. This ratio was 11.49% in 2009.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to match the time, PDIS simultaneously queried the statistics of the “Household Affordability Indicators” conducted by the Ministry of the Interior in the fourth quarter of 2017, and found that the top six counties in the “price-to-income ratio” in that quarter were Taipei City (14.99 times), New Taipei City (12.71 times), Taichung City (9.61 times), Changhua County (8.79 times), Hsinchu County (8.62 times), Kaohsiung City (8.22 times). At the same time, the proportion of “low-use (electricity) housing” in the above six counties and cities is 6.73%, 7.65%, 9.66%, 11.78%, 11.13% and 10.53%, respectively. It can be seen from this that the relationship between the proportion of “low-use (electricity) housing” and housing prices is still open to question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, “low-use (electricity) housing” has many causes and it is difficult to generalize. In terms of regional statistics, it may be that the population is moving out, or it may be the accumulation of unsold surplus houses. In addition, a certain house will be used at a low level, except for those held by investors and not yet rented out. It is because the building is remote and the ownership is so complicated that the owner does not want to manage and many other factors. In short, the multi-dimensional nature behind the phenomenon of “low-use (electricity) housing” cannot be ignored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, PDIS and the organizer will select the “low-use (electricity) residential” data as the basis for this collaborative meeting. However, after the discussion on the same day, we also found that if we use water resources and field visits, we can better enable local governments to accurately grasp the quantity, type and distribution of “empty houses” in their respective jurisdictions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposal for a public policy participation platform often involves many levels of social phenomena. Through this collaborative meeting, we hope to clarify the facts as much as possible, so that future discussions will be more focused and traceable, and we welcome everyone to continue to pay attention to the follow-up response.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">If the water use data and the on-site visits are conducted, it will enable local governments to accurately grasp the quantity, type and distribution of &quot;empty houses&quot; in their respective jurisdictions.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c90126ea4dc7daa2c64754190d534851232265a2.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Beyond Flatland: Machine learning and the end of the two-party binary</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E5%B9%B3%E9%9D%A2%E5%9C%8B-%E6%A9%9F%E5%99%A8%E5%AD%B8%E7%BF%92%E5%92%8C%E4%BA%8C%E5%85%83%E9%BB%A8%E6%B4%BE%E7%9A%84%E7%B5%82%E7%B5%90/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beyond Flatland: Machine learning and the end of the two-party binary" /><published>2019-07-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-07-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E5%B9%B3%E9%9D%A2%E5%9C%8B:%E6%A9%9F%E5%99%A8%E5%AD%B8%E7%BF%92%E5%92%8C%E4%BA%8C%E5%85%83%E9%BB%A8%E6%B4%BE%E7%9A%84%E7%B5%82%E7%B5%90</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E5%B9%B3%E9%9D%A2%E5%9C%8B-%E6%A9%9F%E5%99%A8%E5%AD%B8%E7%BF%92%E5%92%8C%E4%BA%8C%E5%85%83%E9%BB%A8%E6%B4%BE%E7%9A%84%E7%B5%82%E7%B5%90/">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This article was originally published JUNE 24, 2019 in &lt;a href=&quot;https://civichall.org/civicist/beyond-flatland-machine-learning-end-two-party-binary/&quot;&gt;Civicist&lt;/a&gt;. It is republished here under the &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/&quot;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In democracies worldwide, billions of citizens hold an untold number of interests, opinions and positions. Political reality on the ground is vastly more complex than our political symbols and categories allow us to express. Our political choices are artificially constrained by existing abstractions that either compress us into just two large opposing parties, or in the case of proportional representation systems, a mix of smaller parties. Either way, the real complexity of people’s opinions is squashed. There are thousands of overlapping interest groups, not just two tribes. There are hundreds of thousands of issues and sub issues, not the small handful the media focus on during election cycles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elections and referendums severely constrain the information populations are able to send to governing bodies. Our current methods of compressing the will of the masses into party platforms, for example, leave out the 42% of Americans who now identify as independents, and whose voices are excluded from the policy formation process at every step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://content.gallup.com/origin/gallupinc/GallupSpaces/Production/Cms/POLL/euflbdw5d0uafxwbcx14dg.png&quot; alt=&quot;Gallup party identification independents&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.gallup.com/poll/245801/americans-continue-embrace-political-independence.aspx&quot;&gt;Gallup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The numbers are about the same in the United Kingdom. This is especially true after Brexit. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/new-centrist-party-politically-homeless-brexit-labour-conservative-poll-a8312991.html&quot;&gt;According to the Independent&lt;/a&gt; “Millions of voters feel politically homeless and would consider backing a new centre-ground party … almost half of those questioned … said both that they did not feel represented by any established party and that a new organisation would have a chance of winning their vote.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc221_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc221_0.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc221_0.png&quot;&gt;The Economist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a democratic population, what we ‘see’ is heavily influenced by what our representations allow us to see. Political parties are like a very low resolution photograph, obscuring critical aspects of what voters might actually want or what they would be willing to accept. Making things worse, party platforms cast off consensus issues in favor of wedge issues useful for gaining power. The Brexit referendum, alternatively, wrapped up thousands of issues into a binary vote and created a new lens — “Leave” or “Remain” — through which to see the polity. The scourge of polarization and deadlock in modern politics is a function of our mechanisms for simplifying citizen input like these, not a feature of our constitutions, governmental structures, or our populations. We live in a political flatland because our categories and our tools for thinking about ourselves and others are one dimensional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What might it offer us to make meaning of our political spaces — of ourselves as a body of citizens — as a whole, in more dimensions and in higher resolution? To answer this question, we’ll need to look to alternative methods of citizen participation, ways that move past resolving every issue by relying on a handful of critical votes like the vote for President or referendums like Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Office of Presidential Correspondence under President Obama’s Administration &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/17/magazine/what-americans-wrote-to-obama.html&quot;&gt;gave us a glimpse&lt;/a&gt; of a data source and process. During Obama’s tenure, the White House received roughly 10,000 letters per day from ordinary people. They were read by a rotating group of 300 volunteers and a handful of dedicated staff, who selected 10 letters for the President to read each day. The 10 letters were chosen as the best compromise — broadly representative of the population’s thoughts and feelings while accepting that he couldn’t possibly read and digest the full spectrum of what was pouring in. They were the result of a kind of compression algorithm run by a particularly empathic, qualitatively oriented human computer, fed a raw input of the population’s agenda in its own words. This was a process deeply rooted in respect for the human voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This practice is not common, however. Recently, I spoke with an individual on the staff of one of the major departments in the US federal bureaucracy. The department was facing a public comment period in which they were expecting nearly one million comments. There was a single Federal employee tasked with reviewing the million plain-text comments. The same policy process would also see input from focused industry lobbyists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While we now live in an age of mass participation, where everyone has a multitude of ways of expressing their voice, our formal government structures haven’t caught up. Today’s democracies are still shortchanging their opportunities to enhance issue-based democratic policy making. As a result, there is enormous pressure to discuss every issue during an election season — a process that predictably leaves citizens feeling unsatisfied and the government without a discernible mandate. We need a scalable compression mechanism for making better meaning of the rich, qualitative data citizens can provide. Could we automate, scale and improve on the process that happened in Obama’s letter room?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the problems of democratic governance need special consideration, processing this scale of input is not a new problem to industry. Netflix, for instance, drives production decisions by using automated data collection and analysis: the company looks at the behavior of its expansive TV- and movie-watching population and use that data to suggest other shows to viewers, as well as to inform decisions about what new shows to produce. The results of their analysis have overturned conventional thinking about who would want what, as Janko Roettgers &lt;a href=&quot;https://variety.com/2017/digital/news/netflix-lab-day-behind-the-scenes-1202011105/&quot;&gt;wrote in Variety&lt;/a&gt; in 2017:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Netflix used to recommend content based on the region that its users were in, following the general school of thinking that subscribers in South America probably would prefer different fare than subscribers in Canada. But upon looking closer at the data, the company realized that this wasn’t actually true,” Netflix VP of Product Todd Yellin said. “We find that to be greater and greater nonsense, and we are disproving it every day.”Instead, Netflix is now dividing up its subscriber base into 1,300 taste communities, which are solely based on past viewing behavior. Each and every user can belong to multiple such communities, and all of these communities spread across the globe. Sure, Yellin admitted, German comedians may be more popular in Germany, but there’s also plenty of users in the U.S. who turn into their shows. “A big part of personalization is finding taste communities globally,” Yellin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result of this data analysis &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2014/01/how-netflix-reverse-engineered-hollywood/282679/&quot;&gt;are categories&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vulture.com/2018/06/how-netflix-swallowed-tv-industry.html&quot;&gt;far more niche&lt;/a&gt; than the one dimensional &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gutenberg.org/files/201/201-h/201-h.htm&quot;&gt;flatland&lt;/a&gt; of ‘Comedy’ and ‘Drama.’ In fact, Netflix breaks movies into 76,000 categories like “Scary Cult Movies from the 1980s,” “Brain Food Docs,” and “Fight-the-System TV Shows.” Movies can belong to multiple categories, just like viewers can belong to multiple taste communities. For Netflix, the goals are clear: better recommendations and more views mean higher customer engagement, and thus retention. The more valuable the platform is, the more likely people are to recommend it and new customers are to join.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Machine learning, along with a substantial profit motive, has rendered the most accurate portrait of the global movie and TV watching public ever created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that Netflix (and the rest of us) can look more accurately at the signals created by large populations, we’re all seeing more details, and finer grain categories that describe us. Netflix can ‘see’ a lot more of the preferences of their community, because they have rendered a more detailed portrait of the complex preference space than Blockbuster ever did. If Netflix presupposed there were only a handful of categories — comedy, drama, horror, war, sports — that would define the resolution it would see its users. It would also influence the resolution at which its users would see themselves, and the language they would have to describe themselves. Imagine if we had the same fine-grained, real-time awareness of the complexity of public opinion across all issues, even issues the government isn’t aware of or ready to consider yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are better ways to represent citizens using machine learning, and these representations can be meaningful in the policy process and lead to better policy outcomes. Driven by the communication challenges inherent in protest movements like Occupy and the Arab Spring, this problem led our software team to create the open source data science platform Polis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polis &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nesta.org.uk/blog/crowdsourcing-democracy-using-wikisurveys/&quot;&gt;offers a rough ethnography&lt;/a&gt; of a population, showing areas of consensus and disagreement across an immense spectrum of possibilities. The math inside it is roughly the same as the recommender engines Spotify or Netflix are using – it’s looking for similarities and differences among people, as well as global consensus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the fall of 2016, I was in Turin, Italy, speaking at the Scuola di Tecnologie Civiche (School of Civic Tech) conference. Italy was focused at the time on the upcoming constitutional referendum, which was to decide the fate of the powers of the Italian executive branch, as well as Renzi’s presidency. Announcing the referendum, Renzi threatened to resign if he lost his bid to centralize powers (he lost, and did resign).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the behest of the organizers, I ran a mock deliberation on the referendum in an intimate setting of forty attendees. Opinions regarding the referendum were submitted by participants, who agreed and disagreed on statements submitted by other attendees. As participants took positions on the statements submitted by their peers, Polis’ machine learning algorithms ran automatically on the resulting opinion matrix. Think: a spreadsheet where the columns are statements instead of movies, and the rows are voters rather than movie watchers, and each cell is an agree or disagree rather than a rating. The algorithms surfaced patterns of opinion amongst participants across all statements, and formed clusters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some obvious opinion clusters emerged – those in favor of Renzi and centralization and those opposed. But a simple, piercing statement by one participant garnered unanimous support: “Referendums shouldn’t be used as an election surrogate.” Regardless of where they stood or their level of expertise, participants agreed that Renzi had invalidated the referendum by threatening to resign if his side lost – thus ensuring the opposition of political rivals regardless of their stance on the constitution. Meanwhile, across other statements, it was clear that a number of Renzi opponents were open to changing the constitution. What was an absolutely polarized issue  when viewed through the lens of a binary vote on a referendum, was in fact a public with complex and nuanced views, willing to consider various propositions and tradeoffs, and eager to challenge the processes by which they were being represented. Running engagements around the world, we’ve seen that same pattern play out again and again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of mid 2019, Polis has been used by multiple national governments, in one high profile case, it served as an input to facilitate rulemaking in the process of &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.pol.is/uber-responds-to-vtaiwans-coherent-blended-volition-3e9b75102b9b&quot;&gt;regulating Uber&lt;/a&gt; in Taiwan. It’s proven able to overcome long standing deadlocks on complex issues with highly polarized stakeholders by visualizing common ground, as in Taiwan’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.technologyreview.com/s/611816/the-simple-but-ingenious-system-taiwan-uses-to-crowdsource-its-laws/&quot;&gt;debate on online alcohol sales&lt;/a&gt;. Canada’s federal government has now run multiple engagements, one of which involved the future of Canada’s visual arts marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polis was recently run in Germany with over &lt;a href=&quot;https://aufstehen.de/pol-is/&quot;&gt;30,000 people&lt;/a&gt;, who produced nearly two million votes on hundreds of crowd submitted statements. Columbia University ran a pilot in Bowling Green, Kentucky, with thousands of Americans participating (roughly 2% of the population of the city) who live in a purple district. This was &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.civic-assembly.org/bowling-green-report/&quot;&gt;written up as a report&lt;/a&gt; as well as in &lt;a href=&quot;https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2018/12/political-polarization-bowling-green-study-kentucky-immigration.html&quot;&gt;Slate&lt;/a&gt;, and covered by &lt;a href=&quot;https://civichall.org/civicist/testing-tech-consensus-purple-town/&quot;&gt;Civicist&lt;/a&gt;. New Zealand’s Department of Conservation is running public engagements with partners in independent media, and Singapore’s Ministry of Culture is talking to thousands of youth at a time. New York City’s Department of Homeless Services is running conversations related to homelessness with frontline staff, who are all able to testify to their experiences in their own words, which can be validated by their colleagues and peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no barrier to scaling the method up to the entire voting-age population of a democracy by strategically sampling, say, 10,000-20,000 people at a time, or even creating ‘always on’ citizen assemblies of that scale or much larger. The challenge now is integrating new computational methodologies with stubborn, legacy policy making processes. We also have a collective choice, whether these models of the public are to be defined by open data and reproducible, open methods, or proprietary and unable to be audited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not every decision in a representative democracy will involve the public. But when the government does go to the public, seeking legitimacy and wisdom about the population’s lived experiences and preferences, democratic institutions can do better. The government can engage the public on issues and sub issues. It can engage people in rich and dynamic ways that let them know their voices are heard. It can engage the population early — when there are more problems to solve than pages of legalese written — and involve them in agenda setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New capabilities for reconciling complexity at scale in democratic populations mean new assumptions regarding the representation of populations. Future democratic systems must be much more effective at managing and integrating qualitative signals from the population at scale to avoid polarized deadlock. Systems of representative government were intentionally designed to break the back of faction. Crippled by faction, we as democratic populations should honor that tradition, and keep designing.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Colin Megill</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Crippled by faction, we as democratic populations should honor that tradition, and keep designing.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/a/a51ab24bd076a61d3d1b07f4ffda418bf88dc724.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Promoting U.S.-Taiwan Economic and Commercial Ties</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%A2%9E%E9%80%B2%E5%8F%B0%E7%BE%8E%E7%B6%93%E8%B2%BF-%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AA%E6%98%AF%E6%97%81%E8%A7%80/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Promoting U.S.-Taiwan Economic and Commercial Ties" /><published>2019-07-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-07-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%A2%9E%E9%80%B2%E5%8F%B0%E7%BE%8E%E7%B6%93%E8%B2%BF-%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AA%E6%98%AF%E6%97%81%E8%A7%80</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%A2%9E%E9%80%B2%E5%8F%B0%E7%BE%8E%E7%B6%93%E8%B2%BF-%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AA%E6%98%AF%E6%97%81%E8%A7%80/">&lt;p&gt;🌐 Many think international relations is the sole domain of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs. But given the rise of public and digital diplomacy, as well as Taiwan’s unique international status, it should be seen as collaborative effort among the citizenry, public and private sectors. It is also the most effective way of finding new solutions and realizing common values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 In April, the American Institute in Taiwan, MOFA and my office (Public Digital Innovation Space, PDIS) launched &lt;a href=&quot;https://talkto.ait.org.tw/&quot;&gt;AIT@40 Digital Dialogues&lt;/a&gt;. This series consists of discussions taking place in April, June, August and October on how to improve each of the four main pillars of the U.S.-Taiwan relationship: “Taiwan’s role in the global community,” “U.S.-Taiwan economic and commercial relations,” “U.S.-Taiwan security cooperation” and “U.S.-Taiwan people-to-people ties.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📲 This collaboration is the first time the U.S. has publicly gathered diplomatic suggestions over the internet. Equally significant, it explores ways of enriching public relations through collective wisdom to improve exchanges and tie-ups with a strategic ally on multifaceted topics. This new benchmark shows that U.S.-Taiwan relations are at an all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📈 Currently, the topic we are discussing is &lt;a href=&quot;https://ait-polis.pdis.nat.gov.tw/8bscsvxb3z&quot;&gt;how to improve the U.S.-Taiwan economic and commercial partnership&lt;/a&gt;. There is no question in my mind that the Digital Dialogues is the best platform to share ideas and opinions on key issues at the heart of this vital aspect of the bilateral relationship. These include mutually beneficial strategies for managing potentially detrimental trade wars, bilateral trade agreement talks and U.S. incentives for firms to relocate manufacturing bases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔝 According to statistics from the Ministry of Finance, the U.S. is Taiwan’s only major export destination recording an increase in shipments during the first half of 2019. The 17.4 percent year-on-year rise is no mean feat given the instability of global markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇺🇸 At the Select USA Investment Summit held by the U.S. Department of Commerce in Washington last month, Taiwan’s delegation numbered more than 100. This was highest among all countries, indicating that many homegrown businesses are ahead of the curve and already moving to get a piece of potential-laden action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🗣 It comes as no surprise, then, that U.S.-Taiwan trade and related matters will dominate the open forum I am hosting in mid-August to discuss and provide feedback on resonating ideas from the Digital Dialogues. The participation of officials from the AIT, U.S. Chamber of Commerce and relevant local ministries is certain to offer fascinating insights on issues impacting the Taiwan-U.S. economic and commercial ties, as well as the stability and prosperity of the Indo-Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🙋 I invite all and sundry to attend the event and help advance related participatory policymaking. Only through collaboration can we truly be more than the sum of our parts.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">Only through collaboration can we truly be more than the sum of our parts.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/4/4f35e160c3cfc113fd1db2eccf4c03c231f56a71.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Age of Digital Interdependence</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%B8%E4%BD%8D%E4%BA%92%E8%B3%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%99%82%E4%BB%A3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Age of Digital Interdependence" /><published>2019-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-07-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%B8%E4%BD%8D%E4%BA%92%E8%B3%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%99%82%E4%BB%A3</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%B8%E4%BD%8D%E4%BA%92%E8%B3%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%99%82%E4%BB%A3/">&lt;p&gt;This summary has been prepared by Nissaba, a new initiative to provide concise, readable and actionable news and analysis on digital policy developments around the world. If you find this document useful, and want to see more information of this quality, please consider helping us to keep the initiative going: https://www.nissaba.net&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The United Nations High-Level Panel on Digital Cooperation released its 47-page report The Age of Interdependence on 10 June. This is a very short summary aimed to help time-poor readers understand the main points of the report. The full report of the UN Secretary General’s High-Level Panel on Digital Cooperation, The Age of digital interdependence, is &lt;a href=&quot;https://digitalcooperation.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/digitalcooperation-report-for-web.pdf&quot;&gt;available here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The introduction of the report contextualises the reasons for the panel and its report:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Digital technologies are changing and touching every part of our lives.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While digital technologies are improving our lives in many ways, they also pose significant risks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The panel was asked to look at ways digital technologies can help achieve the 17 goals of the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Around half of the world’s population still do not have access to the Internet.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The speed of digital development is getting faster all the time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We need to act now to find better ways of managing digital governance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Digital governance can benefit from utilizing the best of both multilateral and multistakeholder processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;declaration-of-digital-interdependence&quot;&gt;Declaration of Digital Interdependence&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The report invites all stakeholders to commit to a Declaration of Digital Interdependence: Humanity is still in the foothills of the digital age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The peaks are yet uncharted, and their promise still untold. But the risks of losing our foothold are apparent: dangerous adventurism among states, exploitative behaviour by companies, regulation that stifles innovation and trade, and an unforgivable failure to realise vast potential for advancing human development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How we manage the opportunities and risks of rapid technological change will profoundly impact our future and the future of the planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that our aspirations and vulnerabilities are deeply interconnected and interdependent; that no one individual, institution, corporation or government alone can or should manage digital developments; and that it is essential that we work through our differences in order to shape our common digital future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We declare our commitment to building on our shared values and collaborating in new ways to realise a vision of humanity’s future in which affordable and accessible digital technologies are used to enable economic growth and social opportunity, lessen inequality, enhance peace and security, promote environmental sustainability, preserve human agency, advance human rights and meet human needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;possible-digital-cooperation-architectures&quot;&gt;Possible digital cooperation architectures&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The panel presents three possible architectures that could contribute to ongoing discussions on digital cooperation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;1-internet-governance-forum-plus&quot;&gt;1. Internet Governance Forum Plus&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would work on policies and norms of direct interest to stakeholder communities.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To consist of: Advisory group, Cooperation accelerator, Policy incubator, Observatory, Help desk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To have a dedicated IGF Trust Fund.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;2-decentralized-co-governance-architecture-cogov&quot;&gt;2. Decentralized co-governance architecture (“COGOV”)&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Build on existing mechanisms and fill any gaps with new mechanisms using a self-forming ‘horizontal’ network approach (e.g. IETF, ICANN).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Decouples the design of digital norms from their implementation and enforcement.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Three functional elements: Digital cooperation networks, Network support platforms, Network of networks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;3-digital-commons-framework&quot;&gt;3. Digital Commons Framework&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Governments, civil society and business to work together to ensure digital technologies promote the 2030 Sustainable Development Goals.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multi-stakeholder tracks would discuss emerging issues, then come together at an annual meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;underpinning-values&quot;&gt;Underpinning values&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The panel identified nine values that should shape the development of digital cooperation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Inclusive&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Respect&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Human-centeredness&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Human flourishing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Transparency&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Accessibility&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sustainability&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Harmony&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;recommendations&quot;&gt;Recommendations&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;1-create-an-inclusive-digital-economy&quot;&gt;1. Create an inclusive digital economy&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Provide every adult with affordable access to digital networks and digitally-enabled finance and health services by 2030.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A broad, multi-stakeholder alliance, involving the UN, to create a platform for sharing “digital public goods”, engaging talent and pooling data sets in areas related to attaining the SDGs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support full digital inclusion for women and marginalized groups; international institutions to focus on women and inclusive technology in research.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Develop metrics on digital inclusiveness, including gender-disaggregated data, for worldwide use and reporting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;2-strengthen-human-and-institutional-capacity&quot;&gt;2. Strengthen human and institutional capacity&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Establishing regional and global digital help desks to help governments, civil society and the private sector understand digital issues and build capacity to steer their social and economic impacts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;3-protect-human-rights-and-human-agency&quot;&gt;3. Protect human rights and human agency&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UN Secretary-General to conduct a UN agencies-wide review of how existing international human rights accords and standards apply to digital technologies. All stakeholders should be encouraged to provide input.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Social media companies to respond to concerns about existing or potential human rights violations around the world, in consultation with governments, civil society and human rights experts.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Engage multiple stakeholders to develop ethical standards for the design and application of accountable and non-biased AI systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;4-ensure-digital-trust-security-and-stability&quot;&gt;4. Ensure digital trust, security and stability&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Develop a Global Commitment on Digital Trust and Security to shape a shared vision, attributes of digital stability and norms for responsible uses of technology, as well as propose priorities for action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;5-update-mechanisms-for-global-digital-cooperation&quot;&gt;5. Update mechanisms for global digital cooperation&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UN Secretary-General to hold an open consultation process to create up-to-date mechanisms for global digital cooperation with three architecture options (described earlier in summary) as a starting point: Internet Governance Forum Plus, Distributed co-governance architecture, Digital commons architecture.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;May involve the appointment of a Technology Envoy.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support a new, multi-stakeholder, “systems” approach for regulation that is adaptive, agile, inclusive and fit for purpose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Nissaba</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Humanity is still in the foothills of the digital age. The peaks are yet uncharted, and their promise still untold.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/b/bdb25714dbd3e9287ba64f5bea7ae75b3385edbf.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">National Champions and National Day</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%9C%8B%E6%89%8B%E8%88%87%E5%9C%8B%E6%85%B6/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="National Champions and National Day" /><published>2019-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%9C%8B%E6%89%8B%E8%88%87%E5%9C%8B%E6%85%B6</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%9C%8B%E6%89%8B%E8%88%87%E5%9C%8B%E6%85%B6/">&lt;p&gt;💯 A piece of good news for everyone — National champions of the WorldSkills Competitions (WSC) will be part of this year’s National Day Parade to receive everyone’s applause! National skill champions and vocational education of all trades will be the highlight of the National Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👷 These are not my words, but those of Executive Yuan Youth Advisory Committee member and Skills for U CEO Huang Wei-xiang. They come from the first paragraph of a post on Facebook page Craftsmanship Insights, posted on June 11.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 Most readers would know Taiwan is an “invisible champion” in many fields, serving as the mainstay of various industries. Taiwan’s famous cuisine, in particular, has received worldwide praise these two years as Taiwanese restaurants gain a presence in the Michelin Guides. However, we should all acknowledge the soul behind Taiwan’s excellent products and services in multiple fields —  the veterans cultivated by vocational education.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎉 In fact, Taiwan’s skill veterans have long been shining on the international stage. WorldSkills Competitions is a biennial event hosted by the 81 member states of WorldSkills International, and the competition is so fierce it is considered to be an Olympics of skills. In the 44th WSC of 2017, Taiwan won four gold medals, one silver medal, and 27 bronze medals, with a winning rate of 88%; in 2015, Taiwan won five gold medals, seven silver medals, and 19 bronze medals, ranking 3rd place overall. These results are no doubt first class in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🥇 Regrettably, such excellent results were not well known in Taiwan. This has caused the disproportional resources allocation on the part of the government, as well as a misunderstanding of the Taiwanese on the strength of the country. Fortunately, Huang Wei-xiang’s proposal alongside with Executive Yuan President Su Tseng-chang’s prompt instructions, and Legislative Yuan President Su Jia-chyuan’s full support have allowed these veteran’s skills to come into light in the National Day celebrations this year, so that they can receive their deserved acknowledgment and acclaim from both nationals and foreign guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Today’s results are made possible by the Yuan-level Youth Advisory Committee, programmed and founded by Executive Yuan’s former Premier, Lin Chuan. They are also concrete proof to Lin’s original intention fulfilled: the members’ deep insights into public policies, active participation and suggestions have brought overall innovation to policy execution.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Youth Engagement" /><summary type="html">The national team of the World Skills Competitions (WSC) will be part of this year's National Day Parade to receive everyone’s applause!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/c/c9a67a08ad4ef90821636f4c30fea558d2880ada.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">“Quadratic Voting” and “Common Ownership Self-Assessed Tax”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%B9%B3%E6%96%B9%E6%8A%95%E7%A5%A8%E6%B3%95-%E8%88%87-%E5%85%B1%E6%9C%89%E8%87%AA%E8%A9%95%E7%A8%85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="“Quadratic Voting” and “Common Ownership Self-Assessed Tax”" /><published>2019-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E3%80%8C%E5%B9%B3%E6%96%B9%E6%8A%95%E7%A5%A8%E6%B3%95%E3%80%8D%E8%88%87%E3%80%8C%E5%85%B1%E6%9C%89%E8%87%AA%E8%A9%95%E7%A8%85%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%B9%B3%E6%96%B9%E6%8A%95%E7%A5%A8%E6%B3%95-%E8%88%87-%E5%85%B1%E6%9C%89%E8%87%AA%E8%A9%95%E7%A8%85/">&lt;p&gt;🗳 As I have &lt;a href=&quot;https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/商周專欄-你來許願-全民-還願/&quot;&gt;mentioned earlier in this column&lt;/a&gt;, this year’s Presidential Hackathon has successfully adopted the newly invented quadratic voting (QV) system so that the voting results for proposals will be more in line with the needs of the people. Incidentally, the Colorado state legislature in the United States had also used QV to vote on their budget priorities. Taiwan and the US have achieved significant milestones in the establishment of a new form of democratic governance in administrative and representative politics respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎪 QV is part of the recent “radical” intellectual current. In 2018, the inventors of QV, Principal Researcher at Microsoft Research Glen Weyl and Eric Posner from the University of Chicago Law School co-authored the book “&lt;a href=&quot;http://radicalmarkets.com/&quot;&gt;Radical Markets&lt;/a&gt;.” In addition to the articulation of QV, the book offers five different proposals on how to change the way our societies are modeled. The book led to heated debates in academia and the community, and was featured by “The Economist” as one of the books of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📢 Glen Weyl and Eric Posner believe that with regard to public affairs, individuals tend to hold different opinions and are reluctant to share their private knowledge with others. If more people can be encouraged to share their genuine opinions through well-designed market mechanisms, the society can work collectively to find better solutions to existing problems. The QV system hinges on the idea that “a higher concentration of votes requires more points,” which encourages people to vote according to their true preferences instead of concealing their actual inclinations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💰 Another novel concept in the book is the Common Ownership Self-Assessed Tax (COST), which allows people to declare the price of their assets but for which they would have to pay an annual fixed tax. If a buyer offers to purchase the asset at the declared price, the owner of the asset cannot refuse to sell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🛒 The idea behind COST originated from the fact that although a person’s appraisal of value may be subjective (especially for intangible assets), this “Harberger Tax” mechanism can still effectively discourage price gouging as well as promote transparency, increase liquidity, and prevent hoarding. Through market design, people can share their actual preferences and information with others, which is the origin of the radical market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎 Glen Weyl and Vitalik Buterin (co-founder of Ethereum) launched the RadicalxChange (RxC) Foundation to advance these principles, and I was invited to work pro-bono as a board member along with the political philosopher Danielle Allen. In the past, civil servants were prohibited from holding concurrent appointments in foreign non-profit organizations, but after this restriction was lifted by the Ministry of Civil Service in October last year, all civil servants can now participate in international organizations in social innovation with the prior permission of the authorities. This was also a change that we had pushed for in the public sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 The evolution of social innovation is based on different intellectual trends. The theories and methods developed by these currents are an important means by which we can achieve our social mission. Starting from the accomplishments of QV in Taiwan and the US, I hope that my civil servant colleagues can be more active in international non-profit organizations in the future and imbibe prevailing intellectual currents more swiftly. These ideas can be applied to their official work and be a source of inspiration for social innovation in Taiwan, which will in turn be disseminated to the international community and contribute significantly to the world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Aafter this restriction was lifted by the Ministry of Civil Service in October last year, all civil servants can now participate in international organizations in social innovation with the prior permission of the authorities.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/0/06b90db7e18c8b1d288d2f565ae1141f14483a11.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Open Government meets Open Parliament</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E9%81%87%E4%B8%8A%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%8B%E6%9C%83/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Open Government meets Open Parliament" /><published>2019-06-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-06-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E9%81%87%E4%B8%8A%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%8B%E6%9C%83</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E6%94%BF%E5%BA%9C%E9%81%87%E4%B8%8A%E9%96%8B%E6%94%BE%E5%9C%8B%E6%9C%83/">&lt;p&gt;⚖️ On May 31st, my office (Public Digital Innovation Space, PDIS) was invited by MP Ch’iu Chih-wei to take part in the preparation and implementation of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=2677074105864517&amp;amp;id=1588286501409955&quot;&gt;Public Hearing&lt;/a&gt; on “Non-Disclosure of Information under Investigation”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎙️ This is the first time that we have tried a new mode of cooperation with the Legislative branch, marking a new chapter in Taiwan’s progress of open government. On this occasion, I would like to express my gratitude and affirmation of MP Ch’iu Chih-wei’s invitation and breakthrough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🆕 There are three main points of difference between this public hearing and those in the past:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;👂 First, we conducted a comprehensive series of pre-hearing interviews. Previously, organizers would invite as many stakeholders as possible to take part so that a diversity of opinions could be collected. However, an increase in the number of attendees and speakers often led to time restrictions on each speaker to express and exchange opinions at the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💬 In view of this, the PDIS host team and the committee office conducted a total of 10 interviews prior to the meeting. Through a painstaking investigation of the “non-disclosure of information under investigation regime” and detailed records, we made sure that all participants have received the &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1mmEO8WPOzB8XDs4V0XMSmbO39I1ZkOZDTxks0J7cx-0/edit#heading=h.jgexw6fafmb&quot;&gt;stakeholders’ complete views and suggestions&lt;/a&gt; one week in advance. In other words, the synchronization and focus of opinions had already begun before the meeting officially started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📊 Second, like other major policy issues, the context of the “non-disclosure of information under investigation regime” is profound and far-reaching. In order to enable all participants as well as viewers watching the live webcast in real time to keep up with the rhythm of the discussion and not “lag behind” in the process, we used &lt;a href=&quot;https://miro.com/app/board/o9J_kx42gKI=/&quot;&gt;Issue Mapping&lt;/a&gt; as an auxiliary tool on the hearing day. That is to say, using the charts, the non-disclosure of information under investigation regime was divided into several major programs, the implementation process and difficulties of each individual program was listed, and the causal relationship between them was linked in the correct order, so that everyone could just “click the map and follow the track” at any time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📜 Third, the public hearing was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M4laQWtbK4o&quot;&gt;livestreamed&lt;/a&gt; and open to online questions. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://sayit.pdis.nat.gov.tw/2019-05-31-%E8%90%BD%E5%AF%A6%E5%81%B5%E6%9F%A5%E4%B8%8D%E5%85%AC%E9%96%8B%E5%85%AC%E8%81%BD%E6%9C%83&quot;&gt;complete transcript&lt;/a&gt; was published on the PDIS website (&lt;a href=&quot;https://track.pdis.tw/&quot;&gt;track.pdis.tw&lt;/a&gt;) afterwards. The purpose of doing so was not only to have a complete record of the meeting but also to allow relevant discussions to continue beyond the meeting and to provide a reference guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 This successful endeavor paves the way to future cross-institutional collaborations. On the 31st, Executive Yuan member Ch’iu Chih-wei also said that he will be conducting another public hearing three months after the implementation of the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://mojlaw.moj.gov.tw/LawContent.aspx?LSID=FL068478&quot;&gt;Non-Disclosure of Information Under Investigation Act&lt;/a&gt;” on June 15th. We look forward to more Legislative public hearings and to further cooperations with MPs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">This opportunity is not only the first time we have tried a new mode of cooperation with the legislators' office, but also a new chapter in the process of Taiwan's promotion of open government and the opening of the Congress.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/e/ec5471e279d887cd99eb619ea8960dca9790691f.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The changing and unchanging National Palace Museum</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%85%E5%AE%AE%E7%9A%84%E8%AE%8A%E8%88%87%E4%B8%8D%E8%AE%8A/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The changing and unchanging National Palace Museum" /><published>2019-05-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%85%E5%AE%AE%E7%9A%84%E8%AE%8A%E8%88%87%E4%B8%8D%E8%AE%8A</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E6%95%85%E5%AE%AE%E7%9A%84%E8%AE%8A%E8%88%87%E4%B8%8D%E8%AE%8A/">&lt;p&gt;🏰 What crosses your mind when someone mentions the “National Palace Museum”? Is it its rich collection of treasures and solemn courtyards, or its status as an international museum with a long history that is still able to keep up with the times and dare to embrace the spirit of openness and collaboration?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💡 Since last month, my office (PDIS, the Executive Yuan’s Public Digital Innovation Space) has officially launched a collaborative program with the Forbidden City at the invitation of the National Palace Museum’s President, Wu Mi-cha. In the next few months, we will be assisting the National Palace Museum in redesigning programs such as automatic ticket purchases, online bookings and entry lines. Through processes such as interviews with multiple stakeholders; completely recorded collaborative discussions with users and full process preliminary testing and other procedures, the National Palace Museum will be offering visitors a convenient and comfortable ticket purchasing experience that is closer to their true feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📖 This represents another step forward by the National Palace Museum on its path of openness and collaboration. In July two years ago, under the impetus of former president Lin Cheng-i, the National Palace Museum opened more than 70,000 cultural relics in the form of open materials, so that any person could download and use them free of charge. Under the continuing efforts of the two succeeding presidents, Ch’en Ch’i-nan and Wu Mi-cha, the number of open materials has reached more than 100,000. Although the speed and quantity of the materials are still not as strong as the materials offered by the Metropolitan Museum of New York or the National Palace Museum of the Netherlands, the National Palace Museum is already at the forefront and has great symbolic significance compared to similar tier museums in Asia. In the near future, the National Palace Museum will continue to expand and deepen the quality of its open materials with the support of the forward-looking infrastructure budget. This is well worth everyone’s anticipation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔮 Furthermore, the National Palace Museum has demonstrated ingenuity in its innovative use of new media. In February last year, I “inhabited” a free-moving robot that was equipped with a 360-degree panoramic lens. In my first visit to the Southern Court of the National Palace Museum, President Lin Cheng-i and hundreds of people were online at the same time, along with viewers who watched the video afterwards. Together, we viewed the “The Pinnacle of Japanese Art: Exhibit from the Collection of Tokyo/Kyushu National Museum” which was extremely rare to see in Taiwan. For me, this viewing experience that transcended temporal and spatial constraints definitely represented a new path to enable the National Palace Museum to improve publicity and establish new paradigms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌈 The essence of the National Palace Museum lies in its steadfast preservation of its precious collection that captures fleeting beauties in moments of history; at the same time, how the Museum should adapt to the times so that more viewers can use multiple ways to gain access and understand the National Palace Museum represents not only an opportunity for us to grasp but also a responsibility for us to achieve change.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Zach Huang</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Open Government" /><summary type="html">In the next few months, we will be assisting the National Palace Museum in redesigning programs such as automatic ticket purchases, online bookings and entry lines.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/776a1eae5095de146f2e2547fd26e3122ad0b9c6.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">From ”warm power” to ”global impact”</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%BE%9E-%E6%9A%96%E5%AF%A6%E5%8A%9B-%E5%88%B0-%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="From ”warm power” to ”global impact”" /><published>2019-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%BE%9E%E3%80%8C%E6%9A%96%E5%AF%A6%E5%8A%9B%E3%80%8D%E5%88%B0%E3%80%8C%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B%E3%80%8D</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E5%BE%9E-%E6%9A%96%E5%AF%A6%E5%8A%9B-%E5%88%B0-%E5%BD%B1%E9%9F%BF%E5%8A%9B/">&lt;p&gt;📈 In the business field, whether to invest in a product or service, the investment report rate (Return on Investment, ROI) is often an important reference. Through calculation of the financial formula, the balance of loss and benefit can be understood at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;❓But this approach is difficult to apply directly to activities of public interest. For example, the three-wheeled cars I have introduced, or the “voting guide” website, these innovations result in the public interest which is often hard to represent as the number of input into the report formula. How can we prove that these achievements are effective? This is an important issue in the innovative field of society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🔄With this increasing demand, many impact assessment methods have been born. For example, the Social Reporting Standard (SRS) set up by the European Union’s Social Reporting Initiative (SRI). Based on the IOOI (input / output / outcome / impact), it presents in its entirety the present organization, related activities, and the aftermath impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💵 The Social Return on Investment (SROI), like the investment rate, combines social benefit and the economic model. For example, the calculation result is $4.5, which means that for every $1 invested, you can create a social price value of $4.5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💁These new evaluation methods, just as the rate of investment and reporting, present the public welfare production of the social association department. They let all those who put into action know how much practical benefit to society and the environment is generated by what they are doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📐Many special cases in the public department will have an impact on society. Therefore, impact evaluation has also been widely valued by the government of various countries as a tool to help make decisions. As far as the “open government” is concerned, as a result of withholding the 16th goal of sustainable development of the United Nations, it has now become the principle of all countries in the world. Whether it is application of cross-departmental data, or coordination with the community of citizens, there is a great need for a global assessment, so that the community and the government can connect with each other and move forward successfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌎I am now at the opening of the Open Government Partnership (OGP) Summit in Canada. This year, Taiwan is not only invited to share the experience of “Presidential Hackathon,” but will also cooperate with the scientific and technological community of citizens and representatives of the governments of various countries to make a common endorsement and mutual reference to the evaluation model, so that the effectiveness of the opening will no longer be limited to the number of data sets, but will also measure the impact on people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞There is one of the most active open communities in the world in Taiwan. Based on that, we will adopt the spirit of impact assessment. Through co-creation with citizens, we will condense it into an “Open Government National Action Plan” so that the world can see how the “warm power” of democracy in Taiwan can be transformed into “global impact” for the whole world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">Through co-creation with citizens, we will condense it into an ”Open Government National Action Plan” so that the world can see how the ”warm power” of democracy in Taiwan can be transformed into ”global impact” for the whole world.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/3/32c68698d6b30829ea114ec939c478d0657b2ad2.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Village’s Journey to Sustainable Fashion</title><link href="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%80%E5%80%8B%E6%9D%91%E8%8E%8A%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E6%99%82%E5%B0%9A%E4%B9%8B%E6%97%85/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Village's Journey to Sustainable Fashion" /><published>2019-05-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%80%E5%80%8B%E6%9D%91%E8%8E%8A%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E6%99%82%E5%B0%9A%E4%B9%8B%E6%97%85</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://pdis.nat.gov.tw/en/blog/%E5%95%86%E5%91%A8%E5%B0%88%E6%AC%84-%E4%B8%80%E5%80%8B%E6%9D%91%E8%8E%8A%E7%9A%84%E6%B0%B8%E7%BA%8C%E6%99%82%E5%B0%9A%E4%B9%8B%E6%97%85/">&lt;p&gt;💎 Have you ever thought that jewelry we wear could be made from environmental waste?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🇮🇩 A little while ago, I heard about a very interesting project—the &lt;a href=&quot;https://issuu.com/sl_studio/docs/fashion_village_lab_roadmap&quot;&gt;Fashion Village Lab&lt;/a&gt; in Cigondewah, Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏆 This year, in order to promote regional sustainable development, the Ministry of Economic Affairs is conducting the first &lt;a href=&quot;https://apses.asia/award/apply&quot;&gt;Asia-Pacific Social Innovation Cooperation Award&lt;/a&gt;. It has received entrants from as many as 13 countries, and ended up with 62 teams in total. The Fashion Village Lab is one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🏭 Indonesia is a garment manufacturing powerhouse. Bandung City accounts for 40% of the national garment output value. Bandung’s Cigondewah area is a distribution center for international brand manufacturers. Five years ago, the Bandung Creative Cities Forum (BCCF) and Dutch researchers established a presence there because the factory’s waste pollution was affecting the quality of life for local workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚸After learning more about it, they combined local community strength to launch the Fashion Village Lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;♻️The lab’s vision is to create a self-sufficient “circular creative ecosystem”: transforming solid pollutants produced in factories into products such as building blocks and jewelry; collaborating with students in architecture and design-related fields to build stores that showcase production processes, retain land for dyeing plants, develop new materials, and conduct experiments on sustainable textiles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🌐 The success of the Fashion Village Lab is based on an effective “3C formula”: connecting with local stakeholders (Connect), inviting everyone to collaborate (Collaborate), and finally incorporating businesses and stakeholders to expand innovative business models (Commerce). This formula is based on the field work of the Bandung Creative City Forum in the past ten years. It has successfully connected the stakeholders in production, government, study, research, and society, and has also made Bandung a member of the UNESCO “Creative City” network (&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.unesco.org/creative-cities/bandung&quot;&gt;UCCN&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🎁 Now that the Fashion Village Laboratory is in its final stages, and the Kawasan Wisata Sandang Cooperative, which is run by local women and youths, is ready to sell the finished products of the circular economy through the lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💞 This year, Cigondewah’s team was unanimously recognized by a panel of experts from Japan, Singapore, Australia, Thailand, and India, and was awarded the “Special Jury Prize”. They will come to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://apses.asia&quot;&gt;Asia Pacific Social Enterprise Summit&lt;/a&gt; in May this year to accept the award. Everyone is welcome to come to Kaohsiung to meet these excellent teams and explore new possibilities for regional revitalization.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Audrey Tang, Sheau-Tyng Peng</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="Social Innovation" /><summary type="html">This year, Cigondewah's team was unanimously recognized by a panel of experts from Japan, Singapore, Australia, Thailand, and India, and was awarded the “Special Jury Prize”.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://talk.pdis.nat.gov.tw/uploads/default/original/2X/7/718c3380c9efb619b63f7f850fb2a1ed368a5c81.jpeg" /></entry></feed>